<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><Project name="Arma3">
  <Package name="Languagemissions_Jets">
    <Container name="Missions">
      <Key ID="str_a3_codename_hornet">
        <Original>Hornet</Original>
        <Chinese>大黃蜂</Chinese>
        <French>Hornet</French>
        <Spanish>Hornet</Spanish>
        <Italian>Hornet</Italian>
        <Polish>Hornet</Polish>
        <Russian>Hornet</Russian>
        <German>Hornet</German>
        <Czech>Hornet</Czech>
        <English>Hornet</English>
        <Portuguese>Vespa</Portuguese>
        <Korean>호넷</Korean>
        <Chinesesimp>大黄蜂</Chinesesimp>
        <Japanese>ホーネット</Japanese>
      </Key>
      <Key ID="str_a3_codename_freeway">
        <Original>Freeway</Original>
        <Chinese>自由路</Chinese>
        <French>Freeway</French>
        <Spanish>Freeway</Spanish>
        <Italian>Freeway</Italian>
        <Polish>Freeway</Polish>
        <Russian>Freeway</Russian>
        <German>Freeway</German>
        <Czech>Freeway</Czech>
        <English>Freeway</English>
        <Portuguese>Expressa</Portuguese>
        <Korean>프리웨이</Korean>
        <Chinesesimp>自由路</Chinesesimp>
        <Japanese>フリーウェイ</Japanese>
      </Key>
      <Key ID="str_a3_identity_ChrisCampbell">
        <Original>Chris Campbell</Original>
        <Chinese>克里斯·坎貝爾</Chinese>
        <French>Chris Campbell</French>
        <Spanish>Chris Campbell</Spanish>
        <Italian>Chris Campbell</Italian>
        <Polish>Chris Campbell</Polish>
        <Russian>Chris Campbell</Russian>
        <German>Chris Campbell</German>
        <Czech>Chris Campbell</Czech>
        <English>Chris Campbell</English>
        <Portuguese>Chris Campbell</Portuguese>
        <Korean>크리스 캠벨</Korean>
        <Chinesesimp>克里斯·坎贝尔</Chinesesimp>
        <Japanese>クリス・キャンベル</Japanese>
      </Key>
      <Container name="Showcase_Jets" dialogName="Showcase_Jets">
        <Key ID="str_a3_showcase_jets_x15_agmlaunch_pilot_0">
          <Original>Rifle.</Original>
          <Chinese>對地導彈.</Chinese>
          <French>Canon.</French>
          <Spanish>Disparo.</Spanish>
          <Italian>Lancio missile aria-terra.</Italian>
          <Polish>Pocisk wystrzelony.</Polish>
          <Russian>Пошла к земле.</Russian>
          <German>Rakete abgefeuert.</German>
          <Czech>Střela vypálena.</Czech>
          <English>Rifle.</English>
          <Portuguese>Míssil lançado.</Portuguese>
          <Korean>미사일 발사.</Korean>
          <Chinesesimp>对地导弹.</Chinesesimp>
          <Japanese>「ライフル」。</Japanese>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="str_a3_showcase_jets_x10_bomblaunch_pilot_0">
          <Original>Bombs away.</Original>
          <Chinese>炸彈投出.</Chinese>
          <French>Bombes larguées.</French>
          <Spanish>Bombas fuera.</Spanish>
          <Italian>Sgancio bombe.</Italian>
          <Polish>Bomby zrzucone.</Polish>
          <Russian>Бомбы сброшены.</Russian>
          <German>Bombe abgeworfen.</German>
          <Czech>Bomby odhozeny.</Czech>
          <English>Bombs away.</English>
          <Portuguese>Bombas lançadas.</Portuguese>
          <Korean>폭탄을 투하했다.</Korean>
          <Chinesesimp>炸弹投出.</Chinesesimp>
          <Japanese>爆弾投下。</Japanese>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="str_a3_showcase_jets_x05_aa120launch_pilot_0">
          <Original>Fox Three.</Original>
          <Chinese>主動雷達導彈.</Chinese>
          <French>Fox trois.</French>
          <Spanish>Fox Tres.</Spanish>
          <Italian>Lancio missile a guida attiva.</Italian>
          <Polish>Fox 3.</Polish>
          <Russian>Ракета три выпущена.</Russian>
          <German>Fox Drei.</German>
          <Czech>Střela tři vypálena.</Czech>
          <English>Fox Three.</English>
          <Portuguese>Míssil de radar ativo.</Portuguese>
          <Korean>폭스 3.</Korean>
          <Chinesesimp>主动雷达导弹.</Chinesesimp>
          <Japanese>FOX 3。</Japanese>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="str_a3_showcase_jets_x01_aa9launch_pilot_0">
          <Original>Fox Two.</Original>
          <Chinese>紅外線導彈.</Chinese>
          <French>Fox deux.</French>
          <Spanish>Fox Dos.</Spanish>
          <Italian>Lancio missile a guida infrarossa.</Italian>
          <Polish>Fox 2.</Polish>
          <Russian>Ракета два выпущена.</Russian>
          <German>Fox Zwei.</German>
          <Czech>Střela dvě vypálena.</Czech>
          <English>Fox Two.</English>
          <Portuguese>Míssil de calor.</Portuguese>
          <Korean>폭스 2.</Korean>
          <Chinesesimp>红外线导弹.</Chinesesimp>
          <Japanese>FOX 2。</Japanese>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="str_a3_showcase_jets_titlecard">
          <Original>SHOWCASE: FIGHTER JETS - New fixed-wing aircraft, Improved sensors, Dynamic load-outs</Original>
          <Chinese>任務展示: 戰鬥機 - 新的固定翼飛機, 改進的傳感器, 動態裝備</Chinese>
          <French>PRÉSENTATION : CHASSEURS - Nouvel avion, capteurs repensés, chargements dynamiques</French>
          <Spanish>EXHIBICIÓN: CAZAS: Nuevos aviones de ala fija, sensores mejorados y cargas dinámicas</Spanish>
          <Italian>DIMOSTRAZIONI: JET DA CACCIA - nuovo velivolo ad ala fissa, sensori migliorati, carico dinamico</Italian>
          <Polish>PREZENTACJA: MYŚLIWCE ODRZUTOWE – nowe statki powietrzne, ulepszone czujniki, dynamiczne uzbrojenie</Polish>
          <Russian>ДЕМОНСТРАЦИЯ: ИСТРЕБИТЕЛИ - Новые самолеты, улучшенные датчики, динамичные комплекты экипировки</Russian>
          <German>PRÄSENTATION: KAMPFJETS – Neue Starrflügler, verbesserte Sensoren, dynamische Ausrüstung</German>
          <Czech>UKÁZKA: STÍHACÍ LETOUNY – Nové stíhací letouny, modernizované snímače, dynamická výzbroj</Czech>
          <English>SHOWCASE: FIGHTER JETS - New fixed-wing aircraft, Improved sensors, Dynamic load-outs</English>
          <Portuguese>MOSTRUÁRIO: JATOS DE COMBATE - Nova aeronave de asa fixa, sensores aprimorados, cargas dinâmicas</Portuguese>
          <Korean>쇼케이스: 전투기 - 신종 전투기, 신규 피해 모델, 최첨단 레이더 시스템, 항공 모함 작전</Korean>
          <Chinesesimp>任务展示: 战斗机 - 新的固定翼飞机, 改进的传感器, 动态装备</Chinesesimp>
          <Japanese>ショーケース：ジェット戦闘機 - 新たな固定翼機、改善されたセンサー、ダイナミック ロードアウト</Japanese>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="str_a3_showcase_jets_sitrep_text">
          <Original>USS Freedom, Mediterranean Sea</Original>
          <Chinese>美國海軍自由號, 地中海</Chinese>
          <French>USS Freedom, mer Méditerranée</French>
          <Spanish>USS Freedom, mar Mediterráneo</Spanish>
          <Italian>USS Freedom, Mar Mediterraneo</Italian>
          <Polish>USS Freedom, Morze Śródziemne</Polish>
          <Russian>USS Freedom, Средиземное море</Russian>
          <German>USS Freedom, Mittelmeer</German>
          <Czech>USS Freedom, Středozemní moře</Czech>
          <English>USS Freedom, Mediterranean Sea</English>
          <Portuguese>USS Freedom, Mar Mediterrâneo</Portuguese>
          <Korean>USS Freedom, 지중해</Korean>
          <Chinesesimp>美国海军自由号, 地中海</Chinesesimp>
          <Japanese>地中海・USS「フリーダム」</Japanese>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="str_a3_showcase_jets_showcase_summary_title">
          <Original>Showcase</Original>
          <Chinese>任務展示</Chinese>
          <French>Démonstration</French>
          <Spanish>Exhibición</Spanish>
          <Italian>Dimostrazioni</Italian>
          <Polish>Prezentacja</Polish>
          <Russian>Демонстрация</Russian>
          <German>Präsentation</German>
          <Czech>Ukázka</Czech>
          <English>Showcase</English>
          <Portuguese>Mostruário</Portuguese>
          <Korean>쇼케이스</Korean>
          <Chinesesimp>任务展示</Chinesesimp>
          <Japanese>ショーケース</Japanese>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="str_a3_showcase_jets_showcase_summary_text">
          <Original>Dominate the skies of Altis in your fighter jet.</Original>
          <Chinese>駕駛戰鬥機去稱霸Altis的天空.</Chinese>
          <French>Dominez le ciel d'Altis aux commandes de votre chasseur.</French>
          <Spanish>Hazte con el control de los cielos de Altis con tu caza.</Spanish>
          <Italian>Domina i cieli di Altis a bordo del tuo jet da caccia.</Italian>
          <Polish>Zdominuj przestworza za sterem myśliwca odrzutowego.</Polish>
          <Russian>Доминируйте в небе над Алтисом в истребителе.</Russian>
          <German>Dominiere den Himmel über Altis in deinem Kampfjet.</German>
          <Czech>Ovládněte ve stíhacím letounu nebe nad Altisem.</Czech>
          <English>Dominate the skies of Altis in your fighter jet.</English>
          <Portuguese>Domine o céu de Altis no seu avião de combate.</Portuguese>
          <Korean>자네 전투기로 알티스 상공을 지배하라.</Korean>
          <Chinesesimp>驾驶战斗机去称霸Altis的天空.</Chinesesimp>
          <Japanese>アルティスの空をジェット戦闘機で制圧せよ。</Japanese>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="str_a3_showcase_jets_mission_name">
          <Original>Fighter Jets</Original>
          <Chinese>戰鬥機</Chinese>
          <French>Chasseurs</French>
          <Spanish>Cazas</Spanish>
          <Italian>Jet da caccia</Italian>
          <Polish>Myśliwce odrzutowe</Polish>
          <Russian>Истребители</Russian>
          <German>Kampfjets</German>
          <Czech>Stíhací letouny</Czech>
          <English>Fighter Jets</English>
          <Portuguese>Jatos de combate</Portuguese>
          <Korean>전투기</Korean>
          <Chinesesimp>战斗机</Chinesesimp>
          <Japanese>ジェット戦闘機</Japanese>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="str_a3_showcase_jets_debriefing_win04_description">
          <Original>Despite your best efforts, you were unable to destroy enemy targets. But our presence over Altis will make the enemy think twice before they try anything else.</Original>
          <Chinese>儘管你盡了最大的努力, 你還是無法消滅掉敵軍目標. 但我們仍能掩護整個Altis的天空, 敵人在做任何行動前一定會再三考慮清楚.</Chinese>
          <French>Vous n'êtes pas parvenu à détruire les cibles ennemies; mais notre simple présence sur Altis fera réfléchir l'ennemi à deux fois avant de tenter quoi que ce soit d'autre.</French>
          <Spanish>A pesar de esforzarte al máximo, no has podido destruir a los objetivos enemigos. Sin embargo, nuestra presencia en Altis hará que el enemigo se lo piense dos veces antes de intentar algo más.</Spanish>
          <Italian>Non sei riuscito a distruggere i bersagli nemici nonostante tu ci abbia provato fino in fondo. Tuttavia, considerata la nostra presenza su Altis, il nemico dovrà pensarci due volte prima che provi a fare qualcos'altro.</Italian>
          <Polish>Mimo podjętych wysiłków nie udało ci się zniszczyć celów, jednak nasza obecność powietrzna na Altis zmusi przeciwnika do przemyślenia działań.</Polish>
          <Russian>Несмотря на все ваши усилия, вы не смогли уничтожить вражеские цели. Однако наше присутствие над Алтисом заставит врага подумать дважды, прежде чем они предпримут что-нибудь еще.</Russian>
          <German>Trotz deiner Mühen hast du es nicht geschafft, die feindlichen Ziele zu zerstören. Dank unserer Präsenz über Altis wird der Feind es sich jedoch zweimal überlegen, ob er es ein weiteres Mal versucht. </German>
          <Czech>I přes veškeré úsilí se vám nepovedlo zničit nepřátelské cíle. Díky vaší přítomnosti na Altisu si však nepřátelé pořádně rozmyslí, zda zkusí ještě něco dalšího.</Czech>
          <English>Despite your best efforts, you were unable to destroy enemy targets. But our presence over Altis will make the enemy think twice before they try anything else.</English>
          <Portuguese>Apesar de se esforçar ao máximo, você não conseguiu destruir os alvos inimigos. Porém, a nossa presença nos céus de Altis fará o inimigo pensar duas vezes antes de tentar qualquer outra coisa.</Portuguese>
          <Korean>최선을 다했지만 표적된 놈들을 파괴하지 못했다. 알티스 내 우리 병력때문에 적들은 신중히 행동할 거다.</Korean>
          <Chinesesimp>尽管你尽了最大的努力, 你还是无法消灭掉敌军目标. 但我们仍能掩护整个Altis的天空, 敌人在做任何行动前一定会再三考虑清楚.</Chinesesimp>
          <Japanese>貴官の努力むなしく、敵目標の撃破は叶わなかった。だがアルティス上空における我が軍の存在は、敵に行動を躊躇させるには十分だろう。</Japanese>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="str_a3_showcase_jets_debriefing_win03_description">
          <Original>Outstanding job, pilot! The skies are clear and ground units are pushing through the enemy lines.</Original>
          <Chinese>幹的真棒, 飛行員! 天空已經安全, 而我們地面的部隊也開始在進攻了.</Chinese>
          <French>Très bon boulot, pilote ! Le ciel est vide de toute menace, et les unités au sol peuvent percer les lignes ennemies.</French>
          <Spanish>¡Buen trabajo, piloto! El cielo está despejado y las unidades terrestres están abriéndose paso a través de las líneas enemigas.</Spanish>
          <Italian>Un lavoro eccellente, pilota! Il cielo è libero dai nemici e le unità di terra spingono verso le linee nemiche.</Italian>
          <Polish>Doskonała robota, pilocie! Przestrzeń powietrzna została oczyszczona, a jednostki naziemne nacierają na linie przeciwnika.</Polish>
          <Russian>Превосходная работа, пилот! Горизонт чист, а наземные части пробиваются сквозь вражеские линии.</Russian>
          <German>Herausragende Arbeit, Pilot! Der Himmel ist klar und unsere Bodentruppen überrennen den Feind. </German>
          <Czech>Vynikající práce, pilote! Nebe je čisté a pozemní jednotky pronikají nepřátelskými liniemi.</Czech>
          <English>Outstanding job, pilot! The skies are clear and ground units are pushing through the enemy lines.</English>
          <Portuguese>Excelente trabalho, piloto! O céu está livre e as unidades terrestres estão avançando pelas linhas inimigas.</Portuguese>
          <Korean>훌륭하다. 조종사! 상공은 안전하고 지상병력이 적진으로 돌진 중이다.</Korean>
          <Chinesesimp>干的真棒, 飞行员! 天空已经安全, 而我们地面的部队也开始在进攻了.</Chinesesimp>
          <Japanese>見事な成果だ、パイロット！空に敵影は無く、地上部隊が敵の戦線を突破しつつある。</Japanese>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="str_a3_showcase_jets_debriefing_win02_description">
          <Original>Good job, pilot! You've supported the ground assault by destroying an enemy strongpoint.</Original>
          <Chinese>幹的好, 飛行員! 你成功打擊了一處敵方據點來讓我軍地面部隊得到支援.</Chinese>
          <French>Bon boulot, pilote ! Vous avez aidé l'assaut terrestre en détruisant un bastion ennemi.</French>
          <Spanish>¡Buen trabajo, piloto! Has apoyado el asalto terrestre al destruir un punto clave enemigo.</Spanish>
          <Italian>Un ottimo lavoro, pilota! Hai supportato l'attacco di terra distruggendo un punto di forza nemico.</Italian>
          <Polish>Dobra robota, pilocie! Udzieliłeś wsparcia uderzeniu naziemnemu, niszcząc punkt umocnienia przeciwnika.</Polish>
          <Russian>Хорошая работа, пилот! Вы поддержали наземную атаку, уничтожив вражеский опорный пункт.</Russian>
          <German>Gute Arbeit, Pilot! Du hast durch die Zerstörung der feindlichen Position den Bodenangriff unterstützt.</German>
          <Czech>Dobrá práce, pilote! Povedlo se vám zničit nepřátelské opevnění a podpořit pozemní útok.</Czech>
          <English>Good job, pilot! You've supported the ground assault by destroying an enemy strongpoint.</English>
          <Portuguese>Bom trabalho, piloto! Você apoiou o ataque terrestre, destruindo uma fortaleza inimiga.</Portuguese>
          <Korean>잘했다. 조종사! 적의 거점 지역을 파괴하여 지상 공격을 지원했다</Korean>
          <Chinesesimp>干的好, 飞行员! 你成功打击了一处敌方据点来让我军地面部队得到支援.</Chinesesimp>
          <Japanese>よくやった、パイロット！敵の拠点を破壊することで地上による進撃を支援することができた。</Japanese>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="str_a3_showcase_jets_debriefing_win01_description">
          <Original>Good job, pilot! Opfor air threats have been eliminated. The skies are clear.</Original>
          <Chinese>幹的好, 飛行員! 敵方空中單位已被殲滅. 天空是我們的了.</Chinese>
          <French>Bon boulot, pilote ! Les menaces aériennes ennemies ont été éliminées. Ciel dégagé.</French>
          <Spanish>¡Muy bien, piloto! Las amenazas aéreas de los rivales han sido eliminadas y el cielo está despejado.</Spanish>
          <Italian>Un ottimo lavoro, pilota! Le minacce aeree sono state eliminate e il cielo è ora libero da nemici.</Italian>
          <Polish>Dobra robota, pilocie! Zagrożenie z powietrza zostało wyeliminowane. Przestworza są czyste.</Polish>
          <Russian>Хорошая работа, пилот! Воздушные угрозы OPFOR были устранены. Небо чисто.</Russian>
          <German>Gute Arbeit, Pilot! Die Opfor-Lufteinheiten wurden eliminiert. Der Himmel ist klar.</German>
          <Czech>Dobrá práce, pilote! Nepřátelské vzdušné hrozby byly zničeny. Nebe je čisté.</Czech>
          <English>Good job, pilot! Opfor air threats have been eliminated. The skies are clear.</English>
          <Portuguese>Bom trabalho, piloto! As ameaças aéreas da Opfor foram eliminadas. O céu está livre.</Portuguese>
          <Korean>잘했다. 조종사! OPFOR의 항공 위협이 제거됐다. 상공이 안전하다.</Korean>
          <Chinesesimp>干的好, 飞行员! 敌方空中单位已被歼灭. 天空是我们的了.</Chinesesimp>
          <Japanese>よくやった、パイロット！敵性航空戦力を撃滅することができた。もう空に敵影は無い。</Japanese>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="str_a3_showcase_jets_debriefing_fail02_description">
          <Original>Your plane was shot down over Altis.</Original>
          <Chinese>你的飛機在Altis上被擊落了.</Chinese>
          <French>Votre avion a été abattu au-dessus d'Altis.</French>
          <Spanish>Tu avión ha sido derribado en Altis.</Spanish>
          <Italian>Il tuo aereo è stato abbattuto su Altis.</Italian>
          <Polish>Twój samolot został zestrzelony nad Altis.</Polish>
          <Russian>Ваш самолет был сбит над Алтисом.</Russian>
          <German>Dein Flugzeug wurde über Altis abgeschossen.</German>
          <Czech>Váš letoun byl nad Altisem sestřelen.</Czech>
          <English>Your plane was shot down over Altis.</English>
          <Portuguese>Seu avião foi derrubado em Altis.</Portuguese>
          <Korean>자네 비행기가 알티스로 추락했다.</Korean>
          <Chinesesimp>你的飞机在Altis上被击落了.</Chinesesimp>
          <Japanese>貴官の乗機はアルティス上空で撃墜されてしまった。</Japanese>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="str_a3_showcase_jets_debriefing_fail01_description">
          <Original>You were unable to respond to enemy air threats in time. NATO ground units met with heavy casualties. The advance has been halted.</Original>
          <Chinese>你無法及時殲滅掉敵方的空中威脅. 北約的地面部隊已承受沉重的打擊. 進攻的腳步被迫停止.</Chinese>
          <French>Vous n'avez pas réussi à neutraliser à temps la menace aérienne ennemie. Les unités terrestres de l'OTAN ont subi de lourdes pertes. Notre progression a été stoppée.</French>
          <Spanish>No has podido responder a las amenazas aéreas enemigas a tiempo. Las unidades terrestres de la OTAN han sufrido varias bajas, por lo que han detenido el avance.</Spanish>
          <Italian>Non sei riuscito a rispondere alle minacce aeree nemiche in tempo. Le unità di terra NATO hanno subito pesanti perdite. L'avanzata è stata arrestata.</Italian>
          <Polish>Nie udało ci się zareagować odpowiednio szybko na zagrożenie z powietrza. Siły naziemne NATO odniosły duże straty. Natarcie zostało powstrzymane.</Polish>
          <Russian>Вы не смогли своевременно среагировать на вражеские воздушные угрозы. Наземные подразделения НАТО понесли большие потери. Продвижение приостановилось.</Russian>
          <German>Du hast es nicht geschafft, dich rechtzeitig gegen die feindlichen Lufteinheiten durchzusetzen. Die NATO-Bodentruppen haben schwere Verluste erlitten und ihr Vorstoß wurde aufgehalten.</German>
          <Czech>Na nepřátelské vzdušné hrozby se vám nepovedlo včas zareagovat. Pozemní jednotky NATO utrpěly těžké ztráty. Postup našich jednotek se zastavil.</Czech>
          <English>You were unable to respond to enemy air threats in time. NATO ground units met with heavy casualties. The advance has been halted.</English>
          <Portuguese>Você não conseguiu responder às ameaças aéreas do inimigo a tempo. As unidades terrestres da OTAN sofreram grandes baixas. O avanço foi interrompido.</Portuguese>
          <Korean>적의 항공 위협에 제때 대응하지 못했다. NATO 지상 병력이 꽤 많은 사상자를 목격했다. 진격이 중지됐다.</Korean>
          <Chinesesimp>你无法及时歼灭掉敌方的空中威胁. 北约的地面部队已承受沉重的打击. 进攻的脚步被迫停止.</Chinesesimp>
          <Japanese>時間内に敵の航空戦力の脅威に対応できなかった。NATO 軍地上部隊には多大な損耗が発生。進軍は中断された。</Japanese>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="str_a3_showcase_jets_briefing_situation_text">
          <Original>After the AAF surrender, NATO continue to clean up remnants of CSAT forces to the northeast. Progress has been halted after CSAT brought in fast-air assets to interdict our ground assault. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Air superiority is vital for victory. USS Freedom has been deployed to Altis. As an F/A-181 fighter pilot, your task is to secure the %4airspace%1 to allow ground assets to continue their attack.</Original>
          <Chinese>在Altis政府軍投降以後, 北約繼續肅清北面殘存的廣協同盟部隊. 但攻勢被迫在廣協同盟高速戰鬥機的威脅下暫時停止了腳步. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;掌握空優將是這場戰役的關鍵. 美國海軍自由號已經被佈署到Altis周邊. 做為一名F/A-181"黑蜂"2型戰鬥攻擊機的飛行員, 你的任務將是去肅清整片%4空域%1來讓我們的地面部隊得以繼續進攻.</Chinese>
          <French>Après la capitulation de l'AAF, l'OTAN a poursuivi son effort d'élimination des forces CSAT restantes au nord-est. Notre avancée terrestre a été interrompue par l'appui aérien rapide du CSAT. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;La supériorité aérienne est indispensable à la victoire. L'USS Freedom a été déployé près d'Altis. En tant que pilote de F/A-181, votre mission est de sécuriser l'%4espace aérien%1 pour permettre aux unités terrestres de poursuivre leur assaut.</French>
          <Spanish>Después de que las Fuerzas Armas de Altis se rindiesen, la OTAN sigue limpiando los restos de las fuerzas del CSAT que se encuentran en el noreste. Al avance ha sido detenido después de que el CSAT haya traído unidades aéreas rápidas para detener nuestro asalto terrestre. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;La superioridad aérea es clave para alzarse con la victoria. El USS Freedom ha sido desplegado en Altis. Como piloto del caza F/A-181, debes asegurar el %4espacio aéreo%1 para permitir que las unidades terrestres continúen con su ataque.</Spanish>
          <Italian>Dopo la resa della AAF, la NATO continua a ripulire quel che è rimasto delle forze CSAT presenti nel nordest. I progressi si sono arrestati dopo che la CSAT ha introdotto risorse aeree rapide che mettono i bastoni tra le ruote al nostro attacco via terra. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;La superiorità aerea è fondamentale per la vittoria. L'USS Freedom è stata schierata ad Altis. In quanto pilota da caccia del F/A-181, il tuo obiettivo è di mettere al sicuro lo %4spazio aereo%1 per consentire alle risorse di terra di proseguire il loro attacco.</Italian>
          <Polish>Po kapitulacji AAF siły NATO wciąż oczyszczają ogniska oporu CSAT na północnym wschodzie. Działania zwolniły po nadciągnięciu wsparcia sił powietrznych CSAT, które mają wstrzymać natarcie sił naziemnych. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Przewaga powietrzna ma tu kluczowe znaczenie. USS Freedom został skierowany w obszar działań na Altis. Jako pilot F/A-181 masz za zadanie zabezpieczyć %4przestrzeń powietrzną%1, aby umożliwić siłom naziemnym wznowienie uderzenia.</Polish>
          <Russian>После капитуляции AAF НАТО продолжает зачищать остатки сил CSAT на северо-востоке. Продвижение приостановилось после того, как CSAT получили в распоряжение скоростную авиацию для пресечения нашего наземного наступления. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Превосходство в воздухе жизненно важно для победы. USS Freedom были развернуты на Алтисе. Вы, как пилот истребителя F/A-181, должны взять под контроль %4воздушное пространство%1, чтобы наземные войска смогли продолжить атаку.</Russian>
          <German>Nach der Kapitulation der AAF ist die NATO weiterhin damit beschäftigt, die restlichen CSAT-Truppen im Nordosten zu beseitigen. Seitdem CSAT schnelle Lufteinheiten gegen unsere Bodentruppen einsetzt, hat es keine Fortschritte mehr gegeben. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Lufthoheit ist für den Sieg unbedingt erforderlich. Die USS Freedom wurde nach Altis versetzt. Als F/A-181-Kampfpilot ist es dein Job, den %4Luftraum%1 zu sichern, damit unsere Bodentruppen ihren Angriff fortsetzen können.</German>
          <Czech>Po kapitulaci AAF pokračuje NATO na severovýchodě v čištění oblasti od zbytků sil CSAT. Postup se zastavil, když síly CSAT podpořily letecké jednotky, které nám zabraňují v pozemním útoku. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;K dosažení vítězství je letecká převaha klíčová. K Altisu byla vyslána letadlová loď USS Freedom. Vaším úkolem jako pilota stíhacího letounu F/A-181 je zajistit %4vzdušný prostor%1 a umožnit pozemním jednotkám pokračovat v útoku.</Czech>
          <English>After the AAF surrender, NATO continue to clean up remnants of CSAT forces to the northeast. Progress has been halted after CSAT brought in fast-air assets to interdict our ground assault. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Air superiority is vital for victory. USS Freedom has been deployed to Altis. As an F/A-181 fighter pilot, your task is to secure the %4airspace%1 to allow ground assets to continue their attack.</English>
          <Portuguese>Após a rendição do AAF, a OTAN continua eliminando os remanescentes das forças da CSAT a nordeste. O progresso foi interrompido depois que a CSAT trouxe recursos aéreos para proibir a nossa investida no solo. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;A superioridade aérea é vital para a vitória. O USS Freedom foi liberado em Altis. Como piloto de caça de um F/A-181, sua tarefa é proteger o %4espaço aéreo%1 para permitir que as tropas terrestres continuem o ataque.</Portuguese>
          <Korean>AAF가 항복한 후에도 NATO는 계속해서 북동쪽 CSAT 잔여군을 소탕하고 있다. CSAT가 우리 지상 공격을 저지기 위해 빠른 고속 항공자산을 도입한 후 진전이 중지된 상태다. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;제공권이 승리의 관건이다. USS Freedom을 알티스에 배치했다. F/A-181 전투기 조종사로서 자네 임무는 지상 자산이 공격을 지속할 수 있도록 %4영공%1을 확보하는 것이다.</Korean>
          <Chinesesimp>在Altis政府军投降以后, 北约继续肃清北面残存的广协同盟部队. 但攻势被迫在广协同盟高速战斗机的威胁下暂时停止了脚步. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;掌握空优将是这场战役的关键. 美国海军自由号已经被布署到Altis周边. 做为一名F/A-181"黑蜂"2型战斗攻击机的飞行员, 你的任务将是去肃清整片%4空域%1来让我们的地面部队得以继续进攻.</Chinesesimp>
          <Japanese>AAF の降伏後、NATO 軍は北東の CSAT 残存部隊の掃討を継続していた。だが CSAT 軍は我が軍の進攻を阻むべく、高速飛行が可能な航空戦力を投入、これにより進軍が停滞している。&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;勝利には制空権の確保が重要となる。現在、USS「フリーダム」がアルティスに展開。貴官の任務は、F/A-181 戦闘機のパイロットとして、地上部隊が進行を続行できるよう%4同空域%1を確保することになる。</Japanese>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="str_a3_showcase_jets_briefing_signal_text">
          <Original>Hornet - Your squadron &lt;br/&gt;Eagle - Friendly squadron &lt;br/&gt;Freeway - USS Freedom</Original>
          <Chinese>大黃蜂 - 你的中隊 &lt;br/&gt;老鷹 - 友軍中隊 &lt;br/&gt;自由路 - 美國海軍自由號</Chinese>
          <French>Hornet - Votre escadrille. &lt;br/&gt;Eagle - Escadrille alliée &lt;br/&gt;Freeway - USS Freedom.</French>
          <Spanish>Hornet: Tu escuadrón. &lt;br/&gt;Eagle: Escuadrón aliado. &lt;br/&gt;Freeway: USS Freedom.</Spanish>
          <Italian>Hornet - il tuo squadrone. &lt;br/&gt;Eagle - squadrone alleato &lt;br/&gt;Freeway - USS Freedom.</Italian>
          <Polish>Hornet – twoja eskadra. &lt;br/&gt;Eagle – sojusznicza eskadra. &lt;br/&gt;Freeway – USS Freedom.</Polish>
          <Russian>Hornet – ваша эскадра. &lt;br/&gt;Eagle – дружественная эскадра &lt;br/&gt;Freeway – USS Freedom.</Russian>
          <German>Hornet – deine Staffel. &lt;br/&gt;Eagle – verbündete Staffel &lt;br/&gt;Freeway – USS Freedom</German>
          <Czech>Hornet – vaše letka &lt;br/&gt;Eagle – spojenecká letka &lt;br/&gt;Freeway – USS Freedom</Czech>
          <English>Hornet - Your squadron &lt;br/&gt;Eagle - Friendly squadron &lt;br/&gt;Freeway - USS Freedom</English>
          <Portuguese>Vespa: Seu esquadrão. &lt;br/&gt;Águia: Esquadrão amigável &lt;br/&gt;Expressa: USS Freedom.</Portuguese>
          <Korean>호넷 - 소속 중대. &lt;br/&gt;이글 - 아군 중대 &lt;br/&gt;프리웨이 - USS Freedom.</Korean>
          <Chinesesimp>大黄蜂 - 你的中队 &lt;br/&gt;老鹰 - 友军中队 &lt;br/&gt;自由路 - 美国海军自由号</Chinesesimp>
          <Japanese>ホーネット - 貴官の飛行隊&lt;br/&gt;イーグル - 友軍飛行隊&lt;br/&gt;フリーウェイ - USS「フリーダム」</Japanese>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="str_a3_showcase_jets_briefing_mission_text">
          <Original>CSAT jets have been spotted over Altis. Patrol the %4airspace%1 and eliminate hostile air assets.</Original>
          <Chinese>廣協同盟的戰鬥機被發現出沒於Altis的上空. 前往該%4空域%1進行巡邏並殲滅掉敵軍的空中單位.</Chinese>
          <French>Des chasseurs du CSAT ont été repérés au-dessus d'Altis. Patrouillez l'%4espace aérien%1 et éliminez les cibles aériennes hostiles.</French>
          <Spanish>Se han visto cazas del CSAT sobre Altis. Patrulla el %4espacio aéreo%1 y elimina las unidades aéreas hostiles del enemigo.</Spanish>
          <Italian>Sono stati avvistati dei jet CSAT su Altis. Perlustra lo %4spazio aereo%1 ed elimina le risorse aeree nemiche.</Italian>
          <Polish>Nad Altis zauważono odrzutowce CSAT. Patroluj %4przestrzeń powietrzną%1 i wyeliminuj siły powietrzne przeciwnika.</Polish>
          <Russian>Истребители CSAT были замечены над Алтисом. Патрулируйте %4воздушное пространство%1 и уничтожьте вражеский воздушный флот.</Russian>
          <German>CSAT-Jets wurden über ganz Altis gesichtet. Patrouilliere den %4Luftraum%1 und eliminiere feindliche Flugzeuge.</German>
          <Czech>Nad Altisem byly zpozorovány proudové letouny CSAT. Hlídkujte ve %4vzdušném prostoru%1 a zneškodněte nepřátelské letecké jednotky.</Czech>
          <English>CSAT jets have been spotted over Altis. Patrol the %4airspace%1 and eliminate hostile air assets.</English>
          <Portuguese>Os jatos CSAT foram avistados sobre Altis. Patrulhe o %4espaço aéreo%1 e elimine as aeronaves hostis.</Portuguese>
          <Korean>CSAT 제트기가 알티스 항공에서 탐지됐다. %4영공%1을 정찰하고 적의 항공자산을 제거하라.</Korean>
          <Chinesesimp>广协同盟的战斗机被发现出没于Altis的上空. 前往该%4空域%1进行巡逻并歼灭掉敌军的空中单位.</Chinesesimp>
          <Japanese>CSAT ジェット機がアルティス上空で目撃されている。%4空域%1内の哨戒を行い、敵性航空戦力を撃滅せよ。</Japanese>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="str_a3_showcase_jets_briefing_execution_text">
          <Original>1. Gear up, board your fighter jet and take off from %2USS Freedom%1. &lt;br/&gt;2. Patrol the %4airspace%1 and eliminate enemy air assets. &lt;br/&gt;3. Return to %2USS Freedom%1 and land.</Original>
          <Chinese>1. 整裝, 然後搭乘你的戰鬥機從%2美國海軍自由號%1上起飛. &lt;br/&gt;2. 前往該%4空域%1進行巡邏並殲滅掉敵軍的空中單位. &lt;br/&gt;3. 返回%2美國海軍自由號%1上降落.</Chinese>
          <French>1. Équipez-vous, montez à bord de votre chasseur et décollez de l'%2USS Freedom%1. &lt;br/&gt;2. Patrouillez l'%4espace aérien%1 et éliminez les unités aériennes ennemies. &lt;br/&gt;3. Retournez à l'%2USS Freedom%1 et appontez.</French>
          <Spanish>1. Prepárate, sube al caza y despega del %2USS Freedom%1. &lt;br/&gt;2. Patrulla el %4espacio aéreo%1 y elimina las unidades aéreas enemigas. &lt;br/&gt;3. Vuelve al %2USS Freedom%1 y aterriza.</Spanish>
          <Italian>1. Preparati, sali a bordo del tuo jet da caccia e decolla dall'%2USS Freedom%1. &lt;br/&gt;2. Perlustra lo %4spazio aereo%1 ed elimina le risorse aeree nemiche. &lt;br/&gt;3. Fai ritorno all'%2USS Freedom%1 e atterra.</Italian>
          <Polish>1. Przygotuj się, wsiądź za ster myśliwca i wystartuj z %2USS Freedom%1. &lt;br/&gt;2. Patroluj %4przestrzeń powietrzną%1 i wyeliminuj siły powietrzne przeciwnika. &lt;br/&gt;3. Powróć do %2USS Freedom%1 i wyląduj.</Polish>
          <Russian>1. Соберите снаряжение, сядьте в кабину истребителя и взлетите с %2USS Freedom%1. &lt;br/&gt;2. Патрулируйте %4воздушное пространство%1 и уничтожьте вражеский воздушный флот. &lt;br/&gt;3. Вернитесь на %2USS Freedom%1 и совершите посадку.</Russian>
          <German>1. Rüste dich aus, steige in deinen Kampfjet und hebe von der %2USS Freedom%1 ab. &lt;br/&gt;2. Patrouilliere den %4Luftraum%1 und eliminiere feindliche Flugzeuge. &lt;br/&gt;3. Kehre zur %2USS Freedom%1 zurück und lande.</German>
          <Czech>1. Vyberte si vybavení, nasedněte do svého proudového stíhacího letounu a vzlétněte z lodě %2USS Freedom%1. &lt;br/&gt;2. Hlídkujte ve %4vzdušném prostoru%1 a zneškodněte nepřátelské letecké jednotky. &lt;br/&gt;3. Vraťte se na %2USS Freedom%1 a přistaňte.</Czech>
          <English>1. Gear up, board your fighter jet and take off from %2USS Freedom%1. &lt;br/&gt;2. Patrol the %4airspace%1 and eliminate enemy air assets. &lt;br/&gt;3. Return to %2USS Freedom%1 and land.</English>
          <Portuguese>1. Prepare-se, embarque no avião de combate e decole do %2USS Freedom%1. &lt;br/&gt;2. Patrulhe o %4espaço aéreo%1 e elimine as aeronaves inimigas. &lt;br/&gt;3. Retorne para o %2USS Freedom% 1 e pouse.</Portuguese>
          <Korean>1. 기어를 올리고 전투기에 탑승하여 %2USS Freedom%1로부터 떨어져라. &lt;br/&gt;2. %4영공%1을 순찰하고 적의 항공자산을 제거하라. &lt;br/&gt;3. %2USS Freedom%1으로 돌아와 착륙하라.</Korean>
          <Chinesesimp>1. 整装, 然后搭乘你的战斗机从%2美国海军自由号%1上起飞. &lt;br/&gt;2. 前往该%4空域%1进行巡逻并歼灭掉敌军的空中单位. &lt;br/&gt;3. 返回%2美国海军自由号%1上降落.</Chinesesimp>
          <Japanese>1.装備を整え、乗機となるジェット戦闘機に乗り込み、%2USS「フリーダム」%1より発艦せよ。&lt;br/&gt;2.%4空域%1内の哨戒を行い、敵性航空戦力を撃滅せよ。&lt;br/&gt;3.%2USS「フリーダム」%1へ帰還し着艦せよ。</Japanese>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="str_a3_showcase_jets_bis_tsktakeoff_wp">
          <Original>TAKE OFF</Original>
          <Chinese>起飛</Chinese>
          <French>DÉCOLLER</French>
          <Spanish>DESPEGUE</Spanish>
          <Italian>DECOLLA</Italian>
          <Polish>WYSTARTUJ</Polish>
          <Russian>ВЗЛЕТ</Russian>
          <German>STARTEN</German>
          <Czech>VZLÉTNĚTE</Czech>
          <English>TAKE OFF</English>
          <Portuguese>DECOLAR</Portuguese>
          <Korean>이륙</Korean>
          <Chinesesimp>起飞</Chinesesimp>
          <Japanese>発艦</Japanese>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="str_a3_showcase_jets_bis_tsktakeoff_title">
          <Original>Take Off</Original>
          <Chinese>起飛</Chinese>
          <French>Décoller</French>
          <Spanish>Despega</Spanish>
          <Italian>Decolla</Italian>
          <Polish>Wystartuj</Polish>
          <Russian>Взлет</Russian>
          <German>Starten</German>
          <Czech>Vzlétněte</Czech>
          <English>Take Off</English>
          <Portuguese>Decolar</Portuguese>
          <Korean>이륙</Korean>
          <Chinesesimp>起飞</Chinesesimp>
          <Japanese>発艦</Japanese>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="str_a3_showcase_jets_bis_tsktakeoff_desc">
          <Original>Take off from %2USS Freedom%1.</Original>
          <Chinese>從%2美國海軍自由號%1上起飛.</Chinese>
          <French>Décollez de l'%2USS Freedom%1.</French>
          <Spanish>Despega del %2USS Freedom%1.</Spanish>
          <Italian>Decolla dall'%2USS Freedom%1.</Italian>
          <Polish>Wystartuj z pokładu %2USS Freedom%1.</Polish>
          <Russian>Взлетите с %2USS Freedom%1.</Russian>
          <German>Starte von der %2USS Freedom%1</German>
          <Czech>Vzlétněte z %2USS Freedom%1.</Czech>
          <English>Take off from %2USS Freedom%1.</English>
          <Portuguese>Decolagem do %2USS Freedom%1.</Portuguese>
          <Korean>%2USS Freedom%1에서 이륙하라.</Korean>
          <Chinesesimp>从%2美国海军自由号%1上起飞.</Chinesesimp>
          <Japanese>%2USS「フリーダム」%1より発艦せよ。</Japanese>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="str_a3_showcase_jets_bis_tskrepair_wp">
          <Original>REPAIR</Original>
          <Chinese>維修</Chinese>
          <French>RÉPARER</French>
          <Spanish>REPARACIONES</Spanish>
          <Italian>RIPARA</Italian>
          <Polish>NAPRAW</Polish>
          <Russian>РЕМОНТ</Russian>
          <German>REPARIEREN</German>
          <Czech>OPRAVTE SE</Czech>
          <English>REPAIR</English>
          <Portuguese>REPARAR</Portuguese>
          <Korean>정비</Korean>
          <Chinesesimp>维修</Chinesesimp>
          <Japanese>修理</Japanese>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="str_a3_showcase_jets_bis_tskrepair_title">
          <Original>(Optional) Repair</Original>
          <Chinese>維修 (可選)</Chinese>
          <French>(Optionnel) Réparer</French>
          <Spanish>(Opcional) Repara</Spanish>
          <Italian>Ripara (opzionale)</Italian>
          <Polish>(Opcjonalne) Napraw</Polish>
          <Russian>(Необязательно) Ремонт</Russian>
          <German>(Optional) Reparieren</German>
          <Czech>(Volitelné) Proveďte opravu</Czech>
          <English>(Optional) Repair</English>
          <Portuguese>(Opcional) Reparar</Portuguese>
          <Korean>(옵션) 정비</Korean>
          <Chinesesimp>维修 (可选)</Chinesesimp>
          <Japanese>（任意）修理</Japanese>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="str_a3_showcase_jets_bis_tskrepair_desc">
          <Original>Land at %2Altis International Airport%1 for %3emergency repairs%1.</Original>
          <Chinese>如果需要%3緊急維修%1的話, 你可以降落在%2Altis國際機場%1.</Chinese>
          <French>Atterrissez à l'%2aéroport international d'Altis%1 pour effectuer des %3réparations d'urgence%1.</French>
          <Spanish>Aterriza en el %2Aeropuerto Internacional de Altis%1 para hacer %3reparaciones de emergencia%1.</Spanish>
          <Italian>Atterra presso l'%2Aeroporto internazionale di Altis%1 per effettuare delle %3riparazioni d'emergenza%1.</Italian>
          <Polish>Wyląduj w %2Międzynarodowym porcie lotniczym Altis%1, aby przeprowadzić %3awaryjną naprawę%1.</Polish>
          <Russian>Приземлитесь в %2Международном аэропорту Алтиса%1 для %3аварийного ремонта%1.</Russian>
          <German>Lande auf dem %2Altis International Airport%1 für %3Notfallreparaturen%1.</German>
          <Czech>Přistaňte na %2Altiském mezinárodním letišti%1 a proveďte %3nouzovou opravu%1.</Czech>
          <English>Land at %2Altis International Airport%1 for %3emergency repairs%1.</English>
          <Portuguese>Pouse no %2Aeroporto Internacional de Altis%1 para executar os %3reparos de emergência%1.</Portuguese>
          <Korean>%2알티스 국제 공항%1에 착륙하여 %3응급 정비%1를 받기.</Korean>
          <Chinesesimp>如果需要%3紧急维修%1的话, 你可以降落在%2Altis国际机场%1.</Chinesesimp>
          <Japanese>%3緊急修理%1のため%2アルティス国際空港%1に着陸せよ。</Japanese>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="str_a3_showcase_jets_bis_tskrearm_wp">
          <Original>REARM</Original>
          <Chinese>彈藥補給</Chinese>
          <French>RÉARMER</French>
          <Spanish>REARME</Spanish>
          <Italian>RIARMA</Italian>
          <Polish>ZMIEŃ UZBROJENIE</Polish>
          <Russian>ПЕРЕВООРУЖЕНИЕ</Russian>
          <German>AUFRÜSTEN</German>
          <Czech>PŘEZBROJTE</Czech>
          <English>REARM</English>
          <Portuguese>REARMAR</Portuguese>
          <Korean>재무장</Korean>
          <Chinesesimp>弹药补给</Chinesesimp>
          <Japanese>弾薬補給</Japanese>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="str_a3_showcase_jets_bis_tskrearm_title">
          <Original>(Optional) Rearm</Original>
          <Chinese>彈藥補給 (可選)</Chinese>
          <French>(Optionnel) Réarmer</French>
          <Spanish>(Opcional) Reármate</Spanish>
          <Italian>Riarma (opzionale)</Italian>
          <Polish>(Opcjonalne) Zmień uzbrojenie</Polish>
          <Russian>(Необязательно) Перевооружение</Russian>
          <German>(Optional) Aufrüsten</German>
          <Czech>(Volitelné) Přezbrojte</Czech>
          <English>(Optional) Rearm</English>
          <Portuguese>(Opcional) Rearmar</Portuguese>
          <Korean>(옵션) 재무장</Korean>
          <Chinesesimp>弹药补给 (可选)</Chinesesimp>
          <Japanese>（任意）弾薬補給</Japanese>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="str_a3_showcase_jets_bis_tskrearm_desc">
          <Original>Land at %2Altis International Airport%1 for %3rearm%1.</Original>
          <Chinese>如果需要%3彈藥補給%1的話, 你可以降落在%2Altis國際機場%1.</Chinese>
          <French>Atterrissez à l'%2aéroport international d'Altis%1 pour %3réarmer%1.</French>
          <Spanish>Aterriza en el %2Aeropuerto Internacional de Altis%1 para %3rearmarte%1.</Spanish>
          <Italian>Atterra presso l'%2Aeroporto internazionale di Altis%1 per effettuare il %3riarmo%1.</Italian>
          <Polish>Wyląduj w %2Międzynarodowym porcie lotniczym Altis%1, aby %3zmienić uzbrojenie%1.</Polish>
          <Russian>Приземлитесь в %2Международном аэропорту Алтиса%1 для %3перевооружения%1.</Russian>
          <German>Lande auf dem %2Altis International Airport%1 um dich %3aufzurüsten%1.</German>
          <Czech>Přistaňte na %2Altiském mezinárodním letišti%1 a %3přezbrojte%1.</Czech>
          <English>Land at %2Altis International Airport%1 for %3rearm%1.</English>
          <Portuguese>Pouse no %2Aeroporto Internacional de Altis%1 para %3rearmar%1.</Portuguese>
          <Korean>%2알티스 국제공항%1에 착륙하여 %3재무장%1하기.</Korean>
          <Chinesesimp>如果需要%3弹药补给%1的话, 你可以降落在%2Altis国际机场%1.</Chinesesimp>
          <Japanese>%3弾薬補給%1のため%2アルティス国際空港%1に着陸せよ。</Japanese>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="str_a3_showcase_jets_bis_tskland_wp">
          <Original>LAND</Original>
          <Chinese>降落</Chinese>
          <French>APPONTER</French>
          <Spanish>ATERRIZAJE</Spanish>
          <Italian>ATTERRA</Italian>
          <Polish>WYLĄDUJ</Polish>
          <Russian>ПРИЗЕМЛЕНИЕ</Russian>
          <German>LANDEN</German>
          <Czech>PŘISTAŇTE</Czech>
          <English>LAND</English>
          <Portuguese>POUSAR</Portuguese>
          <Korean>착륙</Korean>
          <Chinesesimp>降落</Chinesesimp>
          <Japanese>着艦</Japanese>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="str_a3_showcase_jets_bis_tskland_title">
          <Original>Land</Original>
          <Chinese>降落</Chinese>
          <French>Apponter</French>
          <Spanish>Aterriza</Spanish>
          <Italian>Atterra</Italian>
          <Polish>Wyląduj</Polish>
          <Russian>Приземление</Russian>
          <German>Landen</German>
          <Czech>Přistaňte</Czech>
          <English>Land</English>
          <Portuguese>Pousar</Portuguese>
          <Korean>착륙</Korean>
          <Chinesesimp>降落</Chinesesimp>
          <Japanese>着艦</Japanese>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="str_a3_showcase_jets_bis_tskland_desc">
          <Original>Return to %2USS Freedom%1 and land.</Original>
          <Chinese>返回%2美國海軍自由號%1上降落.</Chinese>
          <French>Retournez sur l'%2USS Freedom%1 et appontez.</French>
          <Spanish>Vuelve al %2USS Freedom%1 y aterriza.</Spanish>
          <Italian>Fai ritorno all'%2USS Freedom%1 e atterra.</Italian>
          <Polish>Wróć i wyląduj na %2USS Freedom%1.</Polish>
          <Russian>Вернитесь на %2USS Freedom%1 и совершите посадку.</Russian>
          <German>Kehre zur %2USS Freedom%1 zurück und lande.</German>
          <Czech>Vraťte se na %2USS Freedom%1 a přistaňte.</Czech>
          <English>Return to %2USS Freedom%1 and land.</English>
          <Portuguese>Retorne para o %2USS Freedom%1 e pouse.</Portuguese>
          <Korean>%2USS Freedom%1으로 돌아와 착륙하기.</Korean>
          <Chinesesimp>返回%2美国海军自由号%1上降落.</Chinesesimp>
          <Japanese>%2USS「フリーダム」%1へ帰還し着艦せよ。</Japanese>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="str_a3_showcase_jets_bis_tsklandapproach_wp">
          <Original>APPROACH</Original>
          <Chinese>進場</Chinese>
          <French>EFFECTUER APPROCHE</French>
          <Spanish>APROXIMACIÓN</Spanish>
          <Italian>AVVICINATI</Italian>
          <Polish>PODEJDŹ</Polish>
          <Russian>ЗАХОД</Russian>
          <German>ANFLUG</German>
          <Czech>PŘIBLIŽTE SE</Czech>
          <English>APPROACH</English>
          <Portuguese>ABORDAGEM</Portuguese>
          <Korean>접근</Korean>
          <Chinesesimp>进场</Chinesesimp>
          <Japanese>アプローチ</Japanese>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="str_a3_showcase_jets_bis_tskjet_wp">
          <Original>GET IN</Original>
          <Chinese>搭乘</Chinese>
          <French>EMBARQUER</French>
          <Spanish>MONTA</Spanish>
          <Italian>SALI A BORDO</Italian>
          <Polish>WSIĄDŹ</Polish>
          <Russian>ЗАЙТИ</Russian>
          <German>EINSTEIGEN</German>
          <Czech>NASTUPTE</Czech>
          <English>GET IN</English>
          <Portuguese>ENTRAR</Portuguese>
          <Korean>탑승</Korean>
          <Chinesesimp>搭乘</Chinesesimp>
          <Japanese>乗り込め</Japanese>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="str_a3_showcase_jets_bis_tskjet_title">
          <Original>Get In</Original>
          <Chinese>搭乘</Chinese>
          <French>Embarquer</French>
          <Spanish>Monta</Spanish>
          <Italian>Sali a bordo</Italian>
          <Polish>Wsiądź</Polish>
          <Russian>Взять управление</Russian>
          <German>Einsteigen</German>
          <Czech>Nastupte</Czech>
          <English>Get In</English>
          <Portuguese>Entrar</Portuguese>
          <Korean>탑승</Korean>
          <Chinesesimp>搭乘</Chinesesimp>
          <Japanese>乗り込め</Japanese>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="str_a3_showcase_jets_bis_tskjet_desc">
          <Original>Board your fighter jet.</Original>
          <Chinese>搭乘你的戰鬥機.</Chinese>
          <French>Montez à bord de votre chasseur.</French>
          <Spanish>Sube a bordo de tu caza.</Spanish>
          <Italian>Sali a bordo del tuo jet da caccia.</Italian>
          <Polish>Wsiądź do kokpitu myśliwca odrzutowego.</Polish>
          <Russian>Сядьте в кабину истребителя.</Russian>
          <German>Steige in deinen Kampfjet.</German>
          <Czech>Nastupte do stíhacího letounu.</Czech>
          <English>Board your fighter jet.</English>
          <Portuguese>Entre no seu avião de combate.</Portuguese>
          <Korean>전투기 제트에 탑승하라.</Korean>
          <Chinesesimp>搭乘你的战斗机.</Chinesesimp>
          <Japanese>ジェット戦闘機に搭乗せよ。</Japanese>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="str_a3_showcase_jets_bis_tskequipment_wp">
          <Original>EQUIP</Original>
          <Chinese>整裝</Chinese>
          <French>S'ÉQUIPER</French>
          <Spanish>EQUIPO</Spanish>
          <Italian>EQUIPAGGIA</Italian>
          <Polish>ZAŁÓŻ</Polish>
          <Russian>СНАРЯДИТЬ</Russian>
          <German>AUSRÜSTEN</German>
          <Czech>VYBAVTE SE</Czech>
          <English>EQUIP</English>
          <Portuguese>EQUIPAR</Portuguese>
          <Korean>장착</Korean>
          <Chinesesimp>整装</Chinesesimp>
          <Japanese>装備</Japanese>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="str_a3_showcase_jets_bis_tskequipment_title">
          <Original>Equipment</Original>
          <Chinese>整裝</Chinese>
          <French>S'équiper</French>
          <Spanish>Equipo</Spanish>
          <Italian>Equipaggiamento</Italian>
          <Polish>Wyposażenie</Polish>
          <Russian>Снаряжение</Russian>
          <German>Ausrüsten</German>
          <Czech>Vybavení</Czech>
          <English>Equipment</English>
          <Portuguese>Equipamento</Portuguese>
          <Korean>장비</Korean>
          <Chinesesimp>整装</Chinesesimp>
          <Japanese>装備</Japanese>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="str_a3_showcase_jets_bis_tskequipment_desc">
          <Original>Equip your helmet.</Original>
          <Chinese>戴上你的頭盔.</Chinese>
          <French>Mettez votre casque.</French>
          <Spanish>Equípate el casco.</Spanish>
          <Italian>Indossa il casco.</Italian>
          <Polish>Załóż kask.</Polish>
          <Russian>Наденьте шлем.</Russian>
          <German>Ziehe deinen Helm an.</German>
          <Czech>Nasaďte si helmu.</Czech>
          <English>Equip your helmet.</English>
          <Portuguese>Equipe o seu capacete.</Portuguese>
          <Korean>헬멧을 착용.</Korean>
          <Chinesesimp>戴上你的头盔.</Chinesesimp>
          <Japanese>ヘルメットを装備せよ。</Japanese>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="str_a3_showcase_jets_bis_tskcas_wp">
          <Original>CAS</Original>
          <Chinese>密接空中支援</Chinese>
          <French>APPUI AÉRIEN</French>
          <Spanish>APOYO AÉREO DE COMBATE</Spanish>
          <Italian>Supporto aereo da combattimento</Italian>
          <Polish>BOJOWE WSPARCIE LOT.</Polish>
          <Russian>Авиационная поддержка</Russian>
          <German>LUFTUNTERSTÜTZUNG</German>
          <Czech>VZDUŠNÁ PODPORA</Czech>
          <English>CAS</English>
          <Portuguese>Apoio aéreo aproximado (CAS)</Portuguese>
          <Korean>CAS</Korean>
          <Chinesesimp>密接空中支援</Chinesesimp>
          <Japanese>CAS</Japanese>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="str_a3_showcase_jets_bis_tskcas_title">
          <Original>CAS</Original>
          <Chinese>密接空中支援</Chinese>
          <French>Appui aérien</French>
          <Spanish>Apoyo aéreo de combate</Spanish>
          <Italian>Supporto aereo da combattimento</Italian>
          <Polish>BOJOWE WSPARCIE LOT.</Polish>
          <Russian>Авиационная поддержка</Russian>
          <German>Luftunterstützung</German>
          <Czech>Vzdušná podpora</Czech>
          <English>CAS</English>
          <Portuguese>Apoio aéreo aproximado (CAS)</Portuguese>
          <Korean>CAS</Korean>
          <Chinesesimp>密接空中支援</Chinesesimp>
          <Japanese>CAS</Japanese>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="str_a3_showcase_jets_bis_tskcas_desc">
          <Original>Provide Combat Air Support for ground units to assist the attack.</Original>
          <Chinese>為地面的友軍部隊提供密接空中支援.</Chinese>
          <French>Apportez un appui aérien aux unités terrestres en cours d'attaque.</French>
          <Spanish>Ofrece apoyo aéreo de combate a las unidades terrestres para asistirlas durante el ataque.</Spanish>
          <Italian>Fornisci supporto aereo da combattimento alle unità di terra in modo da supportare l'attacco.</Italian>
          <Polish>Udziel bojowego wsparcia lotniczego jednostkom naziemnym podczas uderzenia.</Polish>
          <Russian>Обеспечьте авиационную поддержу  наземных частей и помогите им в проведении атаки.</Russian>
          <German>Liefere Luftunterstützung für die Bodeneinheiten, um beim Angriff zu helfen.</German>
          <Czech>Poskytněte vzdušnou podporu pro útočící pozemní jednotky.</Czech>
          <English>Provide Combat Air Support for ground units to assist the attack.</English>
          <Portuguese>Forneça apoio aéreo de combate às unidades terrestres para auxiliar no ataque.</Portuguese>
          <Korean>지상 병력에게 전투 항공 지원을 제공하여 공격을 지원하기.</Korean>
          <Chinesesimp>为地面的友军部队提供密接空中支援.</Chinesesimp>
          <Japanese>地上部隊の近接航空支援 (CAS) を行い、進軍を支援せよ。</Japanese>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="str_a3_showcase_jets_bis_tskcap_wp">
          <Original>CAP</Original>
          <Chinese>戰鬥空中巡邏</Chinese>
          <French>PATROUILLE AÉRIENNE</French>
          <Spanish>PATRULLA AÉREA DE COMBATE</Spanish>
          <Italian>Pattugliamento aereo da combattimento</Italian>
          <Polish>BOJOWY PATROL POW.</Polish>
          <Russian>Боевое патрулирование</Russian>
          <German>KAMPFPATROUILLE</German>
          <Czech>BOJOVÁ HLÍDKA</Czech>
          <English>CAP</English>
          <Portuguese>Patrulha aérea</Portuguese>
          <Korean>CAP</Korean>
          <Chinesesimp>战斗空中巡逻</Chinesesimp>
          <Japanese>CAP</Japanese>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="str_a3_showcase_jets_bis_tskcap_title">
          <Original>CAP</Original>
          <Chinese>戰鬥空中巡邏</Chinese>
          <French>Patrouille aérienne</French>
          <Spanish>Patrulla aérea de combate</Spanish>
          <Italian>Pattugliamento aereo da combattimento</Italian>
          <Polish>BOJOWY PATROL POW.</Polish>
          <Russian>Боевое патрулирование</Russian>
          <German>Kampfpatrouille</German>
          <Czech>Bojová hlídka</Czech>
          <English>CAP</English>
          <Portuguese>Patrulha aérea</Portuguese>
          <Korean>CAP</Korean>
          <Chinesesimp>战斗空中巡逻</Chinesesimp>
          <Japanese>CAP</Japanese>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="str_a3_showcase_jets_bis_tskcap_desc">
          <Original>Patrol the %2airspace%1 and eliminate enemy air assets.</Original>
          <Chinese>去巡邏這片%2空域%1並殲滅掉敵軍的空中單位.</Chinese>
          <French>Patrouillez l'%2espace aérien%1 et éliminez les unités aériennes ennemies.</French>
          <Spanish>Patrulla el %2espacio aéreo%1 y elimina las unidades aéreas enemigas.</Spanish>
          <Italian>Perlustra lo %2spazio aereo%1 ed elimina le risorse aeree nemiche.</Italian>
          <Polish>Patroluj %2przestrzeń powietrzną%1 i wyeliminuj siły powietrzne przeciwnika.</Polish>
          <Russian>Патрулируйте %2воздушное пространство%1 и уничтожьте вражеский воздушный флот.</Russian>
          <German>Patrouilliere den %2Luftraum%1 und eliminiere feindliche Flugzeuge.</German>
          <Czech>Hlídkujte ve %4vzdušném prostoru%1 a zneškodněte nepřátelské letecké jednotky.</Czech>
          <English>Patrol the %2airspace%1 and eliminate enemy air assets.</English>
          <Portuguese>Patrulhe o %2espaço aéreo%1 e elimine as aeronaves inimigas.</Portuguese>
          <Korean>%2영공%1을 순찰하고 적의 항공자산을 제거하기.</Korean>
          <Chinesesimp>去巡逻这片%2空域%1并歼灭掉敌军的空中单位.</Chinesesimp>
          <Japanese>%2空域%1内の哨戒を行い、敵性航空戦力を撃滅せよ。</Japanese>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="str_a3_showcase_jets_01_intro_pilot_0">
          <Original>Consider it done, sir.</Original>
          <Chinese>交給我吧, 長官.</Chinese>
          <French>C'est comme si c'était fait, chef.</French>
          <Spanish>Eso está hecho, señor.</Spanish>
          <Italian>Sarà fatto.</Italian>
          <Polish>Robi się.</Polish>
          <Russian>Будет сделано, сэр.</Russian>
          <German>So gut wie erledigt, Sir.</German>
          <Czech>Rozumím, pane.</Czech>
          <English>Consider it done, sir.</English>
          <Portuguese>Considere o serviço feito, senhor.</Portuguese>
          <Korean>완료했습니다, 대위님.</Korean>
          <Chinesesimp>交给我吧, 长官.</Chinesesimp>
          <Japanese>了解です、サー。</Japanese>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="str_a3_showcase_jets_01_intro_tower_0">
          <Original>Captain - QRA update.</Original>
          <Chinese>上校 - 緊急任務報告.</Chinese>
          <French>Capitaine, alerte de veille.</French>
          <Spanish>Capitán, actualización de alerta de reacción rápida.</Spanish>
          <Italian>Capitano, aggiornamento su reazione rapida su allarme.</Italian>
          <Polish>Kapitanie, podwyższona gotowość bojowa.</Polish>
          <Russian>Капитан, докладываю о немедленной боевой готовности.</Russian>
          <German>Captain – Update zur Schnellstartbereitschaft.</German>
          <Czech>Kapitáne – informace k situaci.</Czech>
          <English>Captain - QRA update.</English>
          <Portuguese>Capitão, alerta de reação rápida atualizado.</Portuguese>
          <Korean>대위 - QRA(긴급대응 비상대기)를 업데이트하라.</Korean>
          <Chinesesimp>上校 - 紧急任务报告.</Chinesesimp>
          <Japanese>大佐 - QRA アップデート。</Japanese>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="str_a3_showcase_jets_01_intro_tower_1">
          <Original>Early-warning radars have a pair of unknown contacts, one hundred klicks north, approaching fast.</Original>
          <Chinese>早期預警雷達搜索到兩個不明目標, 在北面100公里遠的地方, 快速接近中.</Chinese>
          <French>Des radars d'alerte précoce ont deux contacts non identifiés, à 100 klicks au nord.</French>
          <Spanish>Los radares de alerta rápida tienen a un par de contactos desconocidos, a cien kilómetros al norte. Se aproximan con rapidez.</Spanish>
          <Italian>I radar di avvistamento a distanza hanno rilevato un paio di contatti sconosciuti. Uno si trova a 100 chilometri a nord e si sta avvicinando rapidamente.</Italian>
          <Polish>Radary wczesnego ostrzegania wykryły dwie nieznane jednostki 100 km stąd. Zbliżają się szybko.</Polish>
          <Russian>Радары раннего предупреждения заметили несколько неопознанных объектов в ста километрах к северу. Приближаются с большой скоростью.</Russian>
          <German>Der Frühwarnradar hat hundert Klicks nördlich zwei unbekannte Kontakte geortet. Sie nähern sich schnell.</German>
          <Czech>Radar včasné výstrahy zachytil dvojici neznámých kontaktů sto kilometrů na sever. Rychle se přibližují.</Czech>
          <English>Early-warning radars have a pair of unknown contacts, one hundred klicks north, approaching fast.</English>
          <Portuguese>Os radares de aviso prévio mostram uns dois contatos desconhecidos, cem klicks ao norte e aproximando-se rapidamente.</Portuguese>
          <Korean>레이더의 조기 경보에 따르면 2개의 알 수 없는 병력이 출현했다. 북쪽으로 100킬로미터 지점으로 빠르게 접근 중이다.</Korean>
          <Chinesesimp>早期预警雷达搜索到两个不明目标, 在北面100公里远的地方, 快速接近中.</Chinesesimp>
          <Japanese>早期警戒レーダーより不明のレーダー反応が 1 組、北へ 100km、高速で近づく。</Japanese>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="str_a3_showcase_jets_01_intro_tower_2">
          <Original>Possible CSAT strike on Altis International. Get up there and interdict - we can't let them target the airport; our entire operation would be at risk.</Original>
          <Chinese>應該是廣協同盟的戰機飛在Altis國際機場上. 請前往那邊並攔截他們 - 我們不能讓他們攻擊機場; 要不然我們的整場行動就會陷入危機.</Chinese>
          <French>Attaque possible du CSAT sur l'aéroport d'Altis. Passez en vol et intervenez. On doit les empêcher de prendre l'aéroport pour cible. Toute l'opération serait compromise.</French>
          <Spanish>Posible ataque del CSAT en el Internacional de Altis. Sube a los cielos y rechaza el ataque. Si les dejamos que se hagan con el aeropuerto, ¡toda nuestra operación estará en peligro!</Spanish>
          <Italian>Possibile attacco CSAT all'aeroporto internazionale di Altis. Dirigiti verso la zona e bloccali. Non possiamo lasciare che prendano di mira l'aeroporto, la nostra operazione sarebbe completamente a rischio.</Italian>
          <Polish>Możliwy atak CSAT na port lotniczy Altis. Skieruj się na miejsce i interweniuj. Zniszczenie lotniska zagraża całej operacji.</Polish>
          <Russian>Возможен удар CSAT по Международному аэропорту Алтиса. Отправляйтесь туда и перехватите их. Мы не можем допустить атаки на аэропорт, иначе вся наша операция будет под угрозой.</Russian>
          <German>Möglicher CSAT-Angriff auf Altis International. Starten Sie und halten Sie sie auf. Wir dürfen den Flughafen nicht verlieren – das würde die gesamte Operation gefährden.</German>
          <Czech>Možný útok CSAT na Altiské mezinárodní letiště. Dostaňte se tam a zabraňte jim v útoku – pokud vyřadí letiště, ohrozí to celou naši operaci.</Czech>
          <English>Possible CSAT strike on Altis International. Get up there and interdict - we can't let them target the airport; our entire operation would be at risk.</English>
          <Portuguese>Possível ataque da CSAT no Aeroporto Internacional de Altis. Vai até lá e interdita o movimento inimigo. A gente não pode deixar eles atingirem o aeroporto — toda a nossa operação ficaria em risco.</Portuguese>
          <Korean>CSAT군이 알티스 인터내서널 공항을 타격할 수 있다. 그곳에서 타격을 막아라. 놈들이 공항을 표적하도록 놔두면 안된다. 우리 작전이 송두리째 와해될 수 있다. </Korean>
          <Chinesesimp>应该是广协同盟的战机飞在Altis国际机场上. 请前往那边并拦截他们 - 我们不能让他们攻击机场; 要不然我们的整场行动就会陷入危机.</Chinesesimp>
          <Japanese>アルティス国際空港で CSAT の攻撃の可能性あり。急行して迎撃せよ - 連中に空港を潰させるな。そうなれば作戦そのものが破綻しかねない。</Japanese>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="str_a3_showcase_jets_05_preflight_pilot_0">
          <Original>Hornet 1, Two is spooled up and ready for take-off.</Original>
          <Chinese>大黃蜂1, 2機已經啟動並準備起飛.</Chinese>
          <French>Hornet 1, Hornet 2 allumé et paré au décollage.</French>
          <Spanish>Hornet 1, Dos está listo para el despegue.</Spanish>
          <Italian>Hornet 1, Due è pronto per il decollo.</Italian>
          <Polish>Hornet 1, dwójka jest gotowa do startu.</Polish>
          <Russian>Hornet 1, все системы в норме, второй готов ко взлету.</Russian>
          <German>Hornet 1, Zwei ist startbereit.</German>
          <Czech>Hornet-1, dvojka je v pořádku a připravena vzlétnout.</Czech>
          <English>Hornet 1, Two is spooled up and ready for take-off.</English>
          <Portuguese>Vespa 1, o 2 com as asas prontas pra decolagem.</Portuguese>
          <Korean>호넷 1, 두개 시스템이 정상적으로 이륙 준비 완료.</Korean>
          <Chinesesimp>大黄蜂1, 2机已经启动并准备起飞.</Chinesesimp>
          <Japanese>ホーネット 1、こちら 2。エンジン始動、離陸可能だ。</Japanese>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="str_a3_showcase_jets_05_preflight_tower_0">
          <Original>Hornet 1, Hornet 2, you're cleared for take-off.</Original>
          <Chinese>大黃蜂1, 大黃蜂2, 你們可以起飛了.</Chinese>
          <French>Hornet 1, Hornet 2, autorisés au décollage.</French>
          <Spanish>Hornet 1, Hornet 2, podéis despegar.</Spanish>
          <Italian>Hornet 1, Hornet 2, avete l'autorizzazione per il decollo.</Italian>
          <Polish>Hornet 1, Hornet 2, macie pozwolenie na start.</Polish>
          <Russian>Hornet 1, Hornet 2, взлет разрешаю.</Russian>
          <German>Hornet 1, Hornet 2, Starterlaubnis erteilt.</German>
          <Czech>Hornet-1, Hornet-2, můžete vzlétnout.</Czech>
          <English>Hornet 1, Hornet 2, you're cleared for take-off.</English>
          <Portuguese>Vespa 1, Vespa 2, tá autorizado pra decolar.</Portuguese>
          <Korean>호넷 1, 호넷 2. 출발해도 좋다.</Korean>
          <Chinesesimp>大黄蜂1, 大黄蜂2, 你们可以起飞了.</Chinesesimp>
          <Japanese>ホーネット 1、ホーネット 2、離陸を許可する。</Japanese>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="str_a3_showcase_jets_05_preflight_wingman_0">
          <Original>Hornet 2, you set?</Original>
          <Chinese>大黃蜂2, 你好了嗎?</Chinese>
          <French>Hornet 2, vous êtes paré ?</French>
          <Spanish>Hornet 2, ¿todo listo?</Spanish>
          <Italian>Hornet 2, sei pronto?</Italian>
          <Polish>Hornet 2, gotowy?</Polish>
          <Russian>Hornet 2, вы готовы?</Russian>
          <German>Hornet 2, sind Sie bereit?</German>
          <Czech>Hornet-2, připraveni?</Czech>
          <English>Hornet 2, you set?</English>
          <Portuguese>Vespa 2, tudo certo?</Portuguese>
          <Korean>호넷 2, 준비됐나?</Korean>
          <Chinesesimp>大黄蜂2, 你好了吗?</Chinesesimp>
          <Japanese>ホーネット 2、準備はいいか？</Japanese>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="str_a3_showcase_jets_05_preflight_wingman_1">
          <Original>Alright. Let's do this.</Original>
          <Chinese>好的. 讓我們上吧.</Chinese>
          <French>Allez, on y va.</French>
          <Spanish>Muy bien, vamos.</Spanish>
          <Italian>Okay. Diamoci da fare.</Italian>
          <Polish>Bierzmy się do roboty.</Polish>
          <Russian>Хорошо. Давай сделаем это.</Russian>
          <German>Alles klar, dann legen wir mal los.</German>
          <Czech>Dobrá. Pojďme na to.</Czech>
          <English>Alright. Let's do this.</English>
          <Portuguese>Ok. Vamos nessa.</Portuguese>
          <Korean>좋았어. 한번 해보자구..</Korean>
          <Chinesesimp>好的. 让我们上吧.</Chinesesimp>
          <Japanese>よし。始めよう。</Japanese>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="str_a3_showcase_jets_05_preflight_wingman_2">
          <Original>Freeway, this is Hornet flight. Ready on the safe-shots. Over.</Original>
          <Chinese>自由路, 這裡是大黃蜂中隊. 已經準備好進行彈射. 完畢.</Chinese>
          <French>Freeway, ici escadron Hornet. Sur piste d'envol pour catapultage. À vous.</French>
          <Spanish>Freeway, aquí Hornet. Listo para disparar. Cambio.</Spanish>
          <Italian>Freeway, qui volo Hornet. Pronto sulla linea di lancio. Passo.</Italian>
          <Polish>Freeway, tu lot Hornet. Jestem na długiej. Odbiór.</Polish>
          <Russian>Freeway, это Hornet. Готов ко взлету. Прием.</Russian>
          <German>Freeway, hier ist Hornet flight. Bereit an der Safe-Shot-Line. Ende.</German>
          <Czech>Freeway, tady letka Hornet. Připraveno v pozici bezpečného vystřelení. Přepínám.</Czech>
          <English>Freeway, this is Hornet flight. Ready on the safe-shots. Over.</English>
          <Portuguese>Expressa, aqui é o Vespa. Pronto e na linha de segurança. Câmbio.</Portuguese>
          <Korean>프리웨이, 이 비행은 호넷 비행이다. 안전 발사 위치로 준비하라. 이상.</Korean>
          <Chinesesimp>自由路, 这里是大黄蜂中队. 已经准备好进行弹射. 完毕.</Chinesesimp>
          <Japanese>フリーウェイ、こちらホーネット隊。セーフショット上で準備完了。オーバー。</Japanese>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="str_a3_showcase_jets_10_takeoff_pilot_0">
          <Original>Hornet 2's up. Joining on lead.</Original>
          <Chinese>大黃蜂2已經起飛. 正在加入長機的編隊中.</Chinese>
          <French>Hornet 2 en vol. Je vous rejoins.</French>
          <Spanish>Hornet 2 listo. Uniéndose.</Spanish>
          <Italian>Hornet 2 è in volo. Ricongiungimento con il leader.</Italian>
          <Polish>Hornet 2 w powietrzu. Dołączam.</Polish>
          <Russian>Hornet 2 взлетел. Следую за вами.</Russian>
          <German>Hornet 2 in der Luft. Bin gleich bei euch.</German>
          <Czech>Hornet-2 je na řadě. Přidávám se k vedení.</Czech>
          <English>Hornet 2's up. Joining on lead.</English>
          <Portuguese>Vespa 2 acima. Vou me juntar à dianteira.</Portuguese>
          <Korean>호넷 2가 맡겠다. 선두 대열에 합류한다.</Korean>
          <Chinesesimp>大黄蜂2已经起飞. 正在加入长机的编队中.</Chinesesimp>
          <Japanese>ホーネット 2、問題なし。先頭に加わる。</Japanese>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="str_a3_showcase_jets_10_takeoff_wingman_0">
          <Original>Hornet 1 copies. Climbing to 1500. Heading 050. Speed 720. Burner to intercept.</Original>
          <Chinese>大黃蜂1收到. 爬升至1500. 航向050. 空速720. 使用後燃器前往攔截.</Chinese>
          <French>Hornet 1, reçu. Je monte à 1 500. Cap 050. Vitesse 720. Postcombustion pour interception.</French>
          <Spanish>Hornet 1, recibido. Subo a 1500. Me dirijo hacia 050. Velocidad: 720. Me dispongo a interceptarlo.</Spanish>
          <Italian>Hornet 1, ricevuto. In salita a 1500. Direzione 050. Velocità 720. Attivazione del postbruciatore per intercettare il nemico.</Italian>
          <Polish>Hornet 1, przyjęto. Wchodzę na 1500. Kierunek 050. Prędkość 720. Dopalam do przechwycenia.</Polish>
          <Russian>Hornet 1, вас понял. Поднимаюсь до 1500. Направляюсь на 050. Скорость 720. Перехожу в форсированный режим для перехвата.</Russian>
          <German>Hornet 1, verstanden. Steige auf 1.500. Richtung: 050, Geschwindigkeit: 720. Nachbrenner ist an, bin auf Abfangkurs.</German>
          <Czech>Hornet-1 slyší. Stoupám na 1500. Směr 050. Rychlost 720. Zahajuji pronásledování.</Czech>
          <English>Hornet 1 copies. Climbing to 1500. Heading 050. Speed 720. Burner to intercept.</English>
          <Portuguese>Vespa 1 aqui. Subindo para 1500. Direção 050. Velocidade 720. Ligando a pós-combustão pra interceptar o inimigo.</Portuguese>
          <Korean>호넷 1, 알았다! 1500으로 상승 중이다.. 050 방향이다. 속도는 720. 최선을 다해 차단하라.</Korean>
          <Chinesesimp>大黄蜂1收到. 爬升至1500. 航向050. 空速720. 使用后燃器前往拦截.</Chinesesimp>
          <Japanese>ホーネット 1、了解。1500 に上昇する。方位 050。速度 720。バーナー作動、迎撃に移る。</Japanese>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="str_a3_showcase_jets_15_flight_pilot_0">
          <Original>Negative. Radar's clean.</Original>
          <Chinese>否定. 雷達上沒有東西.</Chinese>
          <French>Négatif. Rien sur le radar.</French>
          <Spanish>Negativo. No aparece nada en el radar.</Spanish>
          <Italian>Negativo. Nessun contatto radar.</Italian>
          <Polish>Nie. Mam pusty radar.</Polish>
          <Russian>Никак нет. Радар чист.</Russian>
          <German>Negativ, der Radar ist sauber.</German>
          <Czech>Negativní. Na radaru nic není.</Czech>
          <English>Negative. Radar's clean.</English>
          <Portuguese>Negativo. O radar tá limpo.</Portuguese>
          <Korean>안 보인다. 레이더에는 잡히는 것이 없다.</Korean>
          <Chinesesimp>否定. 雷达上没有东西.</Chinesesimp>
          <Japanese>いいや。レーダーに反応なし。</Japanese>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="str_a3_showcase_jets_15_flight_wingman_0">
          <Original>Two, you see anything?</Original>
          <Chinese>2機, 你有看到什麼嗎?</Chinese>
          <French>2, vous voyez quelque chose ?</French>
          <Spanish>Dos, ¿ves algo?</Spanish>
          <Italian>Due, riesci a vedere qualcosa?</Italian>
          <Polish>Dwójka, widzisz coś?</Polish>
          <Russian>Второй, ты видишь что-нибудь?</Russian>
          <German>Zwei, sehen Sie was?</German>
          <Czech>Dvojko, vidíte něco?</Czech>
          <English>Two, you see anything?</English>
          <Portuguese>Dois, tá vendo alguma coisa?</Portuguese>
          <Korean>자네 둘, 뭐가 보이나?</Korean>
          <Chinesesimp>2机, 你有看到什么吗?</Chinesesimp>
          <Japanese>ツー、そちらは何か見えるか？</Japanese>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="str_a3_showcase_jets_15_flight_wingman_1">
          <Original>Roger. Stay sharp. Keep your eyes open. Out.</Original>
          <Chinese>了解. 保持機警. 眼觀四面. 通話完畢.</Chinese>
          <French>Compris. Vigilance. Gardez bien les yeux ouverts. Terminé.</French>
          <Spanish>Recibido. Céntrate y permanece ojo avizor. Corto.</Spanish>
          <Italian>Ricevuto. Stai in campana, tieni gli occhi aperti. Chiudo.</Italian>
          <Polish>Przyjąłem. Skup się. Oczy szeroko otwarte. Bez odbioru.</Polish>
          <Russian>Понял вас. Будьте начеку. Смотрите в оба. Конец связи.</Russian>
          <German>Roger, konzentrieren Sie sich und halten Sie die Augen offen. Ende.</German>
          <Czech>Rozumím. Dávejte pozor. Opatrně. Konec.</Czech>
          <English>Roger. Stay sharp. Keep your eyes open. Out.</English>
          <Portuguese>Entendido. Fica atento. Olhos bem abertos. Câmbio.</Portuguese>
          <Korean>알았다. 긴장 상태를 유지하라. 경계를 늦추지 마라. 이상.</Korean>
          <Chinesesimp>了解. 保持机警. 眼观四面. 通话完毕.</Chinesesimp>
          <Japanese>了解。気を抜くなよ。目を光らせておけ。以上。</Japanese>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="str_a3_showcase_jets_20_wingmanhit_pilot_0">
          <Original>Incoming!</Original>
          <Chinese>敵機來襲!</Chinese>
          <French>Tir en approche !</French>
          <Spanish>¡De camino!</Spanish>
          <Italian>Missile nemico in arrivo!</Italian>
          <Polish>Ostrzał!</Polish>
          <Russian>Осторожно! Ракета!</Russian>
          <German>Sie kommen!</German>
          <Czech>Blíží se střela!</Czech>
          <English>Incoming!</English>
          <Portuguese>Míssil se aproximando!</Portuguese>
          <Korean>간다!</Korean>
          <Chinesesimp>敌机来袭!</Chinesesimp>
          <Japanese>来るぞ！</Japanese>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="str_a3_showcase_jets_20_wingmanhit_wingman_0">
          <Original>Hornet 1, spiked!</Original>
          <Chinese>這裡是大黃蜂1, 我被鎖定了!</Chinese>
          <French>Hornet 1, on m'a verrouillé !</French>
          <Spanish>Hornet 1, ¡fijado!</Spanish>
          <Italian>Hornet 1, sono stato colpito!</Italian>
          <Polish>Hornet 1, nabili mnie!</Polish>
          <Russian>Hornet 1, меня засекли!</Russian>
          <German>Hornet 1, ich wurde anvisiert!</German>
          <Czech>Hornet-1, zaměřili mě!</Czech>
          <English>Hornet 1, spiked!</English>
          <Portuguese>Vespa 1, tô na mira!</Portuguese>
          <Korean>호넷 1, 당했다! </Korean>
          <Chinesesimp>这里是大黄蜂1, 我被锁定了!</Chinesesimp>
          <Japanese>ホーネット 1、ミサイル照射！</Japanese>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="str_a3_showcase_jets_20_wingmanhit_wingman_1">
          <Original>Hornet 1, avionics fucked! Repeat! I'm...</Original>
          <Chinese>這裡是大黃蜂1, 航電失效! 重複一遍! 我的...</Chinese>
          <French>Hornet 1, mes commandes sont foutues ! Je répète ! J'ai...</French>
          <Spanish>Hornet 1, ¡esto falla! ¡Repito! Estoy...</Spanish>
          <Italian>Hornet 1, dispositivi avionici fottuti! Ripeto! Sono…</Italian>
          <Polish>Hornet 1, awionika skopana! Powtarzam-</Polish>
          <Russian>Hornet 1, бортовая электроника накрылась пиздой! Повторяю! Я...</Russian>
          <German>Hornet 1, Avionik beschädigt! Ich wiederhole: Ich …</German>
          <Czech>Hornet-1, avionika je v prdeli! Opakuji. Jsem...</Czech>
          <English>Hornet 1, avionics fucked! Repeat! I'm...</English>
          <Portuguese>Vespa 1, aviônica comprometida! Repito! Eu tô…</Portuguese>
          <Korean>호넷 1, 항공전자기기가 먹통이다! 반복한다! 으...</Korean>
          <Chinesesimp>这里是大黄蜂1, 航电失效! 重复一遍! 我的...</Chinesesimp>
          <Japanese>ホーネット 1、アビオニクスをやられた！繰り返す！こちら…</Japanese>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="str_a3_showcase_jets_22_reportwingmanhit_pilot_0">
          <Original>Hornet 1, do you read?</Original>
          <Chinese>大黃蜂1, 你有收到嗎?</Chinese>
          <French>Hornet 1, vous me recevez ?</French>
          <Spanish>Hornet 1, ¿me recibes?</Spanish>
          <Italian>Hornet 1, mi ricevi?</Italian>
          <Polish>Hornet 1, słyszysz mnie?</Polish>
          <Russian>Hornet 1, как слышите?</Russian>
          <German>Hornet 1, kannst du mich hören?</German>
          <Czech>Hornet-1, slyšíte mě?</Czech>
          <English>Hornet 1, do you read?</English>
          <Portuguese>Vespa 1, na escuta?</Portuguese>
          <Korean>호넷 1, 알아들었나?</Korean>
          <Chinesesimp>大黄蜂1, 你有收到吗?</Chinesesimp>
          <Japanese>ホーネット 1、聞こえるか？</Japanese>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="str_a3_showcase_jets_22_reportwingmanhit_pilot_1">
          <Original>Shit. Shit. Shit.</Original>
          <Chinese>幹. 幹. 幹.</Chinese>
          <French>Merde. Merde. Merde !</French>
          <Spanish>Mierda, mierda, mierda.</Spanish>
          <Italian>Merda, merda, merda.</Italian>
          <Polish>Kurwa. Kurwa. Kurwa.</Polish>
          <Russian>Дерьмо. Дерьмо. Дерьмо.</Russian>
          <German>Scheiße, scheiße, scheiße!</German>
          <Czech>Sakra. Sakra. Sakra.</Czech>
          <English>Shit. Shit. Shit.</English>
          <Portuguese>Merda. Merda. Merda.</Portuguese>
          <Korean>제기랄. 제기랄. 제기랄.</Korean>
          <Chinesesimp>干. 干. 干.</Chinesesimp>
          <Japanese>クソッ。クソッ。クソッ。</Japanese>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="str_a3_showcase_jets_22_reportwingmanhit_pilot_2">
          <Original>Freeway. Hornet 2. Hornet 1 is down. Advise, over!</Original>
          <Chinese>自由路. 這裡是大黃蜂2. 大黃蜂1已被擊落. 請指示, 完畢!</Chinese>
          <French>Freeway. Hornet 2. Hornet 1 abattu. Attente instructions, à vous !</French>
          <Spanish>Freeway. Hornet 2. Hornet 1 ha caído. ¿Qué hago? ¡Cambio!</Spanish>
          <Italian>Freeway. Hornet 2. Hornet 1 è stato abbattuto. Attendo istruzioni, passo!</Italian>
          <Polish>Freeway. Hornet 2. Hornet 1 strącony. Jakie rozkazy, odbiór.</Polish>
          <Russian>Freeway, это Hornet 2. Hornet 1 сбит. Нужны ваши указания, прием!</Russian>
          <German>Freeway. Hornet 2. Hornet 1 ist zerstört. Warte auf Anweisungen, Ende!</German>
          <Czech>Freeway. Hornet-2. Hornet-1 byl sestřelen. Žádám o rozkazy, konec.</Czech>
          <English>Freeway. Hornet 2. Hornet 1 is down. Advise, over!</English>
          <Portuguese>Expressa. Vespa 2. O Vespa 1 foi abatido. Como proceder? Câmbio!</Portuguese>
          <Korean>프리웨이. 호넷 2 호넷 1이 추격됐다. 알았다, 이상!</Korean>
          <Chinesesimp>自由路. 这里是大黄蜂2. 大黄蜂1已被击落. 请指示, 完毕!</Chinesesimp>
          <Japanese>フリーウェイ。こちらホーネット 2。ホーネット 1 がやられた。指示をくれ！</Japanese>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="str_a3_showcase_jets_22_reportwingmanhit_tower_0">
          <Original>Acknowledged, Hornet 2. Fangs out. Rerouting Eagle squadron for immediate assist.</Original>
          <Chinese>了解, 大黃蜂2. 直接還擊. 我正在調派老鷹中隊前往支援.</Chinese>
          <French>Entendu, Hornet 2. Engagez l'ennemi. Escadron Eagle redirigé pour appui immédiat.</French>
          <Spanish>Recibido, Hornet 2. A por todas. Desviando al escuadrón Eagle para apoyo inmediato.</Spanish>
          <Italian>Ricevuto, Hornet 2. Pronto al combattimento. Squadrone Eagle deviato per supporto immediato.</Italian>
          <Polish>Przyjąłem, Hornet 2. Strzelaj bez rozkazu. Wysyłam eskadrę Eagle jako wsparcie.</Polish>
          <Russian>Понял вас, Hornet 2. Оружие наготове. Перебрасываю эскадрилью Eagle для оказания немедленной поддержки.</Russian>
          <German>Verstanden, Hornet 2. Heizt ihnen ordentlich ein! Wir schicken euch Eagle zur Unterstützung.</German>
          <Czech>Rozumím, Hornet-2. Výzbroj aktivována. Vysíláme letku Eagle na okamžitou podporu.</Czech>
          <English>Acknowledged, Hornet 2. Fangs out. Rerouting Eagle squadron for immediate assist.</English>
          <Portuguese>Entendido, Vespa 2. O Presa desligou. O esquadrão Águia tá sendo realocado pra dar assistência imediata.</Portuguese>
          <Korean>알았다. 호넷 2. 격렬한 공중전이다. 이글 비행대는 노선을 변경하여 즉각 지원한다.</Korean>
          <Chinesesimp>了解, 大黄蜂2. 直接还击. 我正在调派老鹰中队前往支援.</Chinesesimp>
          <Japanese>了解だ、ホーネット 2。やってやるぞ。今すぐイーグル隊を支援に向かわせる。</Japanese>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="str_a3_showcase_jets_25_scratchone_pilot_0">
          <Original>Splash one!</Original>
          <Chinese>擊落一架!</Chinese>
          <French>Un de moins !</French>
          <Spanish>¡Impacto!</Spanish>
          <Italian>Preso!</Italian>
          <Polish>Strącenie!</Polish>
          <Russian>Получай!</Russian>
          <German>Einer weniger!</German>
          <Czech>Cíl zničen!</Czech>
          <English>Splash one!</English>
          <Portuguese>Detonei um!</Portuguese>
          <Korean>착탄 완료!</Korean>
          <Chinesesimp>击落一架!</Chinesesimp>
          <Japanese>一機撃墜！</Japanese>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="str_a3_showcase_jets_25_scratchone_pilot_1">
          <Original>This one's for you, Chris!</Original>
          <Chinese>克里斯, 這架是為你打的!</Chinese>
          <French>C'est pour toi, Chris !</French>
          <Spanish>¡Esta va por ti, Chris!</Spanish>
          <Italian>Questo è per te, Chris!</Italian>
          <Polish>To za ciebie, Chris!</Polish>
          <Russian>Это за тебя, Chris!</Russian>
          <German>Der ist für dich, Chris!</German>
          <Czech>Tahle je pro tebe, Chrisi!</Czech>
          <English>This one's for you, Chris!</English>
          <Portuguese>Este é pra você, Chris!</Portuguese>
          <Korean>크리스, 이번에는 네가 맡아라!</Korean>
          <Chinesesimp>克里斯, 这架是为你打的!</Chinesesimp>
          <Japanese>クリス、こいつはお前に捧げてやる！</Japanese>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="str_a3_showcase_jets_30_reinforcements_tower_0">
          <Original>Hornet 2, this is Freeway. Eagle's in the killbox and engaging bandits.</Original>
          <Chinese>大黃蜂2, 這裡是自由路. 老鷹中隊已經進入殺戮區, 開始與敵人交戰.</Chinese>
          <French>Hornet 2, ici Freeway. Eagle est en place et engage l'ennemi.</French>
          <Spanish>Hornet 2, aquí Freeway. Eagle está en la zona designada luchando contra los enemigos.</Spanish>
          <Italian>Hornet 2, qui Freeway. Eagle si trova nel cubo della morte e sta ingaggiando i bersagli nemici.</Italian>
          <Polish>Hornet 2, tu Freeway. Eagle jest na miejscu i atakuje przeciwnika.</Polish>
          <Russian>Hornet 2, это Freeway. Eagle в районе задания, ведет бой против вражеских самолетов.</Russian>
          <German>Hornet 2, hier spricht Freeway. Eagle ist in der Killbox angekommen und greift die Bandits an.</German>
          <Czech>Hornet-2, tady Freeway. Letka Eagle je na bojišti a útočí na nepřátele.</Czech>
          <English>Hornet 2, this is Freeway. Eagle's in the killbox and engaging bandits.</English>
          <Portuguese>Vespa 2, aqui é o Expressa. O Águia tá na área da missão enfrentando os inimigos.</Portuguese>
          <Korean>호넷 2, 여기는 프리웨이다. 이글이 살상 지대에서 강도단 항공기와 교전 중이다.</Korean>
          <Chinesesimp>大黄蜂2, 这里是自由路. 老鹰中队已经进入杀戮区, 开始与敌人交战.</Chinesesimp>
          <Japanese>ホーネット 2、こちらフリーウェイ。キルボックスにイーグルが入った。現在敵と交戦中。</Japanese>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="str_a3_showcase_jets_35_winchester_pilot_0">
          <Original>Hornet 2. Winchester.</Original>
          <Chinese>這裡是大黃蜂2. 彈藥用完.</Chinese>
          <French>Hornet 2. Winchester.</French>
          <Spanish>Hornet 2. Winchester.</Spanish>
          <Italian>Hornet 2. A corto di munizioni.</Italian>
          <Polish>Hornet 2. Koniec amunicji.</Polish>
          <Russian>Hornet 2. Winchester.</Russian>
          <German>Hornet 2. Winchester.</German>
          <Czech>Hornet-2. Došla mi munice.</Czech>
          <English>Hornet 2. Winchester.</English>
          <Portuguese>Vespa 2. Winchester.</Portuguese>
          <Korean>호넷 2 윈체스터.</Korean>
          <Chinesesimp>这里是大黄蜂2. 弹药用完.</Chinesesimp>
          <Japanese>こちらホーネット 2。「ウィンチェスター」。</Japanese>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="str_a3_showcase_jets_35_winchester_tower_0">
          <Original>Copy that, Hornet 2.</Original>
          <Chinese>收到, 大黃蜂2.</Chinese>
          <French>Bien reçu, Hornet 2.</French>
          <Spanish>Recibido, Hornet 2.</Spanish>
          <Italian>Ricevuto, Hornet 2.</Italian>
          <Polish>Zrozumiano, Hornet 2.</Polish>
          <Russian>Понял вас, Hornet 2.</Russian>
          <German>Verstanden, Hornet 2.</German>
          <Czech>Hornet-2, rozumím.</Czech>
          <English>Copy that, Hornet 2.</English>
          <Portuguese>Afirmativo, Vespa 2.</Portuguese>
          <Korean>알았다. 호넷 2.</Korean>
          <Chinesesimp>收到, 大黄蜂2.</Chinesesimp>
          <Japanese>了解だ、ホーネット 2。</Japanese>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="str_a3_showcase_jets_35_winchester_tower_1">
          <Original>Divert to Altis International Airport or head back here - your call. Rearm, then re-engage. Out.</Original>
          <Chinese>請前往Altis國際機場或是返回來這裡 - 你自己決定. 重新補給後再繼續交戰. 通話完畢.</Chinese>
          <French>Déroutez-vous vers l'aéroport international d'Altis, ou rentrez au bercail. À vous de voir. Réarmez, puis réengagez. Terminé.</French>
          <Spanish>Desvíate hacia el Aeropuerto Internacional de Altis o ven aquí. Tú decides. Reármate y luego vuelve al ataque. Corto.</Spanish>
          <Italian>Devia in direzione dell'Aeroporto Internazionale di Altis o torna qui, a te la scelta. Riarmati e poi procedi di nuovo con l'ingaggio. Chiudo.</Italian>
          <Polish>Obierz kierunek na Międzynarodowy port lotniczy Altis lub wróć tu – twoja decyzja. Uzupełnij uzbrojenie i wznów działania. Bez odbioru.</Polish>
          <Russian>Отправляйтесь в Международный аэропорт Алтиса либо возвращайтесь сюда. Вам решать. Перевооружитесь, затем возвращайтесь на задание. Конец связи.</Russian>
          <German>Fliegen Sie zum Altis International Airport, oder kehren Sie hierher zurück – Ihre Entscheidung. Rüsten Sie auf und greifen Sie wieder an. Ende.</German>
          <Czech>Přistaňte na Altiském mezinárodním letišti nebo se vraťte sem, jak chcete. Přezbrojte a potom se znovu zapojte do boje. Konec.</Czech>
          <English>Divert to Altis International Airport or head back here - your call. Rearm, then re-engage. Out.</English>
          <Portuguese>Desvie para o Aeroporto Internacional de Altis ou volte para cá. A decisão é sua. Rearme-se e volte pra o combate. Câmbio.</Portuguese>
          <Korean>알티스 국제공항으로 선회를 하던 귀환을 하던, 알아서 하시지. 재무장 후 다시 교전한다. 이상.</Korean>
          <Chinesesimp>请前往Altis国际机场或是返回来这里 - 你自己决定. 重新补给后再继续交战. 通话完毕.</Chinesesimp>
          <Japanese>アルティス国際空港へ向かうか、こちらへ戻れ - 判断はそちらに任せる。補給後、再度攻撃に移れ。以上。</Japanese>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="str_a3_showcase_jets_40_skiesclear_pilot_0">
          <Original>All enemy jets destroyed - the skies are ours.</Original>
          <Chinese>敵軍戰機皆已殲滅 - 天空是我們的了.</Chinese>
          <French>Chasseurs ennemis abattus. Le ciel est à nous.</French>
          <Spanish>Cazas enemigos destruidos. El cielo es nuestro.</Spanish>
          <Italian>Tutti i jet nemici sono stati distrutti. Il cielo è nostro.</Italian>
          <Polish>Przeciwnik zniszczony – niebo należy do nas.</Polish>
          <Russian>Все вражеские самолеты уничтожены. Небо наше.</Russian>
          <German>Alle feindlichen Jets wurden zerstört – der Himmel gehört uns.</German>
          <Czech>Všechny nepřátelské stíhačky jsou zničeny – nebe je naše.</Czech>
          <English>All enemy jets destroyed - the skies are ours.</English>
          <Portuguese>Todos os jatos inimigos destruídos, o céu é nosso.</Portuguese>
          <Korean>적의 모든 제트기가 파괴됐다. 영공은 이제 우리 차지다.</Korean>
          <Chinesesimp>敌军战机皆已歼灭 - 天空是我们的了.</Chinesesimp>
          <Japanese>全敵性戦闘機を撃破 - 空はこちらの物だ。</Japanese>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="str_a3_showcase_jets_45_groundclear_pilot_0">
          <Original>Shack!</Original>
          <Chinese>命中!</Chinese>
          <French>Coup au but !</French>
          <Spanish>¡Impacto!</Spanish>
          <Italian>Colpito!</Italian>
          <Polish>Trafienie!</Polish>
          <Russian>Прямое попадание!</Russian>
          <German>Volltreffer!</German>
          <Czech>Zásah!</Czech>
          <English>Shack!</English>
          <Portuguese>Na mosca!</Portuguese>
          <Korean>명중이다!</Korean>
          <Chinesesimp>命中!</Chinesesimp>
          <Japanese>命中！</Japanese>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="str_a3_showcase_jets_45_groundclear_pilot_1">
          <Original>Hornet 2, enemy armor neutralized. Over.</Original>
          <Chinese>這裡是大黃蜂2, 敵軍裝甲車已被摧毀. 完畢.</Chinese>
          <French>Hornet 2, forces ennemies neutralisées. Terminé.</French>
          <Spanish>Hornet 2, blindado enemigo neutralizado. Cambio.</Spanish>
          <Italian>Hornet 2, nemici corazzati neutralizzati. Passo.</Italian>
          <Polish>Hornet 2, jednostka pancerna zneutralizowana. Odbiór.</Polish>
          <Russian>Hornet 2, вражеская бронированная техника нейтрализована. Прием.</Russian>
          <German>Hornet 2, feindliche Fahrzeuge neutralisiert, Ende.</German>
          <Czech>Hornet-2, nepřátelská obrněná vozidla byla zneškodněna. Přepínám.</Czech>
          <English>Hornet 2, enemy armor neutralized. Over.</English>
          <Portuguese>Vespa 2, armadura inimiga neutralizada. Câmbio.</Portuguese>
          <Korean>호넷 2, 적의 기갑 차량이 무력화됐다. 이상.</Korean>
          <Chinesesimp>这里是大黄蜂2, 敌军装甲车已被摧毁. 完毕.</Chinesesimp>
          <Japanese>こちらホーネット 2、敵装甲車両を無力化。オーバー。</Japanese>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="str_a3_showcase_jets_50_goodjobrtb_tower_0">
          <Original>Good job. Hornet 2 - come on home.</Original>
          <Chinese>幹的好. 大黃蜂2 - 回家吧.</Chinese>
          <French>Bon boulot. Hornet 2, rentrez au bercail.</French>
          <Spanish>Buen trabajo. Hornet 2, a casa.</Spanish>
          <Italian>Ottimo lavoro. Hornet 2, torna alla base.</Italian>
          <Polish>Dobra robota. Hornet 2, wracaj do bazy.</Polish>
          <Russian>Отличная работа. Hornet 2, возвращайтесь домой.</Russian>
          <German>Gute Arbeit, Hornet 2! Kommen Sie nach Hause.</German>
          <Czech>Dobrá práce. Hornet-2, vraťte se domů.</Czech>
          <English>Good job. Hornet 2 - come on home.</English>
          <Portuguese>Bom trabalho. Vespa 2 — pode voltar pra casa.</Portuguese>
          <Korean>잘했다. 호넷 2 - 귀환하라.</Korean>
          <Chinesesimp>干的好. 大黄蜂2 - 回家吧.</Chinesesimp>
          <Japanese>よくやった。ホーネット 2 - 帰投してくれ。</Japanese>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="str_a3_showcase_jets_55_requestlanding_pilot_0">
          <Original>Freeway, Hornet 2 on approach. Request landing. Over.</Original>
          <Chinese>自由路, 這裡是大黃蜂2, 進場中. 請求降落許可. 完畢.</Chinese>
          <French>Freeway, Hornet 2 en approche. Demande autorisation appontage. À vous.</French>
          <Spanish>Freeway, Hornet 2 de camino. Petición de aterrizaje. Cambio.</Spanish>
          <Italian>Freeway, Hornet 2 in avvicinamento. Richiesta di atterraggio. Passo.</Italian>
          <Polish>Freeway, Hornet 2 na podejściu. Prośba o lądowanie. Odbiór.</Polish>
          <Russian>Freeway, Hornet 2 на подходе. Запрашиваю посадку. Прием.</Russian>
          <German>Freeway, Hornet 2 im Anflug. Bitte um Landeerlaubnis, Ende.</German>
          <Czech>Freeway, Hornet-2 se blíží. Žádám o povolení k přistání. Přepínám.</Czech>
          <English>Freeway, Hornet 2 on approach. Request landing. Over.</English>
          <Portuguese>Expressa, Vespa 2 se aproximando. Solicito permissão para pouso. Câmbio.</Portuguese>
          <Korean>프리웨이, 호넷 2가 진입 중이다. 착륙을 요청하라. 이상.</Korean>
          <Chinesesimp>自由路, 这里是大黄蜂2, 进场中. 请求降落许可. 完毕.</Chinesesimp>
          <Japanese>フリーウェイへ。ホーネット 2、アプローチを開始。着艦許可を求む。オーバー。</Japanese>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="str_a3_showcase_jets_55_requestlanding_tower_0">
          <Original>Go ahead, Hornet-2. Your signal's Charlie.</Original>
          <Chinese>請繼續, 大黃蜂2. 允許降落.</Chinese>
          <French>Allez-y, Hornet 2. Charlie pour appontage.</French>
          <Spanish>Adelante, Hornet-2. Puedes aterrizar.</Spanish>
          <Italian>Procedi, Hornet-2. Inizia subito l'avvicinamento e atterra all'arrivo.</Italian>
          <Polish>Droga wolna, Hornet 2. Możesz lądować.</Polish>
          <Russian>Hornet-2, посадку разрешаю.</Russian>
          <German>Legen Sie los, Hornet-2. Ihr Signal ist Charlie.</German>
          <Czech>Můžete se přiblížit, Hornet-2. Přistávací zóna je volná, můžete přistát.</Czech>
          <English>Go ahead, Hornet-2. Your signal's Charlie.</English>
          <Portuguese>Siga em frente, Vespa 2. Tudo pronto pra pousar.</Portuguese>
          <Korean>어서, 호넷-2. 자네 부호는 찰리다.</Korean>
          <Chinesesimp>请继续, 大黄蜂2. 允许降落.</Chinesesimp>
          <Japanese>着陸地点はクリアだ、ホーネット 2。いつでもどうぞ。</Japanese>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="str_a3_showcase_jets_60_castask_pilot_0">
          <Original>Solid copy, Freeway. Hornet-2, Out.</Original>
          <Chinese>完整收到, 自由路. 大黃蜂2, 通話完畢.</Chinese>
          <French>Bien reçu, Freeway. Hornet 2, terminé.</French>
          <Spanish>Alto y claro, Freeway. Hornet-2, corto.</Spanish>
          <Italian>Ricevuto forte e chiaro, Freeway. Hornet-2, chiudo.</Italian>
          <Polish>Zrozumiałem wyraźnie, Freeway. Hornet 2, bez odbioru.</Polish>
          <Russian>Понял хорошо, Freeway. Hornet-2, конец связи.</Russian>
          <German>Verstanden, Freeway. Hornet-2, Ende.</German>
          <Czech>Slyším vás dobře, Freeway. Hornet-2, konec.</Czech>
          <English>Solid copy, Freeway. Hornet-2, Out.</English>
          <Portuguese>Afirmativo, Expressa. Vespa 2, câmbio.</Portuguese>
          <Korean>알았다. 프리웨이. 호넷-2, 빠져라.</Korean>
          <Chinesesimp>完整收到, 自由路. 大黄蜂2, 通话完毕.</Chinesesimp>
          <Japanese>全了解だ、フリーウェイ。ホーネット 2、交信終わる。</Japanese>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="str_a3_showcase_jets_60_castask_tower_0">
          <Original>Hornet-2, ground forces are reporting CSAT armor on Hill 87. I'm retasking you to take them out. How copy? Over.</Original>
          <Chinese>大黃蜂2, 地面部隊報告有廣協同盟的裝甲載具出現在87高地上. 我重新指派你前往殲滅掉他們. 有收到嗎? 完畢.</Chinese>
          <French>Hornet 2, l'infanterie nous indique des forces du CSAT sur la Colline 87. Vous avez pour mission de les éliminer. Vous me recevez ? À vous.</French>
          <Spanish>Hornet-2, las fuerzas terrestres informan de que hay blindados del CSAT en la colina 87. Quiero que acabes con ellas. ¿Me recibes? Cambio.</Spanish>
          <Italian>Hornet-2, le forze di terra riferiscono la presenza di veicoli corazzati CSAT ad Hill 87. Il tuo nuovo obiettivo è di tirarle fuori da lì. Mi ricevi? Passo.</Italian>
          <Polish>Hornet 2, siły naziemne donoszą o jednostce pancernej CSAT na wzgórzu 87. Przydzielam cię do jej zniszczenia. Zrozumiano? Odbiór.</Polish>
          <Russian>Hornet-2, наземные силы докладывают о бронированной технике на Hill 87. Ваша новое задание – уничтожить их. Как поняли? Прием.</Russian>
          <German>Hornet-2, Bodentruppen haben CSAT-Fahrzeuge auf Hügel 87 gesichtet. Schalten Sie sie aus. Over.</German>
          <Czech>Hornet-2, pozemní jednotky hlásí obrněná vozidla CSAT na kopci 87. Vydejte se tam a zničte je. Jak nás slyšíte? Přepínám.</Czech>
          <English>Hornet-2, ground forces are reporting CSAT armor on Hill 87. I'm retasking you to take them out. How copy? Over.</English>
          <Portuguese>Vespa 2, as forças terrestres estão reportando a presença de blindados da CSAT em Hill 87. Você tá sendo realocado pra acabar com eles. Entendido? Câmbio.</Portuguese>
          <Korean>호넷-2, 지상군이 Hill 87에서 CSAT 기갑차량을 보고하고 있다. 재임무를 주겠다. 놈들을 타격하라. 들었나? 이상.</Korean>
          <Chinesesimp>大黄蜂2, 地面部队报告有广协同盟的装甲载具出现在87高地上. 我重新指派你前往歼灭掉他们. 有收到吗? 完毕.</Chinesesimp>
          <Japanese>ホーネット 2、地上部隊より 87 高地に CSAT 装甲車両の報告あり。任務内容を変更、そちらを排除せよ。了解か？オーバー。</Japanese>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="str_a3_showcase_jets_65_minordamage_pilot_0">
          <Original>Hornet-2, I'm hit!</Original>
          <Chinese>這裡是大黃蜂2, 我中彈了!</Chinese>
          <French>Hornet 2, je suis touché !</French>
          <Spanish>Hornet-2, ¡me han dado!</Spanish>
          <Italian>Hornet-2, sono stato colpito!</Italian>
          <Polish>Hornet 2, oberwałem!</Polish>
          <Russian>Hornet-2, в меня попали!</Russian>
          <German>Hornet-2, ich bin getroffen!</German>
          <Czech>Hornet-2, zasáhli mě!</Czech>
          <English>Hornet-2, I'm hit!</English>
          <Portuguese>Vespa 2, fui atingido!</Portuguese>
          <Korean>호넷-2, 당했다!</Korean>
          <Chinesesimp>这里是大黄蜂2, 我中弹了!</Chinesesimp>
          <Japanese>ホーネット 2、食らった！</Japanese>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="str_a3_showcase_jets_65_minordamage_pilot_1">
          <Original>Roger, Freeway, I'm RTB.</Original>
          <Chinese>收到, 自由路, 我正在返航.</Chinese>
          <French>Compris, Freeway, retour à la base.</French>
          <Spanish>Recibido, Freeway, vuelvo a la base.</Spanish>
          <Italian>Ricevuto, Freeway, torno alla base.</Italian>
          <Polish>Przyjąłem, Freeway, wracam do bazy.</Polish>
          <Russian>Понял вас, Freeway. Возвращаюсь на базу.</Russian>
          <German>Roger, Freeway, kehre zur Basis zurück!</German>
          <Czech>Rozumím, Freeway, vracím se na základnu.</Czech>
          <English>Roger, Freeway, I'm RTB.</English>
          <Portuguese>Entendido, Expressa, tô retornando pra base.</Portuguese>
          <Korean>알았다, 프리웨이. 귀환하겠다.</Korean>
          <Chinesesimp>收到, 自由路, 我正在返航.</Chinesesimp>
          <Japanese>了解した、フリーウェイ。帰投する。</Japanese>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="str_a3_showcase_jets_65_minordamage_tower_0">
          <Original>Message received, Hornet-2. Abort mission. Over.</Original>
          <Chinese>收到訊息, 大黃蜂2. 中止任務. 完畢.</Chinese>
          <French>Message reçu, Hornet 2. Annulez la mission. À vous.</French>
          <Spanish>Mensaje recibido, Hornet-2. Aborta la misión. Cambio.</Spanish>
          <Italian>Messaggio ricevuto, Hornet-2. Annulla la missione. Passo.</Italian>
          <Polish>Przyjąłem, Hornet 2. Przerwij misję. Odbiór.</Polish>
          <Russian>Сообщение получено, Hornet-2. Прекратить выполнение задания. Прием.</Russian>
          <German>Nachricht erhalten, Hornet-2. Mission abbrechen, Over.</German>
          <Czech>Slyšíme, Hornet-2. Zrušte misi. Přepínám.</Czech>
          <English>Message received, Hornet-2. Abort mission. Over.</English>
          <Portuguese>Mensagem recebida, Vespa 2. Aborta a missão. Câmbio.</Portuguese>
          <Korean>메시지를 수신했다. 호넷-2. 임무를 취소하라. 이상.</Korean>
          <Chinesesimp>收到讯息, 大黄蜂2. 中止任务. 完毕.</Chinesesimp>
          <Japanese>メッセージ了解、ホーネット 2。任務中止。オーバー。</Japanese>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="str_a3_showcase_jets_70_majordamage_pilot_0">
          <Original>Mayday! Mayday! Mayday! This is Hornet-2, losing altitude!</Original>
          <Chinese>求救! 求救! 求救! 這裡是大黃蜂2, 失去高度中!</Chinese>
          <French>Mayday ! Mayday ! Mayday ! Ici Hornet 2, je perds de l'altitude !</French>
          <Spanish>¡Mayday! ¡Mayday! ¡Mayday! Aquí Hornet-2: ¡pierdo altitud!</Spanish>
          <Italian>Mayday! Mayday! Mayday! Qui Hornet-2, sto perdendo quota!</Italian>
          <Polish>Mayday! Mayday! Mayday! Tu Hornet 2, spadam!</Polish>
          <Russian>Терплю бедствие! Это Hornet-2, я теряю высоту!</Russian>
          <German>Mayday! Mayday! Mayday! Hier ist Hornet-2, ich verliere an Flughöhe!</German>
          <Czech>Mayday! Mayday! Mayday! Tady Hornet-2, ztrácím výšku!</Czech>
          <English>Mayday! Mayday! Mayday! This is Hornet-2, losing altitude!</English>
          <Portuguese>Socorro! Socorro! Aqui é o Vespa 2, perdendo altitude!</Portuguese>
          <Korean>메이데이! 메이데이! 메이데이! 여기는 호넷-2, 고도를 잃고 있다!</Korean>
          <Chinesesimp>求救! 求救! 求救! 这里是大黄蜂2, 失去高度中!</Chinesesimp>
          <Japanese>メーデー！メーデー！メーデー！こちらホーネット 2、高度低下中！</Japanese>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="str_a3_showcase_jets_70_majordamage_pilot_1">
          <Original>Christ, I - I'm punching out!</Original>
          <Chinese>天殺的, 我 - 我要彈射了!</Chinese>
          <French>Merde, je - Je dois sauter !</French>
          <Spanish>Dios, ¡voy a salir disparado!</Spanish>
          <Italian>Cristo, m-mi sto lanciando!</Italian>
          <Polish>Chryste, katapultuję się!</Polish>
          <Russian>Черт, я падаю!</Russian>
          <German>Verdammt, ich…ich bin raus!</German>
          <Czech>Zatraceně, musím vypadnout!</Czech>
          <English>Christ, I - I'm punching out!</English>
          <Portuguese>Meu Deus, eu… eu tô ejetando!</Portuguese>
          <Korean>젠장, 비.. 비상 탈출을 하고 있다!</Korean>
          <Chinesesimp>天杀的, 我 - 我要弹射了!</Chinesesimp>
          <Japanese>マズいっ、 - 脱出する！</Japanese>
        </Key>
        <Key ID="str_a3_showcase_jets_75_ejected_pilot_0">
          <Original>Well... this is gonna suck.</Original>
          <Chinese>媽的... 這下可慘了.</Chinese>
          <French>Hmm... Ça va faire mal.</French>
          <Spanish>Bueno... Menudo asco.</Spanish>
          <Italian>Beh… sarà una bella rogna.</Italian>
          <Polish>Kiepsko to widzę.</Polish>
          <Russian>Так... а вот это хреново.</Russian>
          <German>Na das kann ja heiter werden ...</German>
          <Czech>Hm... nebude to žádná prdel.</Czech>
          <English>Well... this is gonna suck.</English>
          <Portuguese>Ai… isso vai ser uma merda.</Portuguese>
          <Korean>이런... 열받는 군.</Korean>
          <Chinesesimp>妈的... 这下可惨了.</Chinesesimp>
          <Japanese>くそ… こいつは面倒なことになりそうだ。</Japanese>
        </Key>
      </Container>
      <Key ID="str_a3_identity_DylanMoore">
        <Original>Dylan Moore</Original>
        <Chinese>迪倫·摩爾</Chinese>
        <French>Dylan Moore</French>
        <Spanish>Dylan Moore</Spanish>
        <Italian>Dylan Moore</Italian>
        <Polish>Dylan Moore</Polish>
        <Russian>Dylan Moore</Russian>
        <German>Dylan Moore</German>
        <Czech>Dylan Moore</Czech>
        <English>Dylan Moore</English>
        <Portuguese>Dylan Moore</Portuguese>
        <Korean>딜란 무어</Korean>
        <Chinesesimp>迪伦·摩尔</Chinesesimp>
        <Japanese>ディラン・ムーア</Japanese>
      </Key>
      <Key ID="str_a3_identity_JeffRyan">
        <Original>Jeff 'Rocket' Ryan</Original>
        <Chinese>傑夫'火箭'雷恩</Chinese>
        <French>Jeff "Rocket" Ryan</French>
        <Spanish>Jeff «Rocket» Ryan</Spanish>
        <Italian>Jeff "Rocket" Ryan</Italian>
        <Polish>Jeff „Rocket” Ryan</Polish>
        <Russian>Jeff 'Rocket' Ryan</Russian>
        <German>Jeff 'Rocket' Ryan</German>
        <Czech>Jeff „Rocket“ Ryan</Czech>
        <English>Jeff 'Rocket' Ryan</English>
        <Portuguese>Jeff Rocket Ryan</Portuguese>
        <Korean>제프 "로켓" 라이언</Korean>
        <Chinesesimp>杰夫'火箭'雷恩</Chinesesimp>
        <Japanese>ジェフ・"ロケット"・ライアン</Japanese>
      </Key>
    </Container>
    <Container name="Welcome">
      <Key ID="str_a3_rscdisplaywelcome_jets_pare_titleb">
        <Original>PLATFORM</Original>
        <Chinese>平台</Chinese>
        <French>PLATEFORME</French>
        <Spanish>PLATAFORMA</Spanish>
        <Italian>PIATTAFORMA</Italian>
        <Polish>PLATFORMA</Polish>
        <Russian>ПЛАТФОРМА</Russian>
        <German>PLATTFORM</German>
        <Czech>PLATFORMA</Czech>
        <English>PLATFORM</English>
        <Portuguese>PLATAFORMA</Portuguese>
        <Korean>플랫폼</Korean>
        <Chinesesimp>平台</Chinesesimp>
        <Japanese>プラットフォーム</Japanese>
      </Key>
      <Key ID="str_a3_rscdisplaywelcome_jets_pare_list9_title">
        <Original>Official Soundtrack</Original>
        <Chinese>官方原聲帶</Chinese>
        <French>Bande originale</French>
        <Spanish>Banda sonora oficial</Spanish>
        <Italian>Colonna sonora ufficiale</Italian>
        <Polish>Oficjalna ścieżka dźwiękowa</Polish>
        <Russian>Официальный саундтрек</Russian>
        <German>Offizieller Soundtrack</German>
        <Czech>Oficiální soundtrack</Czech>
        <English>Official Soundtrack</English>
        <Portuguese>Trilha sonora oficial</Portuguese>
        <Korean>공식 사운드트랙</Korean>
        <Chinesesimp>官方原声带</Chinesesimp>
        <Japanese>公式サウンドトラック</Japanese>
      </Key>
      <Key ID="str_a3_rscdisplaywelcome_jets_pare_list9">
        <Original>a new music track befitting the jets theme</Original>
        <Chinese>一首配合戰機主題的曲子</Chinese>
        <French>un nouveau morceau sur le thème des chasseurs</French>
        <Spanish>Una nueva pista de música, ideal para los cazas.</Spanish>
        <Italian>un nuovo brano fedele al tema dei jet</Italian>
        <Polish>nowy utwór inspirowany motywem odrzutowców</Polish>
        <Russian>Новая музыкальная композиция, соответствующая теме самолетов</Russian>
        <German>ein neuer Musiktrack passend zum Jets-Thema</German>
        <Czech>nová skladba vhodná k tematice stíhacích letounů</Czech>
        <English>a new music track befitting the jets theme</English>
        <Portuguese>uma nova faixa musical condizente com o tema de Jets</Portuguese>
        <Korean>제트기별 테마에 어울리는 신규 음악 트랙입니다.</Korean>
        <Chinesesimp>一首配合战机主题的曲子</Chinesesimp>
        <Japanese>Jets のテーマに沿った新規音楽トラック</Japanese>
      </Key>
      <Key ID="str_a3_rscdisplaywelcome_jets_pare_list8_title">
        <Original>Surface-to-Air</Original>
        <Chinese>地對空武器</Chinese>
        <French>Mer-Air</French>
        <Spanish>Tierra-aire</Spanish>
        <Italian>Terra-aria</Italian>
        <Polish>Ziemia-powietrze</Polish>
        <Russian>Орудия класса "земля-воздух"</Russian>
        <German>Boden-Luft</German>
        <Czech>Země-vzduch</Czech>
        <English>Surface-to-Air</English>
        <Portuguese>Da superfície para o ar</Portuguese>
        <Korean>지대공</Korean>
        <Chinesesimp>地对空武器</Chinesesimp>
        <Japanese>地対空</Japanese>
      </Key>
      <Key ID="str_a3_rscdisplaywelcome_jets_pare_list8">
        <Original>3 autonomous systems designed to accompany the carrier and serve as its self-defense package</Original>
        <Chinese>三款自主防衛系統, 被設計用來搭載在航空母艦上進行自衛防禦</Chinese>
        <French>3 systèmes autonomes destinés à l'autodéfense du porte-avions.</French>
        <Spanish>3 sistemas autónomos diseñados para ir con el portaaviones y funcionar como modo de autodefensa.</Spanish>
        <Italian>tre sistemi autonomi con funzione di autodifesa progettati per la portaerei.</Italian>
        <Polish>Trzy autonomiczne systemy samoobrony lotniskowca</Polish>
        <Russian>Три автономные системы, предназначенные для сопровождения авианосца и служащие в качестве своеобразного комплекса самообороны</Russian>
        <German>3 autonome Systeme, die den Träger begleiten und als Selbstverteidigungssystem fungieren</German>
        <Czech>3 autonomní systémy navržené jako doplněk letadlové lodě, které slouží jako balíček samostatné obrany</Czech>
        <English>3 autonomous systems designed to accompany the carrier and serve as its self-defense package</English>
        <Portuguese>3 sistemas autônomos projetados para acompanhar o porta-aviões e servir de pacote de autodefesa.</Portuguese>
        <Korean>항공 모함을 동반하고 자가 방어 패키지 역할을 하도록 설계된 3개의 자율 시스템입니다.</Korean>
        <Chinesesimp>三款自主防卫系统, 被设计用来搭载在航空母舰上进行自卫防御</Chinesesimp>
        <Japanese>自己防衛パッケージの一部として空母に追随する 3 つの自律システム。</Japanese>
      </Key>
      <Key ID="str_a3_rscdisplaywelcome_jets_pare_list7_title">
        <Original>USS Freedom (CVN-83)</Original>
        <Chinese>美國海軍自由號(CVN-83)</Chinese>
        <French>USS Freedom (CVN-83)</French>
        <Spanish>USS Freedom (CVN-83)</Spanish>
        <Italian>USS Freedom (CVN-83)</Italian>
        <Polish>USS Freedom (CVN-83)</Polish>
        <Russian>USS Freedom (CVN-83)</Russian>
        <German>USS Freedom (CVN-83)</German>
        <Czech>USS Freedom (CVN-83)</Czech>
        <English>USS Freedom (CVN-83)</English>
        <Portuguese>USS Freedom (CVN-83)</Portuguese>
        <Korean>USS Freedom(CVN-83)</Korean>
        <Chinesesimp>美国海军自由号(CVN-83)</Chinesesimp>
        <Japanese>USS「フリーダム」 (CVN-83)</Japanese>
      </Key>
      <Key ID="str_a3_rscdisplaywelcome_jets_pare_list7">
        <Original>a static functional aircraft carrier that can be placed as an object in Eden Editor</Original>
        <Chinese>可以在伊甸編輯器中擺出做為固定物件的航空母艦</Chinese>
        <French>un porte-avions statique et fonctionnel, utilisable en tant qu'objet dans Eden Editor</French>
        <Spanish>Un portaaviones estático, pero funcional, que se puede poner como un objeto en el Eden Editor.</Spanish>
        <Italian>una portaerei statica funzionale che può essere posizionata come oggetto nell'Eden Editor</Italian>
        <Polish>nieruchomy, działający lotniskowiec, który można umieścić w scenariuszu jako obiekt z poziomu Eden Editor</Polish>
        <Russian>Статический функциональный авианосец, который может быть помещен как объект в Eden Editor</Russian>
        <German>ein statischer, funktioneller Flugzeugträger, der als Objekt im Eden Editor platziert werden kann</German>
        <Czech>statická funkční letadlová loď, kterou lze umístit jako objekt v editoru Eden Editor</Czech>
        <English>a static functional aircraft carrier that can be placed as an object in Eden Editor</English>
        <Portuguese>um porta-aviões estático funcional que pode ser colocado como objeto no Eden Editor</Portuguese>
        <Korean>고정 기능 항공 모함으로 Eden Editor에서 개체로 배치될 수 있습니다.</Korean>
        <Chinesesimp>可以在伊甸编辑器中摆出做为固定物件的航空母舰</Chinesesimp>
        <Japanese>Eden Editor 内で稼働固定オブジェクトとして配置可能な航空母艦</Japanese>
      </Key>
      <Key ID="str_a3_rscdisplaywelcome_jets_pare_list6_title">
        <Original>Showcase Fighter Jets</Original>
        <Chinese>戰鬥機任務展示</Chinese>
        <French>Présentation des chasseurs</French>
        <Spanish>Exhibición Cazas</Spanish>
        <Italian>Dimostrazioni Jet da caccia</Italian>
        <Polish>Prezentacja myśliwców odrzutowych</Polish>
        <Russian>Демонстрация истребителей</Russian>
        <German>Präsentation: Kampfjets</German>
        <Czech>Ukázka Stíhací letouny</Czech>
        <English>Showcase Fighter Jets</English>
        <Portuguese>Mostruário jatos de combate</Portuguese>
        <Korean>전투기 쇼케이스</Korean>
        <Chinesesimp>战斗机任务展示</Chinesesimp>
        <Japanese>ショーケース・ジェット戦闘機</Japanese>
      </Key>
      <Key ID="str_a3_rscdisplaywelcome_jets_pare_list6">
        <Original>take to the skies over Altis and engage in Air-to-Air and Air-to-Ground operations</Original>
        <Chinese>前往Altis體驗空對空與空對地的飛行任務</Chinese>
        <French>envolez-vous au-dessus d'Altis et prenez part à des opérations air-air ou air-sol</French>
        <Spanish>Asciende a los cielos de Altis y enfréntate a operaciones aire-aire y aire-tierra.</Spanish>
        <Italian>sfreccia per i cieli di Altis e conduci operazioni di combattimento aria-aria e aria-terra</Italian>
        <Polish>wzbij się w przestworza nad Altis i weź udział w pojedynkach powietrznych oraz nalotach bombowych</Polish>
        <Russian>Покорите небеса над Алтисом и сразитесь с вражескими самолетами и средствами ПВО</Russian>
        <German>Starte in den Himmel über Altis und nimm an Luft-Luft- und Luft-Boden-Operationen teil</German>
        <Czech>vzlétněte nad Altis a zapojte se do bojových protivzdušných a protipozemních operací</Czech>
        <English>take to the skies over Altis and engage in Air-to-Air and Air-to-Ground operations</English>
        <Portuguese>domine os céus sobre Altis e participe das operações ar-ar e ar-terra</Portuguese>
        <Korean>알티스 영공으로 이동하여 공대공, 공대지 작전을 수행합니다.</Korean>
        <Chinesesimp>前往Altis体验空对空与空对地的飞行任务</Chinesesimp>
        <Japanese>アルティスの上空へと飛び出し、空中戦、そして空対地戦へと突入せよ</Japanese>
      </Key>
      <Key ID="str_a3_rscdisplaywelcome_jets_pare_list5_title">
        <Original>Deck Crew Vests</Original>
        <Chinese>甲板人員背心</Chinese>
        <French>Gilets d'officiers d'appontage</French>
        <Spanish>Chalecos de la tripulación de cabina</Spanish>
        <Italian>Gilet per l'equipaggio addetto al ponte</Italian>
        <Polish>Kamizelki załogi pokładowej</Polish>
        <Russian>Жилеты палубной команды</Russian>
        <German>Deckbesatzungs-Westen</German>
        <Czech>Vesty palubního personálu</Czech>
        <English>Deck Crew Vests</English>
        <Portuguese>Trajes da equipe da plataforma</Portuguese>
        <Korean>데크 승무원 조끼</Korean>
        <Chinesesimp>甲板人员背心</Chinesesimp>
        <Japanese>甲板要員用ベスト</Japanese>
      </Key>
      <Key ID="str_a3_rscdisplaywelcome_jets_pare_list5">
        <Original>colored vests for various character roles on the carrier</Original>
        <Chinese>數種不同顏色的背心供航空母艦的甲板人員使用</Chinese>
        <French>gilets aux couleurs des différentes unités d'appontage</French>
        <Spanish>Chalecos de colores para los diferentes miembros de la tripulación del portaaviones.</Spanish>
        <Italian>gilet colorati adatti ai vari ruoli sulla portaerei</Italian>
        <Polish>różnokolorowe kamizelki dla różnych członków załogi lotniskowca</Polish>
        <Russian>Цветные жилеты для различных персонажей на авианосце</Russian>
        <German>verschiedenfarbige Westen für unterschiedliche Rollen auf dem Träger</German>
        <Czech>barevné vesty pro posádku letadlové lodě s různými rolemi</Czech>
        <English>colored vests for various character roles on the carrier</English>
        <Portuguese>trajes coloridos para várias funções de personagens no porta-aviões</Portuguese>
        <Korean>항공 모함에서 다수의 캐릭터에 따라 구분한 색상별 조끼</Korean>
        <Chinesesimp>数种不同颜色的背心供航空母舰的甲板人员使用</Chinesesimp>
        <Japanese>空母の多様なキャラクター用の色付きベスト</Japanese>
      </Key>
      <Key ID="str_a3_rscdisplaywelcome_jets_pare_list4_title">
        <Original>Sentinel</Original>
        <Chinese>"哨兵"無人戰機</Chinese>
        <French>Sentinel</French>
        <Spanish>Sentinel</Spanish>
        <Italian>Sentinel</Italian>
        <Polish>Sentinel</Polish>
        <Russian>Sentinel</Russian>
        <German>Sentinel</German>
        <Czech>Sentinel</Czech>
        <English>Sentinel</English>
        <Portuguese>Sentinel</Portuguese>
        <Korean>Sentinel</Korean>
        <Chinesesimp>"哨兵"无人战机</Chinesesimp>
        <Japanese>センチネル</Japanese>
      </Key>
      <Key ID="str_a3_rscdisplaywelcome_jets_pare_list4">
        <Original>a NATO carrier-based Unmanned Combat Air Vehicle</Original>
        <Chinese>北約的一台艦載無人戰機</Chinese>
        <French>un drone aérien de combat de l'OTAN, destiné aux porte-avions</French>
        <Spanish>Un vehículo aéreo de combate no tripulado de la OTAN, listo para ir en el portaaviones.</Spanish>
        <Italian>aereo imbarcato tattico da combattimento privo di equipaggio NATO</Italian>
        <Polish>bojowy bezzałogowy statek powietrzny NATO dostosowany do lotniskowców</Polish>
        <Russian>Палубный беспилотный летательный аппарат НАТО</Russian>
        <German>ein unbemanntes, trägergestütztes NATO-Kampfflugzeug</German>
        <Czech>bezpilotní bojový letoun NATO se startem z letadlové lodě</Czech>
        <English>a NATO carrier-based Unmanned Combat Air Vehicle</English>
        <Portuguese>um veículo aéreo de combate não tripulado baseado em um porta-aviões da OTAN</Portuguese>
        <Korean>NATO 항공모함 기반 무인 전투 항공기</Korean>
        <Chinesesimp>北约的一台舰载无人战机</Chinesesimp>
        <Japanese>NATO 軍の空母発艦型無人戦闘航空機</Japanese>
      </Key>
      <Key ID="str_a3_rscdisplaywelcome_jets_pare_list3_title">
        <Original>A-149 Gryphon</Original>
        <Chinese>A-149"獅鷲"戰鬥機</Chinese>
        <French>A-149 Gryphon</French>
        <Spanish>A-149 Gryphon</Spanish>
        <Italian>A-149 Gryphon</Italian>
        <Polish>A-149 Gryphon</Polish>
        <Russian>A-149 Gryphon</Russian>
        <German>A-149 Gryphon</German>
        <Czech>A-149 Gryphon</Czech>
        <English>A-149 Gryphon</English>
        <Portuguese>A-149 Gryphon</Portuguese>
        <Korean>A-149 Gryphon</Korean>
        <Chinesesimp>A-149"狮鹫"战斗机</Chinesesimp>
        <Japanese>A-149 グリフォン</Japanese>
      </Key>
      <Key ID="str_a3_rscdisplaywelcome_jets_pare_list3">
        <Original>an advanced fourth generation AAF fighter jet</Original>
        <Chinese>Altis政府軍的一台先進第四代戰鬥機</Chinese>
        <French>un chasseur de combat avancé de 4e génération de l'AAF</French>
        <Spanish>Un caza AAF avanzado de cuarta generación.</Spanish>
        <Italian>jet da caccia avanzato di quarta generazione dell'AAF</Italian>
        <Polish>zaawansowany myśliwiec odrzutowy AAF 4. generacji</Polish>
        <Russian>Современный истребитель AAF четвертого поколения</Russian>
        <German>ein fortschrittlicher AAF-Kampfjet der vierten Generation</German>
        <Czech>pokročilý proudový stíhací letoun AAF čtvrté generace</Czech>
        <English>an advanced fourth generation AAF fighter jet</English>
        <Portuguese>uma caça AAF avançado da quarta geração </Portuguese>
        <Korean>최신 4세대 AAF 전투기</Korean>
        <Chinesesimp>Altis政府军的一台先进第四代战斗机</Chinesesimp>
        <Japanese>AAF 軍の先進型第四世代ジェット戦闘機</Japanese>
      </Key>
      <Key ID="str_a3_rscdisplaywelcome_jets_pare_list2_title">
        <Original>To-201 Shikra</Original>
        <Chinese>To-201"褐耳鷹"戰鬥機</Chinese>
        <French>To-201 Shikra</French>
        <Spanish>To-201 Shikra</Spanish>
        <Italian>To-201 Shikra</Italian>
        <Polish>To-201 Shikra</Polish>
        <Russian>To-201 Shikra</Russian>
        <German>To-201 Shikra</German>
        <Czech>To-201 Shikra</Czech>
        <English>To-201 Shikra</English>
        <Portuguese>To-201 Shikra</Portuguese>
        <Korean>To-201 Shikra</Korean>
        <Chinesesimp>To-201"褐耳鹰"战斗机</Chinesesimp>
        <Japanese>To-201 シクラ</Japanese>
      </Key>
      <Key ID="str_a3_rscdisplaywelcome_jets_pare_list2">
        <Original>a fifth generation CSAT air superiority fighter jet</Original>
        <Chinese>廣協同盟的一台第五代空優戰鬥機</Chinese>
        <French>un chasseur de supériorité aérienne de 5e génération du CSAT</French>
        <Spanish>Un caza de superioridad aérea del CSAT de quinta generación.</Spanish>
        <Italian>jet da caccia da superiorità aerea di quinta generazione della CSAT</Italian>
        <Polish>myśliwiec odrzutowy przewagi powietrznej CSAT 5. generacji</Polish>
        <Russian>Истребитель CSAT пятого поколения, предназначенный для завоевания господства в воздухе</Russian>
        <German>ein CSAT-Jagdflugzeug der fünften Generation</German>
        <Czech>proudový stíhací letoun vzdušné převahy CSAT páté generace</Czech>
        <English>a fifth generation CSAT air superiority fighter jet</English>
        <Portuguese>um caça de combate superior da quinta geração da CSAT </Portuguese>
        <Korean>5세대 CSAT 제공권 전투기</Korean>
        <Chinesesimp>广协同盟的一台第五代空优战斗机</Chinesesimp>
        <Japanese>CSAT 軍の第五世代ジェット制空戦闘機</Japanese>
      </Key>
      <Key ID="str_a3_rscdisplaywelcome_jets_pare_list1_title">
        <Original>F/A-181 Black Wasp II</Original>
        <Chinese>F/A-181"黑蜂"2型戰鬥攻擊機</Chinese>
        <French>F/A-181 Black Wasp II</French>
        <Spanish>F/A-181 Black Wasp II</Spanish>
        <Italian>F/A-181 Black Wasp II</Italian>
        <Polish>F/A-181 Black Wasp II</Polish>
        <Russian>F/A-181 Black Wasp II</Russian>
        <German>F/A-181 Black Wasp II</German>
        <Czech>F/A-181 Black Wasp II</Czech>
        <English>F/A-181 Black Wasp II</English>
        <Portuguese>F/A-181 Black Wasp II</Portuguese>
        <Korean>F/A-181 Black Wasp II</Korean>
        <Chinesesimp>F/A-181"黑蜂"2型战斗攻击机</Chinesesimp>
        <Japanese>F/A-181 ブラックワスプ II</Japanese>
      </Key>
      <Key ID="str_a3_rscdisplaywelcome_jets_pare_list1">
        <Original>a fifth generation NATO carrier-based fighter jet</Original>
        <Chinese>北約的一台第五代艦載戰鬥攻擊機</Chinese>
        <French>un chasseur de combat de 5e génération de l'OTAN (pour porte-avions)</French>
        <Spanish>Un caza embarcado de la OTAN de quinta generación.</Spanish>
        <Italian>jet imbarcato da caccia di quinta generazione della NATO</Italian>
        <Polish>myśliwiec odrzutowy CSAT 5. generacji dostosowany do lotniskowców</Polish>
        <Russian>Палубный истребитель НАТО пятого поколения</Russian>
        <German>ein trägergestützter NATO-Kampfjet der fünften Generation</German>
        <Czech>proudový stíhací letoun NATO páté generace se startem z letadlové lodě</Czech>
        <English>a fifth generation NATO carrier-based fighter jet</English>
        <Portuguese>um caça de combate baseado no porta-aviões da quinta geração da OTAN</Portuguese>
        <Korean>5세대 NATO 항공모함 기반 전투기</Korean>
        <Chinesesimp>北约的一台第五代舰载战斗攻击机</Chinesesimp>
        <Japanese>NATO 軍の空母発艦型第五世代ジェット戦闘機</Japanese>
      </Key>
      <Key ID="str_a3_rscdisplaywelcome_jets_pare_footer">
        <Original>You can be our wingman any time!</Original>
        <Chinese>歡迎你隨時成為我們的僚機!</Chinese>
        <French>Découvrez si vous avez l'étoffe d'un ailier !</French>
        <Spanish>¡Puedes ser nuestro copiloto siempre que quieras!</Spanish>
        <Italian>Potrai essere il nostro gregario tutte le volte che vorrai!</Italian>
        <Polish>Zawsze możesz być naszym skrzydłowym!</Polish>
        <Russian>Станьте летчиком в любое время!</Russian>
        <German>Du kannst jederzeit unser Flügelmann sein!</German>
        <Czech>Bude nám ctí být vašimi wingmany!</Czech>
        <English>You can be our wingman any time!</English>
        <Portuguese>Você pode ser o nosso ala a qualquer momento!</Portuguese>
        <Korean>언제라도 우리 조종사가 될 수 있다 !</Korean>
        <Chinesesimp>欢迎你随时成为我们的僚机!</Chinesesimp>
        <Japanese>いつでも僚機として歓迎するぞ！</Japanese>
      </Key>
      <Key ID="str_a3_rscdisplaywelcome_jets_pare">
        <Original>Arma 3 Jets takes to the skies with the following premium content and platform additions:</Original>
        <Chinese>ArmA3戰機資料片為天空帶來了以下優質付費內容:</Chinese>
        <French>Arma 3 Jets envahit le ciel avec le contenu premium et les ajouts de plateforme suivants :</French>
        <Spanish>Arma 3 Jets te lleva a lo más alto gracias a la adición del contenido premium y de las plataformas siguientes:</Spanish>
        <Italian>Arma 3 Jets prende il volo con il contenuto premium e le integrazioni alla piattaforma che seguono:</Italian>
        <Polish>Arma 3 Jets wzbija się w przestworza wraz z następującą zawartością premium i dodatkami do platformy:</Polish>
        <Russian>Arma 3 Jets покоряет небеса со следующим платным контентом и дополнениями для платформы:</Russian>
        <German>Arma 3 Jets hebt ab mit folgenden Premium-Inhalten und Plattformergänzungen:</German>
        <Czech>Rozšíření Arma 3 Jets vám díky následujícímu prémiovému obsahu a rozšíření platformy otevře nebe:</Czech>
        <English>Arma 3 Jets takes to the skies with the following premium content and platform additions:</English>
        <Portuguese>Arma 3 Jets chega ao céu com os seguintes extras e conteúdos premium:</Portuguese>
        <Korean>Arma 3 Jets에서는 다음의 프리미엄 콘텐츠와 플랫폼 추가 기능으로 비행합니다.</Korean>
        <Chinesesimp>ArmA3战机资料片为天空带来了以下优质付费内容:</Chinesesimp>
        <Japanese>Arma 3 Jets では下記のプレミアムコンテンツ、さらにプラットフォームにも新機能を追加</Japanese>
      </Key>
      <Key ID="str_a3_rscdisplaywelcome_jets_pard_unmapped">
        <Original>Unmapped</Original>
        <Chinese>未對應</Chinese>
        <French>Non assigné</French>
        <Spanish>Sin mapear</Spanish>
        <Italian>Non configurati</Italian>
        <Polish>Niezamapowany</Polish>
        <Russian>Не нанесено на карту</Russian>
        <German>Nicht belegt</German>
        <Czech>Nepřiřazeno</Czech>
        <English>Unmapped</English>
        <Portuguese>Não mapeado</Portuguese>
        <Korean>매핑 안됨</Korean>
        <Chinesesimp>未对应</Chinesesimp>
        <Japanese>マッピングなし</Japanese>
      </Key>
      <Key ID="str_a3_rscdisplaywelcome_jets_pard_title">
        <Original>CONTROLS_</Original>
        <Chinese>按鍵設定</Chinese>
        <French>COMMANDES_</French>
        <Spanish>CONTROLES_</Spanish>
        <Italian>CONTROLLI_</Italian>
        <Polish>STEROWANIE_</Polish>
        <Russian>УПРАВЛЕНИЕ_</Russian>
        <German>STEUERUNG_</German>
        <Czech>OVLÁDÁNÍ_</Czech>
        <English>CONTROLS_</English>
        <Portuguese>CONTROLES_</Portuguese>
        <Korean>제어_</Korean>
        <Chinesesimp>按键设定</Chinesesimp>
        <Japanese>操作_</Japanese>
      </Key>
      <Key ID="str_a3_rscdisplaywelcome_jets_pard_list7_title">
        <Original>Vectoring</Original>
        <Chinese>向量噴嘴</Chinese>
        <French>Angle vectoriel</French>
        <Spanish>Empuje vectorial</Spanish>
        <Italian>Spinta vettoriale</Italian>
        <Polish>Wektorowanie</Polish>
        <Russian>Вектор тяги</Russian>
        <German>Vektorierung</German>
        <Czech>Vektorování</Czech>
        <English>Vectoring</English>
        <Portuguese>Vetorização</Portuguese>
        <Korean>벡터링</Korean>
        <Chinesesimp>向量喷嘴</Chinesesimp>
        <Japanese>ベクタリング</Japanese>
      </Key>
      <Key ID="str_a3_rscdisplaywelcome_jets_pard_list7">
        <Original>%1 and %2 (same as for flaps) now control the VTOL vectoring angle in manual mode</Original>
        <Chinese>%1與%2(同控制襟翼)現在能在手動模式下控制垂直起降機的向量噴嘴角度</Chinese>
        <French>%1 et %2 (identique aux volets) contrôlent l'angle de poussée vectorielle de l'ADAV en mode manuel</French>
        <Spanish>%1 y %2 (igual que para los alerones) ahora controlan el ángulo de empuje vectorial en el modo manual.</Spanish>
        <Italian>%1 e %2 (lo stesso vale per i flap) consentono ora di controllare l'angolo vettoriale del velivolo a decollo e atterraggio verticale in modalità manuale</Italian>
        <Polish>%1 i %2 (wspólne z klapami) odpowiadają teraz za kąt wektorowania VTOL-a w trybie ręcznym</Polish>
        <Russian>%1 и %2 (аналогично для закрылок) теперь управляют вектором тяги СВВП в ручном режиме</Russian>
        <German>%1 und %2 (wie bei den Landeklappen) steuern jetzt den Vektorierungswinkel des VTOLs im manuellen Modus</German>
        <Czech>%1 a %2 (stejně jako pro klapky) nyní ovládají úhel vektorování letounu VTOL v ručním režimu</Czech>
        <English>%1 and %2 (same as for flaps) now control the VTOL vectoring angle in manual mode</English>
        <Portuguese>%1 e %2 (o mesmo para os flaps) agora controlam o ângulo de vetorização VTOL no modo manual</Portuguese>
        <Korean>%1 및 %2 (플랩에도 마찬가지)(은)는 이제 수동 모드에서 VTOL 벡터링 각도를 제어합니다</Korean>
        <Chinesesimp>%1与%2(同控制襟翼)现在能在手动模式下控制垂直起降机的向量喷嘴角度</Chinesesimp>
        <Japanese>%1 と %2（フラップと同様）は手動モードでの VTOL ベクタリング角の調節に使用されます</Japanese>
      </Key>
      <Key ID="str_a3_rscdisplaywelcome_jets_pard_list6_title">
        <Original>Speedbrake</Original>
        <Chinese>減速板</Chinese>
        <French>Aérofrein</French>
        <Spanish>Aerofrenos</Spanish>
        <Italian>Aerofreno</Italian>
        <Polish>Hamulec aerodynamiczny</Polish>
        <Russian>Гаситель скорости</Russian>
        <German>Luftbremse</German>
        <Czech>Rychlostní brzda</Czech>
        <English>Speedbrake</English>
        <Portuguese>Freio aerodinâmico</Portuguese>
        <Korean>속도 제어기</Korean>
        <Chinesesimp>减速板</Chinesesimp>
        <Japanese>スピードブレーキ</Japanese>
      </Key>
      <Key ID="str_a3_rscdisplaywelcome_jets_pard_list6">
        <Original>%1 deploys available air brakes (this was decoupled from throttling)</Original>
        <Chinese>按下%1來展開減速板(這功能與油門分開了)</Chinese>
        <French>%1 déploie l'aérofrein (à présent découplé du régime moteur)</French>
        <Spanish>%1 despliega los aerofrenos disponibles (esto era independiente a la aceleración).</Spanish>
        <Italian>%1 consente di usare gli aerofreni disponibili (disaccoppiato dalla spinta di propulsione)</Italian>
        <Polish>%1 uruchamia dostępne hamulce aerodynamiczne (oddzielnie od regulacji ciągu)</Polish>
        <Russian>%1 включает доступные воздушные тормоза (сделано отдельно от контролирования газа)</Russian>
        <German>%1 aktiviert verfügbare Luftbremsen (dies wurde von der Beschleunigung getrennt)</German>
        <Czech>%1 použije dostupné vzduchové brzdy (spojení s ovládáním plynu bylo zrušeno)</Czech>
        <English>%1 deploys available air brakes (this was decoupled from throttling)</English>
        <Portuguese>%1 libera os freios aerodinâmicos disponíveis (ação desacoplada da aceleração)</Portuguese>
        <Korean>%1는 이용 가능한 에어 브레이크를 배치합니다(스로틀에서 분리됨)</Korean>
        <Chinesesimp>按下%1来展开减速板(这功能与油门分开了)</Chinesesimp>
        <Japanese>%1 は使用可能なエアブレーキを展開します（スロットルとは別になりました）</Japanese>
      </Key>
      <Key ID="str_a3_rscdisplaywelcome_jets_pard_list5_title">
        <Original>Lase Range</Original>
        <Chinese>雷射測量距離</Chinese>
        <French>Portée laser</French>
        <Spanish>Alcance del láser</Spanish>
        <Italian>Portata del laser</Italian>
        <Polish>Dalmierz laserowy</Polish>
        <Russian>Расстояние до цели</Russian>
        <German>Laserreichweite</German>
        <Czech>Laserový dálkoměr</Czech>
        <English>Lase Range</English>
        <Portuguese>Alcance do laser</Portuguese>
        <Korean>요격 거리</Korean>
        <Chinesesimp>雷射测量距离</Chinesesimp>
        <Japanese>レーザー照射距離</Japanese>
      </Key>
      <Key ID="str_a3_rscdisplaywelcome_jets_pard_list5">
        <Original>%1 was previously used for auto elevation, but now also controls range measuring and weapon Fire Control Systems</Original>
        <Chinese>%1之前被用來自動調整武器仰角, 但現在也被用來距離量測以及火控系統等操作</Chinese>
        <French>%1 servait uniquement au niveau auto, mais permet maintenant de contrôler la mesure de portée et les systèmes de contrôle du tir</French>
        <Spanish>%1 solo se usaba para la elevación automática, pero ahora también controla la medición del alcance y los sistemas de control de disparo.</Spanish>
        <Italian>%1 veniva utilizzato in precedenza per l'altitudine automatica, ma ora consente di controllare anche la misurazione della portata e i sistemi di controllo di tiro delle armi</Italian>
        <Polish>%1 (poprzednio autom. regulacja kąta podniesienia) odpowiada od teraz również za pomiar zasięgu i systemy kierowania ogniem</Polish>
        <Russian>%1 ранее использовался для автоматического набора высоты, но теперь также управляет измерением дальности и системами управления огнем</Russian>
        <German>%1 wurde bisher für das automatische Höhenruder verwendet, kontrolliert jetzt allerdings auch Reichweitenmessung und die Feuerkontrollsysteme der Waffen</German>
        <Czech>%1 předtím sloužilo k automatickému udržování letové hladiny, nyní také umožňuje ovládat měření vzdálenosti a zbraňové palebné systémy.</Czech>
        <English>%1 was previously used for auto elevation, but now also controls range measuring and weapon Fire Control Systems</English>
        <Portuguese>%1 foi usado anteriormente para elevação automática, mas agora também controla a medição de alcance e os sistemas de controle de disparo</Portuguese>
        <Korean>%1는 이전에 자동 고각에 사용되었지만 이제 거리 측정 및 화기 관제 시스템을 제어합니다.</Korean>
        <Chinesesimp>%1之前被用来自动调整武器仰角, 但现在也被用来距离量测以及火控系统等操作</Chinesesimp>
        <Japanese>%1 はこれまで自動仰角に使用されましたが、現在は距離測定と武装の火器管制システムの制御にも使われるようになりました。</Japanese>
      </Key>
      <Key ID="str_a3_rscdisplaywelcome_jets_pard_list4_title">
        <Original>Radar</Original>
        <Chinese>雷達</Chinese>
        <French>Radar</French>
        <Spanish>Radar</Spanish>
        <Italian>Radar</Italian>
        <Polish>Radar</Polish>
        <Russian>РЛС</Russian>
        <German>Radar</German>
        <Czech>Radar</Czech>
        <English>Radar</English>
        <Portuguese>Radar</Portuguese>
        <Korean>레이더</Korean>
        <Chinesesimp>雷达</Chinesesimp>
        <Japanese>レーダー</Japanese>
      </Key>
      <Key ID="str_a3_rscdisplaywelcome_jets_pard_list4">
        <Original>%1 switches any available active radar on or off (an active radar can also reveal your position to more threats)</Original>
        <Chinese>%1可用來開啟或關閉雷達(開啟中的雷達有可能會暴露出你的位置給敵人)</Chinese>
        <French>%1 active ou désactive le radar actif (un radar actif risque de révéler votre position à d'autres ennemis)</French>
        <Spanish>%1 alterna entre los radares disponibles y los activa o los desactiva (un radar activo también puede hacerte más vulnerable a otras amenazas).</Spanish>
        <Italian>%1 consente di attivare o disattivare qualsiasi radar attivo (un radar attivo può anche rivelare la tua posizione a più minacce nemiche)</Italian>
        <Polish>%1 włącza i wyłącza radar (radar aktywny zdradza jednocześnie przeciwnikowi twoje położenie)</Polish>
        <Russian>%1 включает или выключает любую активную РЛС (активная РЛС может раскрыть вашу позицию врагам)</Russian>
        <German>%1 schaltet jedes verfügbare Radar ein oder aus (ein aktives Radar kann deine Position preisgeben)</German>
        <Czech>%1 zapne nebo vypne jakýkoliv dostupný radar (aktivní radar může také prozradit vaši polohu dalším hrozbám)</Czech>
        <English>%1 switches any available active radar on or off (an active radar can also reveal your position to more threats)</English>
        <Portuguese>%1 liga ou desliga qualquer radar disponível ativo (com o radar ativo, sua posição também pode ser revelada para mais inimigos)</Portuguese>
        <Korean>%1는 이용 가능한 활성 레이더를 설정 또는 해제로 전환합니다(활성 레이더는 사용자 위치를 노출하여 많은 위협이 발생할 수 있습니다)</Korean>
        <Chinesesimp>%1可用来开启或关闭雷达(开启中的雷达有可能会暴露出你的位置给敌人)</Chinesesimp>
        <Japanese>%1 で利用可能なあらゆるアクティブレーダーをオンまたはオフにします（アクティブレーダーはより多くの脅威に自身の位置を知られやすくなります）</Japanese>
      </Key>
      <Key ID="str_a3_rscdisplaywelcome_jets_pard_list3_title">
        <Original>Info Panel Miscellaneous</Original>
        <Chinese>多功能面板額外說明</Chinese>
        <French>Panneau d'information - Divers</French>
        <Spanish>Panel de información variada</Spanish>
        <Italian>Info pannello varie</Italian>
        <Polish>Panel informacyjny (różne)</Polish>
        <Russian>Информационная панель с различными данными</Russian>
        <German>Infopanel – Sonstiges</German>
        <Czech>Informační panel – různé</Czech>
        <English>Info Panel Miscellaneous</English>
        <Portuguese>Painel de informações diversas</Portuguese>
        <Korean>기타 정보 패널</Korean>
        <Chinesesimp>多功能面板额外说明</Chinesesimp>
        <Japanese>情報パネル・その他</Japanese>
      </Key>
      <Key ID="str_a3_rscdisplaywelcome_jets_pard_list3">
        <Original>there exist controls to switch to the previous info panel module or to close them directly, but these are not mapped by default</Original>
        <Chinese>在按鍵設定中有可以切換到上一個多功能面板與直接關閉多功能面板的按鍵設定, 但在預設的按鍵設定上並沒有綁定按鍵</Chinese>
        <French>des commandes ont été créées pour passer au module de panneau d'information précédent ou le fermer directement, mais aucune touche n'est assignée par défaut.</French>
        <Spanish>Hay controles para alternar entre el módulo del panel de información anterior o para cerrarlo directamente, pero no están mapeados por defecto.</Spanish>
        <Italian>qui puoi trovare i controlli che consentono di passare al modulo del pannello informazioni precedente o di chiuderli direttamente, ma non sono configurati per impostazione predefinita </Italian>
        <Polish>dodano klawisze odpowiadające za przełączanie do poprzedniego modułu lub jego zamknięcie (nieprzypisane domyślnie)</Polish>
        <Russian>У вас есть возможность переключиться на предыдущий модуль информационной панели или закрыть их напрямую, однако это не отображается по умолчанию</Russian>
        <German>es gibt die Möglichkeit, auf das vorherige Infopanel zu wechseln, oder es direkt zu schließen, aber diese Tasten sind standardmäßig nicht belegt.</German>
        <Czech>k dispozici jsou ovládací prvky umožňující přímo přepnout na předchozí modul informačního panelu nebo ho zavřít, toto ovládání však není ve výchozím nastavení přiřazeno</Czech>
        <English>there exist controls to switch to the previous info panel module or to close them directly, but these are not mapped by default</English>
        <Portuguese>exibe os controles para alternar para o módulo do painel de informações anterior ou para fechá-los diretamente, mas o padrão é que não sejam mapeados</Portuguese>
        <Korean>이전 정보 패널 모듈로 전환하는 제어 기능 또는 이 제어 기능을 직접 종료하는 제어 기능이 있으며, 기본적으로 매핑되지 않았습니다.</Korean>
        <Chinesesimp>在按键设定中有可以切换到上一个多功能面板与直接关闭多功能面板的按键设定, 但在预设的按键设定上并没有绑定按键</Chinesesimp>
        <Japanese>前の情報パネルモジュールへ切り替えたり、モジュールを直接閉じたりする操作方法もありますが、これらはデフォルトではマッピングされていません</Japanese>
      </Key>
      <Key ID="str_a3_rscdisplaywelcome_jets_pard_list2_title">
        <Original>Info Panel Mode</Original>
        <Chinese>多功能面板模式</Chinese>
        <French>Mode de panneau d'information</French>
        <Spanish>Modo del panel de información</Spanish>
        <Italian>Info modalità pannello</Italian>
        <Polish>Tryb panelu informacyjnego</Polish>
        <Russian>Режим информационной панели</Russian>
        <German>Infopanelmodus</German>
        <Czech>Režim informačního panelu</Czech>
        <English>Info Panel Mode</English>
        <Portuguese>Modo “Painel de informações”</Portuguese>
        <Korean>정보 패널 모드</Korean>
        <Chinesesimp>多功能面板模式</Chinesesimp>
        <Japanese>情報パネルモード</Japanese>
      </Key>
      <Key ID="str_a3_rscdisplaywelcome_jets_pard_list2">
        <Original>%1 or %2 switch the mode of the left or right info panels where available (e.g. zoom)</Original>
        <Chinese>%1或%2可以來切換左右多功能面板的不同模式(像是改變雷達搜索距離)</Chinese>
        <French>%1 et %2 changent le mode des panneaux d'information droite et gauche, si disponible (ex. : zoom)</French>
        <Spanish>%1 o %2 cambia el modo de los paneles de información de la izquierda y de la derecha (como el zoom).</Spanish>
        <Italian>%1 o %2 consente di cambiare la modalità del pannello informativo destro o sinistro laddove disponibile (es. zoom)</Italian>
        <Polish>%1 lub %2 zmienia tryb lewego lub prawego panelu w możliwych przypadkach (np. powiększenie)</Polish>
        <Russian>%1 или %2 переключают режим левой или правой информационных панелей, если он доступен (например, масштабирование)</Russian>
        <German>%1 oder %2 wechseln den Modus des linken oder rechten Infopanels, sofern verfügbar (z. B. Zoom)</German>
        <Czech>%1 nebo %2 umožňuje přepínat režim levého nebo pravého informačního panelu, je-li k dispozici (např. přiblížení)</Czech>
        <English>%1 or %2 switch the mode of the left or right info panels where available (e.g. zoom)</English>
        <Portuguese>%1 ou %2 alternam o modo dos painéis de informação esquerdo ou direito quando disponíveis (por exemplo, o zoom)</Portuguese>
        <Korean>%1 또는 %2는 가능한 경우 좌측 또는 우측 정보 패널의 모드를 전환합니다.(예, 확대/축소)</Korean>
        <Chinesesimp>%1或%2可以来切换左右多功能面板的不同模式(像是改变雷达搜索距离)</Chinesesimp>
        <Japanese>%1 および %2 は左もしくは右の情報パネルを使用可能なモードに切り替えます（ズームなど）</Japanese>
      </Key>
      <Key ID="str_a3_rscdisplaywelcome_jets_pard_list1_title">
        <Original>Info Panel Module</Original>
        <Chinese>多功能面板類型</Chinese>
        <French>Module de panneau d'information</French>
        <Spanish>Módulo del panel de información</Spanish>
        <Italian>Info modulo pannello</Italian>
        <Polish>Moduł panelu informacyjnego</Polish>
        <Russian>Модуль информационной панели</Russian>
        <German>Infopanel-Module</German>
        <Czech>Modul informačního panelu</Czech>
        <English>Info Panel Module</English>
        <Portuguese>Módulo “Painel de informações”</Portuguese>
        <Korean>정보 패널 모드</Korean>
        <Chinesesimp>多功能面板类型</Chinesesimp>
        <Japanese>情報パネルモジュール</Japanese>
      </Key>
      <Key ID="str_a3_rscdisplaywelcome_jets_pard_list1">
        <Original>%3 or %4 switch the left or right &lt;a href='%2' color='%1'&gt;info panels&lt;/a&gt; to the next module where available (GPS, radar, off, etc.)</Original>
        <Chinese>%3或%4可以來切換左右多功能面板&lt;a href='%2' color='%1'&gt;info panels&lt;/a&gt;到下一個可用的類型(GPS, 雷達, 關閉等等...)</Chinese>
        <French>%3 et %4 font passer les &lt;a href='%2' color='%1'&gt;panneaux d'information&lt;/a&gt; gauche et droite au module suivant disponible (GPS, radar, désactivé, etc.)</French>
        <Spanish>%3 o %4 cambia los &lt;a href='%2' color='%1'&gt;paneles de información&lt;/a&gt; izquierdo y derecho para mostrar el siguiente módulo disponible (GPS, radar, desactivado, etc.)</Spanish>
        <Italian>%3 o %4 consente di passare dai &lt;a href='%2' color='%1'&gt;pannelli informativi&lt;/a&gt; destro o sinistro al modulo successivo, laddove disponibile (GPS, radar, disattivo, ecc.)</Italian>
        <Polish>klawisz %3 lub %4 przełącza lewy lub prawy &lt;a href='%2' color='%1'&gt;panel informacyjny&lt;/a&gt; na następny moduł, o ile to możliwe (GPS, radar, wył. itd.)</Polish>
        <Russian>%3 или %4 переключают левую или правую &lt;a href='%2' color='%1'&gt;информационные панели&lt;/a&gt; на следующий модуль, если он доступен (GPS, РЛС, выкл. и т.д.)</Russian>
        <German>%3 oder %4 wechseln im linken oder rechten &lt;a href='%2' color='%1'&gt;Infopanel&lt;/a&gt; zum nächsten Modul, sofern verfügbar (GPS, Radar, aus etc.)</German>
        <Czech>%3 nebo %4 umožňuje přepínat levý nebo pravý &lt;a href='%2' color='%1'&gt;informační panel&lt;/a&gt; na následující modul, pokud je k dispozici (GPS, radar, vyp. atd.)</Czech>
        <English>%3 or %4 switch the left or right &lt;a href='%2' color='%1'&gt;info panels&lt;/a&gt; to the next module where available (GPS, radar, off, etc.)</English>
        <Portuguese>%3 ou %4 alternam entre os &lt;a href='%2'color='%1'&gt;painéis de informação&lt;/a&gt; da esquerda ou da direita para o próximo módulo quando disponível (GPS, radar, desligado, etc.)</Portuguese>
        <Korean>%3 또는 %4는 가능한 경우 좌측 또는 우측 &lt;a href='%2' color='%1'&gt;정보 패널&lt;/a&gt;을 다음 모듈로(GPS, 레이더, 종료 등)으로 전환합니다(예, 확대/축소)</Korean>
        <Chinesesimp>%3或%4可以来切换左右多功能面板&lt;a href='%2' color='%1'&gt;info panels&lt;/a&gt;到下一个可用的类型(GPS, 雷达, 关闭等等...)</Chinesesimp>
        <Japanese>%3 および %4 は左もしくは右の&lt;a href='%2' color='%1'&gt;情報パネル&lt;/a&gt;を使用可能な次のモジュールに切り替えます（GPS、レーダー、オフなど）</Japanese>
      </Key>
      <Key ID="str_a3_rscdisplaywelcome_jets_pard">
        <Original>With the addition of these new features and deepening of existing gameplay, there have been several &lt;t color='%1'&gt;control additions and tweaks&lt;/t&gt;. You can inspect these in the CONTROLS section of the OPTIONS menu. It's also possible to reset to the Arma 3 or now standard Arma 3 Apex PRESETS, but please be aware that doing so will remove any customized control bindings.</Original>
        <Chinese>隨著新功能的登場與更加細緻的遊戲體驗, 我們&lt;t color='%1'&gt;新增與調整了一些控制按鍵&lt;/t&gt;. 你可以到選項中的按鍵設定進行調整. 你也可以直接重設按鍵設定到標準的ArmA3頂尖按鍵配置, 但如果這樣做, 你的那些自定按鍵就會全部不見.</Chinese>
        <French>Outre l'ajout de ces fonctionnalités et l'approfondissement du gameplay existant, certaines &lt;t color='%1'&gt;commandes ont été ajoutées ou modifiées&lt;/t&gt;. Vous pouvez les consulter dans la section COMMANDES du menu OPTIONS. Vous pouvez également réinitialiser les PRÉSÉLECTIONS Arma 3 ou Arma 3 Apex (défaut), mais sachez que cela supprimera les assignations de commandes personnalisées.</French>
        <Spanish>Con la adición de estas nuevas funciones, que hará que la jugabilidad sea más intensa, se han &lt;t color='%1'&gt;añadido varios controles y se han mejorado otros&lt;/t&gt;. Puedes verlos en la sección de CONTROLES del menú de OPCIONES. También es posible restablecer los ajustes preseleccionados de Arma 3 o Arma 3 Apex, pero ten en cuenta que, si haces eso, eliminarás las asignaciones de control personalizadas.</Spanish>
        <Italian>Grazie alla presenza di queste nuove funzionalità e all'approfondimento dell'esistente modalità di gioco sono state apportate svariate &lt;t color='%1'&gt;integrazioni e modifiche ai controlli&lt;/t&gt; che puoi verificare nella sezione CONTROLLI del menu OPZIONI. Puoi inoltre reimpostare i PRESET di Arma 3 o quelli predefiniti di Arma 3 Apex, ma tieni a mente che così facendo rimuoverai tutte le associazioni personalizzate dei controlli.</Italian>
        <Polish>Oprócz dodania nowych funkcji oraz rozbudowania możliwości gry wprowadziliśmy też kilka &lt;t color='%1'&gt;dodatkowych rozwiązań i poprawek do sterowania&lt;/t&gt;. Można się z nimi zapoznać w sekcji STEROWANIE z poziomu menu OPCJE. Można również przywrócić DOMYŚLNE ustawienia sterowania dla Arma 3 lub standardowego Arma 3 Apex, ale usunie to przypisanie klawiszy użytkownika.</Polish>
        <Russian>С добавлением этих новых функций и углублением существующего игрового процесса мы внесли несколько &lt;t color='%1'&gt;изменений в управление&lt;/t&gt;. Вы можете изучить все изменения в разделе УПРАВЛЕНИЕ в меню НАСТРОЙКИ. Вы также можете использовать стандартную раскладку Arma 3 или Arma 3 Apex, однако при этом вы потеряете любые пользовательские настройки.</Russian>
        <German>Mit der Implementierung dieser neuen Features haben wir nicht nur das Gameplay verbessert, sondern auch ein paar &lt;t color='%1'&gt;Verbesserungen an der Steuerung&lt;/t&gt; vorgenommen. Du kannst diese unter OPTIONEN im Abschnitt STEUERUNG einsehen. Du kannst deine Steuerung auch auf die VOREINSTELLUNGEN von Arma 3 oder Arma 3 Apex zurücksetzen, aber dadurch gehen alle personalisierten Tastenbelegungen verloren. </German>
        <Czech>Kromě těchto nových funkcí a prohloubení stávající hratelnosti jsme přidali několik &lt;t color='%1'&gt;doplňků a úprav ovládání&lt;/t&gt;. Tyto nové prvky naleznete v nabídce MOŽNOSTI v části OVLÁDÁNÍ. Také můžete resetovat ovládání na PŘEDVOLENÉ NASTAVENÍ hry Arma 3 nebo nyní standardní nastavení Arma 3 Apex – nezapomeňte však, že tím zrušíte všechna vlastní přiřazení ovládání.</Czech>
        <English>With the addition of these new features and deepening of existing gameplay, there have been several &lt;t color='%1'&gt;control additions and tweaks&lt;/t&gt;. You can inspect these in the CONTROLS section of the OPTIONS menu. It's also possible to reset to the Arma 3 or now standard Arma 3 Apex PRESETS, but please be aware that doing so will remove any customized control bindings.</English>
        <Portuguese>Com a adição destes novos recursos e o aprofundamento da jogabilidade existente, fizemos várias &lt;t color='%1'&gt;adições e ajustes de controle&lt;/ t&gt;. Você pode conferir na seção CONTROLES do menu de OPÇÕES. Também é possível usar as PREDEFINIÇÕES do Arma 3 ou do Arma 3 Apex (que agora é padrão), mas não esqueça que, ao fazer isso você, você estará removendo todas as configurações de controle personalizadas.</Portuguese>
        <Korean>새 기능을 추가하고 기존의 게임플레이를 심화함에 따라 &lt;t color='%1'&gt;제어에 추가 사항과 조정 사항이 포함되었습니다&lt;/t&gt;. 이 변경 사항은 선택 메뉴의 제어 섹션에서 확인할 수 있습니다. Arma 3 또는 현재 Arma 3 Apex의 기본 사전설정으로 재설정할 수 있게 되었습니다. 단, 이렇게 하면 모든 사용자 정의 제어 바인딩이 제거되므로 주의하십시오.</Korean>
        <Chinesesimp>随着新功能的登场与更加细致的游戏体验, 我们&lt;t color='%1'&gt;新增与调整了一些控制按键&lt;/t&gt;. 你可以到选项中的按键设定进行调整. 你也可以直接重设按键设定到标准的ArmA3顶尖按键配置, 但如果这样做, 你的那些自定按键就会全部不见.</Chinesesimp>
        <Japanese>これら新機能の実装や既存のゲームプレイの拡張に加え、複数の&lt;t color='%1'&gt;操作系への追加や調整&lt;/t&gt;が行われました。これらは「オプション」メニューの「コントロール」セクションで確認できます。また Arma 3 および標準となった Arma 3 Apex プリセットにリセットすることも可能です。但し、カスタマイズしたコントロールバインドは全てリセットされますのでご注意ください。</Japanese>
      </Key>
      <Key ID="str_a3_rscdisplaywelcome_jets_parc_list8">
        <Original>optional new throttle behavior, new airplane animation and &lt;a href='%2' color='%1'&gt;MFD&lt;/a&gt; sources for modders, tweaked controls, and more!</Original>
        <Chinese>可選的新式油門操作, 新的飛機動作, &lt;a href='%2' color='%1'&gt;多功能顯示螢幕&lt;/a&gt;與更加擬真的操作等等!</Chinese>
        <French>Commande régime moteur modifiée et optionnelle, sources des &lt;a href='%2' color='%1'&gt;affichages multifonctions&lt;/a&gt; et des animations d'avion pour les modders, et plus encore !</French>
        <Spanish>Nuevo comportamiento de aceleración opcional, nueva animación de aviones, fuentes de &lt;a href='%2' color='%1'&gt;pantallas multifunción&lt;/a&gt; para modders, controles mejorados y mucho más</Spanish>
        <Italian>nuovo comportamento della spinta opzionale, nuova animazione dell'aeroplano, sorgenti &lt;a href='%2' color='%1'&gt;MFD&lt;/a&gt; per modder, controlli modificati, e tanto altro!</Italian>
        <Polish>nowe opcjonalne zachowanie ciągów, nowa animacja samolotów, źródła &lt;a href='%2' color='%1'&gt;MDF&lt;/a&gt; dla twórców modów, udoskonalone sterowanie i wiele innych!</Polish>
        <Russian>Дополнительное новое поведение дроссельной заслонки, новая анимация самолета и источники &lt;a href='%2' color='%1'&gt;многофункционального дисплея&lt;/a&gt; для моддеров, улучшенные элементы управления и многое другое!</Russian>
        <German>optionales Beschleunigungsverhalten, neue Flugzeuganimationen, &lt;a href='%2' color='%1'&gt;MFD&lt;/a&gt;-Ressourcen für Modder, eine verbesserte Steuerung und vieles mehr!</German>
        <Czech>nové volitelné chování plynu, nová animace letadel a &lt;a href='%2' color='%1'&gt;MFD&lt;/a&gt; zdroje pro autory modů, upravené ovládání a mnoho dalšího!</Czech>
        <English>optional new throttle behavior, new airplane animation and &lt;a href='%2' color='%1'&gt;MFD&lt;/a&gt; sources for modders, tweaked controls, and more!</English>
        <Portuguese>novo comportamento opcional do acelerador, nova animação de avião e fontes &lt;a href='%2'color='%1'&gt;MFD&lt;/a&gt; para modders, ajustes de controles e muito mais!</Portuguese>
        <Korean>신규 스로틀 태세 옵션, 신규 비행기 애니메이션, 모더를 위한 &lt;a href='%2' color='%1'&gt;MFD&lt;/a&gt; 소스, 변경된 제어 기능 등 많은 새기능이 있습니다!</Korean>
        <Chinesesimp>可选的新式油门操作, 新的飞机动作, &lt;a href='%2' color='%1'&gt;多功能显示荧幕&lt;/a&gt;与更加拟真的操作等等!</Chinesesimp>
        <Japanese>任意で設定可能な新しいスロットル挙動、MOD 作成用の新しい航空機アニメーションおよび&lt;a href='%2' color='%1'&gt;MFD&lt;/a&gt;ソース、調整された操作などなど！</Japanese>
      </Key>
      <Key ID="str_a3_rscdisplaywelcome_jets_parc_list7_title">
        <Original>Ejection Seats</Original>
        <Chinese>彈射椅</Chinese>
        <French>Sièges éjectables</French>
        <Spanish>Asientos eyectables</Spanish>
        <Italian>Seggiolini eiettabili</Italian>
        <Polish>Fotele katapultowe</Polish>
        <Russian>Катапультируемые кресла</Russian>
        <German>Schleudersitze</German>
        <Czech>Vystřelovací sedadla</Czech>
        <English>Ejection Seats</English>
        <Portuguese>Assentos de ejeção</Portuguese>
        <Korean>비상탈출 좌석</Korean>
        <Chinesesimp>弹射椅</Chinesesimp>
        <Japanese>射出座席</Japanese>
      </Key>
      <Key ID="str_a3_rscdisplaywelcome_jets_parc_list7">
        <Original>a more appropriate scripted emergency bail-out procedure for airplanes</Original>
        <Chinese>更加擬真的飛機緊急逃生裝置</Chinese>
        <French>une procédure d'éjection des avions mieux scriptée</French>
        <Spanish>Un procedimiento de huida de emergencia preparado y más apropiado para los aviones</Spanish>
        <Italian>una procedura protocollata più opportuna riguardante il lancio d'emergenza negli aeroplani</Italian>
        <Polish>poprawiona oskryptowana procedura awaryjnej ewakuacji dla samolotów</Polish>
        <Russian>Более подходящий сценарий эвакуации для экипажа самолетов</Russian>
        <German>eine bessere geskriptete Notfall-Absprungprozedur für Flugzeuge</German>
        <Czech>vhodnější naskriptovaný postup nouzového opuštění letadla</Czech>
        <English>a more appropriate scripted emergency bail-out procedure for airplanes</English>
        <Portuguese>um procedimento de ejeção de emergência com scripts mais apropriado para aviões</Portuguese>
        <Korean>비행기용 응급 구제 절차가 개선되었습니다.</Korean>
        <Chinesesimp>更加拟真的飞机紧急逃生装置</Chinesesimp>
        <Japanese>航空機における緊急脱出手順にさらに適切なスクリプトを適用</Japanese>
      </Key>
      <Key ID="str_a3_rscdisplaywelcome_jets_parc_list6_title">
        <Original>Carrier Ops</Original>
        <Chinese>航空母艦作業</Chinese>
        <French>Opérations sur porte-avions</French>
        <Spanish>Operaciones de portaaviones</Spanish>
        <Italian>Operazioni di trasporto</Italian>
        <Polish>Lotniskowce</Polish>
        <Russian>Эксплуатация с авианосцев</Russian>
        <German>Träger-Operationen</German>
        <Czech>Operace na letadlové lodi</Czech>
        <English>Carrier Ops</English>
        <Portuguese>Porta-aviões</Portuguese>
        <Korean>항공모함 작전</Korean>
        <Chinesesimp>航空母舰作业</Chinesesimp>
        <Japanese>空母オプス</Japanese>
      </Key>
      <Key ID="str_a3_rscdisplaywelcome_jets_parc_list6">
        <Original>scripted support for carrier launching and automated landing of naval aircraft</Original>
        <Chinese>現在你擁有一台可以透過腳本來彈射與自動降落的航空母艦</Chinese>
        <French>assistance scriptée pour le décollage et l'appontage automatisés sur porte-avions</French>
        <Spanish>Apoyo preparado para el lanzamiento desde portaaviones y el aterrizaje automatizado de aeronaves navales</Spanish>
        <Italian>supporto protocollato per il lancio dalla portaerei e per l'atterraggio automatizzato del velivolo imbarcato</Italian>
        <Polish>oskryptowane wsparcie startowania z lotniskowców oraz automatycznego lądowania statków powietrznych marynarki</Polish>
        <Russian>Заскриптованная поддержка для запуска с авианосца, а также автоматизированная посадка самолетов авиации ВМС</Russian>
        <German>geskriptete Unterstützung für den Startvorgang auf Flugzeugträgern und automatisiertes Landen von Marineflugzeugen</German>
        <Czech>naskriptovaná podpora startu námořních letadel a jejich automatické přistávání na letadlové lodi</Czech>
        <English>scripted support for carrier launching and automated landing of naval aircraft</English>
        <Portuguese>suporte baseado em scripts para lançamento a partir do porta-aviões e aterrissagem automatizada de aeronaves navais</Portuguese>
        <Korean>항공 모함 런칭, 해군 항공기 자동 착륙에 대한 스크립트 처리된 지원.</Korean>
        <Chinesesimp>现在你拥有一台可以透过脚本来弹射与自动降落的航空母舰</Chinesesimp>
        <Japanese>海上航空機の空母発艦および自動着艦のスクリプトでサポート</Japanese>
      </Key>
      <Key ID="str_a3_rscdisplaywelcome_jets_parc_list5_title">
        <Original>Improved Airplane Audio</Original>
        <Chinese>改進飛機的音效</Chinese>
        <French>Amélioration des sons des avions</French>
        <Spanish>Audio de los aviones mejorado</Spanish>
        <Italian>Audio aeroplano migliorato</Italian>
        <Polish>Poprawiony dźwięk samolotu</Polish>
        <Russian>Улучшение звука самолета</Russian>
        <German>Verbesserte Flugzeuggeräusche</German>
        <Czech>Vylepšené zvuky letadel</Czech>
        <English>Improved Airplane Audio</English>
        <Portuguese>Áudio de aeronave melhorado</Portuguese>
        <Korean>강화된 비행기 오디오</Korean>
        <Chinesesimp>改进飞机的音效</Chinesesimp>
        <Japanese>航空機関係の音響を改善</Japanese>
      </Key>
      <Key ID="str_a3_rscdisplaywelcome_jets_parc_list5">
        <Original>fast movers now benefit from a better speed of sound simulation and distance-based sound effects</Original>
        <Chinese>高速飛機的音效已經被重新調整, 現在有更真實的聲音與不同距離的層次感</Chinese>
        <French>la vitesse du son des chasseurs et les effets sonores distants sont mieux simulés</French>
        <Spanish>Los más ágiles ahora se benefician de una mejor simulación de la velocidad y de los efectos de sonido basados en la distancia</Spanish>
        <Italian>i jet da caccia ora godono di un miglioramento della simulazione della velocità del suono e di effetti sonori basati sulla distanza</Italian>
        <Polish>miłośnicy szybkości usłyszą poprawioną symulację dźwięku dużych prędkości oraz efekty dźwiękowe zależne od odległości</Polish>
        <Russian>Более реалистичное моделирование звуковых эффектов, связанных с полетом истребителей</Russian>
        <German>Kampfjets profitieren jetzt von einer besseren Schallgeschwindigkeits-Simulation und entfernungsbasierten Soundeffekten</German>
        <Czech>nadzvuková letadla nyní mohou využívat rychlejší simulaci zvuku a zvukových efektů podle vzdálenosti</Czech>
        <English>fast movers now benefit from a better speed of sound simulation and distance-based sound effects</English>
        <Portuguese>as unidades rápidas agora se beneficiam de uma melhor velocidade de simulação de som e de efeitos sonoros baseados na distância</Portuguese>
        <Korean>이제 고속체도 강화된 고속 사운드 시뮬레이션과 거리 기반 사운드 효과를 이용할 수 있게 되었습니다</Korean>
        <Chinesesimp>高速飞机的音效已经被重新调整, 现在有更真实的声音与不同距离的层次感</Chinesesimp>
        <Japanese>高速航空機ではより良質な音速シミュレーションならびに距離に応じた音響効果が味わえます</Japanese>
      </Key>
      <Key ID="str_a3_rscdisplaywelcome_jets_parc_list4_title">
        <Original>Extended Hitpoints</Original>
        <Chinese>飛機弱點模擬</Chinese>
        <French>Hitbox améliorées</French>
        <Spanish>Puntos de vida extendidos</Spanish>
        <Italian>Punti deboli aeroplano</Italian>
        <Polish>Rozbudowane punkty trafień samolotu</Polish>
        <Russian>Больше точек попадания</Russian>
        <German>Verbesserte Trefferpunkte</German>
        <Czech>Rozšířené zásahové body</Czech>
        <English>Extended Hitpoints</English>
        <Portuguese>Pontos de vida estendidos</Portuguese>
        <Korean>확장된 충돌 지점</Korean>
        <Chinesesimp>飞机弱点模拟</Chinesesimp>
        <Japanese>ヒットポイントの拡張</Japanese>
      </Key>
      <Key ID="str_a3_rscdisplaywelcome_jets_parc_list4">
        <Original>more simulated weak-spots for airplanes, ranging from single engine failure to fuel leaks and HUD malfunctions</Original>
        <Chinese>飛機的弱點更加擬真, 像是單發引擎故障, 燃油洩漏與抬頭顯示器故障等</Chinese>
        <French>davantage de points faibles simulés sur les avions : panne de l'ATH, panne de tuyère ou encore fuite de carburant</French>
        <Spanish>Más puntos débiles simulados para los aviones, que pueden ir de un fallo en un motor hasta pérdidas de combustible y fallos en el visualizador en pantalla.</Spanish>
        <Italian>maggior simulazione dei punti deboli degli aerei, a partire dall'avaria del monomotore fino alle perdite di carburante e ai malfunzionamenti dell'HUD</Italian>
        <Polish>więcej symulowanych słabych punktów samolotów: od awarii pojedynczego silnika po wyciek paliwa i usterki HUD-a</Polish>
        <Russian>Различные механики для симуляции уязвимостей самолетов: от отказа одного из двигателей до утечки топлива и сбоев ИЛС</Russian>
        <German>mehr simulierte Schwachpunkte für Flugzeuge, einschließlich einzelner Triebwerkausfälle, Treibstoffverlust und HUD-Fehlfunktionen</German>
        <Czech>více simulovaných citlivých míst letadel od selhání jednoho motoru až po únik paliva nebo poruchy průhledového displeje</Czech>
        <English>more simulated weak-spots for airplanes, ranging from single engine failure to fuel leaks and HUD malfunctions</English>
        <Portuguese>mais pontos fracos simulados para os aviões, desde a falha de um único motor até vazamentos de combustível e problemas na HUD</Portuguese>
        <Korean>비행기에는 싱글 엔진 오류부터 연료 유출, HUD 오작동 등에 이르기까지 취약한 시뮬레이트 지점이 많아졌습니다.</Korean>
        <Chinesesimp>飞机的弱点更加拟真, 像是单发引擎故障, 燃油泄漏与抬头显示器故障等</Chinesesimp>
        <Japanese>航空機の弱点に関するシミュレーションを強化。単発エンジンの緊急停止や燃料漏れ、HUD 故障など</Japanese>
      </Key>
      <Key ID="str_a3_rscdisplaywelcome_jets_parc_list3_title">
        <Original>Dynamic Vehicle Loadouts</Original>
        <Chinese>動態載具裝備</Chinese>
        <French>Chargement dynamique</French>
        <Spanish>Equipamiento vehículos dinámicos</Spanish>
        <Italian>Equipaggiamento dinamico veicoli</Italian>
        <Polish>Dynamiczne uzbrojenie pojazdu</Polish>
        <Russian>Динамичные комплекты экипировки техники</Russian>
        <German>Dynamische Fahrzeugausrüstung</German>
        <Czech>Dynamická výzbroj vozidel</Czech>
        <English>Dynamic Vehicle Loadouts</English>
        <Portuguese>Cargas dinâmicas dos veículos</Portuguese>
        <Korean>동적 차량 장비</Korean>
        <Chinesesimp>动态载具装备</Chinesesimp>
        <Japanese>ダイナミック機体ロードアウト</Japanese>
      </Key>
      <Key ID="str_a3_rscdisplaywelcome_jets_parc_list3">
        <Original>customize variable vehicle loadouts in Eden Editor (selecting aircraft pylon ordnance being the highlight)</Original>
        <Chinese>在伊甸編輯器中使用動態裝備來隨意調整載具的武器配置(調整不同武器掛架的裝備)</Chinese>
        <French>personnalisation des différents chargements de véhicules dans Eden Editor (notamment les points d'emport des avions)</French>
        <Spanish>Personaliza varias configuraciones de vehículos en el Eden Editor (destacando la artillería del pilón de la aeronave)</Spanish>
        <Italian>personalizza gli equipaggiamenti variabili del veicolo nell'Eden Editor (selezionando gli armamenti del pilone alare dell'aeromobile come punto principale)</Italian>
        <Polish>dostosuj zmienne uzbrojenie pojazdów w Eden Editor (w szczególności dobór węzłów uzbrojenia myśliwców)</Polish>
        <Russian>Настройка варьируемых комплектов экипировки техники в редакторе Eden Editor (выбрав боеприпасы пилонного размещения)</Russian>
        <German>personalisiere deine Fahrzeug-Ausrüstung im Eden Editor (das Highlight dabei ist, die Pylon-Bewaffnung für Flugzeuge festlegen zu können)</German>
        <Czech>upravte různou výzbroj vozidel v editoru Eden Editor (zejména možnost výběru výzbroje závěsných bodů letadla)</Czech>
        <English>customize variable vehicle loadouts in Eden Editor (selecting aircraft pylon ordnance being the highlight)</English>
        <Portuguese>personaliza as cargas variáveis dos veículos ​​no Eden Editor (o destaque fica por conta da seleção de artilharia do pilone da aeronave).</Portuguese>
        <Korean>Eden Editor(강조되는 항공기 장착대 포격 선택)에서 차량의 다양한 장비를 사용자 정의할 수 있습니다.</Korean>
        <Chinesesimp>在伊甸编辑器中使用动态装备来随意调整载具的武器配置(调整不同武器挂架的装备)</Chinesesimp>
        <Japanese>Eden Editor で変更可能な機体ロードアウトをカスタマイズ可能（特に機体パイロン武装の選択）</Japanese>
      </Key>
      <Key ID="str_a3_rscdisplaywelcome_jets_parc_list2_title">
        <Original>Data Link</Original>
        <Chinese>資料鏈結</Chinese>
        <French>Flux de données</French>
        <Spanish>Enlace de datos</Spanish>
        <Italian>Collegamento dati</Italian>
        <Polish>Łącze danych</Polish>
        <Russian>Канал передачи данных</Russian>
        <German>Datenlink</German>
        <Czech>Datové spojení</Czech>
        <English>Data Link</English>
        <Portuguese>Datalink</Portuguese>
        <Korean>레이터 링크</Korean>
        <Chinesesimp>资料链结</Chinesesimp>
        <Japanese>データリンク</Japanese>
      </Key>
      <Key ID="str_a3_rscdisplaywelcome_jets_parc_list2">
        <Original>enables vehicles to transmit their sensor data to other vehicles for advanced cooperation</Original>
        <Chinese>現在飛機之間可以透過資料鏈結來分享傳感器的資訊, 進而提高協同作戰的緊密度</Chinese>
        <French>permet aux véhicules de transmettre les données de leurs capteurs aux autres véhicules, pour une meilleure coopération</French>
        <Spanish>Permite que los vehículos transmitan los datos del sensor a otros vehículos para poder cooperar mejor</Spanish>
        <Italian>consente ai veicoli di trasmettere i dati rilevati dal proprio sensore ad altri veicoli per fini di cooperazione avanzata.</Italian>
        <Polish>umożliwia pojazdom transmisję danych z czujników do innych pojazdów w celu zaawansowanej współpracy</Polish>
        <Russian>Позволяет самолетам передавать данные своих датчиков другой технике в целях взаимодействия</Russian>
        <German>erlaubt es Fahrzeugen, ihre Sensordaten für bessere Zusammenarbeit an andere Fahrzeuge zu senden</German>
        <Czech>umožňuje vozidlům odesílat data ze snímačů do jiných vozidel za účelem lepší spolupráce</Czech>
        <English>enables vehicles to transmit their sensor data to other vehicles for advanced cooperation</English>
        <Portuguese>permite aos veículos transmitir os dados do sensor para outros veículos objetivando uma cooperação avançada</Portuguese>
        <Korean>강화된 협력을 통해 감지기 데이터를 다른 차량으로 전송할 수 있습니다.</Korean>
        <Chinesesimp>现在飞机之间可以透过资料链结来分享传感器的资讯, 进而提高协同作战的紧密度</Chinesesimp>
        <Japanese>機体がセンサーデータを他機に発信することで高度な共同作戦行動が可能</Japanese>
      </Key>
      <Key ID="str_a3_rscdisplaywelcome_jets_parc_list1_title">
        <Original>Sensor Overhaul</Original>
        <Chinese>全新的傳感器系統</Chinese>
        <French>Capteurs repensés</French>
        <Spanish>Mejora del sensor</Spanish>
        <Italian>Revisione sensore</Italian>
        <Polish>Przebudowa czujników</Polish>
        <Russian>Подробные показания датчиков</Russian>
        <German>Sensor-Überarbeitung</German>
        <Czech>Předělání snímačů</Czech>
        <English>Sensor Overhaul</English>
        <Portuguese>Renovação do sensor</Portuguese>
        <Korean>감지기 점검</Korean>
        <Chinesesimp>全新的传感器系统</Chinesesimp>
        <Japanese>センサー系を全面改修</Japanese>
      </Key>
      <Key ID="str_a3_rscdisplaywelcome_jets_parc_list1">
        <Original>a new radar interface for targeting guided weapons (used by a variety of vehicles, including jets, helicopters and tanks), powered by advanced Active Radar and Infrared sensor technology</Original>
        <Chinese>新的雷達介面來給導引武器使用(各種載具皆可使用, 像是飛機, 直升機與坦克等), 此科技使用到先進的主動式雷達與紅外線傳感器</Chinese>
        <French>une nouvelle interface de radar pour le ciblage des armes guidées (utilisée notamment par les chasseurs, les hélicoptères ou les chars), avec des radars actifs et des capteurs infrarouges avancés.</French>
        <Spanish>Una nueva interfaz de radar para apuntar con las armas guiadas (que usan una gran variedad de vehículos, como cazas, helicópteros o tanques), que funciona gracias a la avanzada tecnología de radar activo y de infrarrojos.</Spanish>
        <Italian>una nuova interfaccia radar per le armi di puntamento guidato (utilizzata da un'ampia varietà di veicoli, tra cui jet, elicotteri e carri armati) alimentata dal radar attivo avanzato e la tecnologia del sensore a infrarossi</Italian>
        <Polish>nowy interfejs radaru do namierzania pocisków kierowanych (stosowanych przez wiele pojazdów, w tym odrzutowce, helikoptery i czołgi) łączący zaawansowany radar i czujniki podczerwieni</Polish>
        <Russian>Новый интерфейс РЛС для наведения управляемого оружия (используется различной техникой, включая истребители, вертолеты и танки) на базе передовой системы активной РЛС с инфракрасными датчиками</Russian>
        <German>ein neues Radarinterface zur Zielerfassung für Lenkwaffen (wird von verschiedenen Fahrzeugen genutzt, einschließlich Jets, Helikopter und Panzer), das auf fortschrittlicher Aktivradar- und Infrarotsensor-Technologie basiert</German>
        <Czech>nové rozhraní radaru pro zaměřování naváděných zbraní (toto rozhraní používají různá vozidla včetně letadel, vrtulníků a tanků) poháněných pokročilou technologií aktivního radaru a infračervených snímačů</Czech>
        <English>a new radar interface for targeting guided weapons (used by a variety of vehicles, including jets, helicopters and tanks), powered by advanced Active Radar and Infrared sensor technology</English>
        <Portuguese>uma nova interface de radar para mirar armas teleguiadas (usadas por diversos veículos, inclusive caças, helicópteros e tanques), alimentada pela tecnologia avançada de radar ativo e sensor infravermelho</Portuguese>
        <Korean>유도 화기(제트기, 헬리콥터, 탱크 등 다양한 항공기에서 사용 가능)를 표적하는 신규 레이더 인터페이스로 최신 활성 레이더 및 적외선 감지기 기술로 구동됩니다.</Korean>
        <Chinesesimp>新的雷达介面来给导引武器使用(各种载具皆可使用, 像是飞机, 直升机与坦克等), 此科技使用到先进的主动式雷达与红外线传感器</Chinesesimp>
        <Japanese>ターゲット捕捉による誘導兵器用の新型レーダーインターフェース（ジェット、ヘリ、戦車など様々な機体・車両で使用）を実装、高度なアクティブレーダーや赤外線センサー技術を使用</Japanese>
      </Key>
      <Key ID="str_a3_rscdisplaywelcome_jets_parc">
        <Original>We're pleased to have been able to provide the entire Arma 3 player-base with a solid set of features in the form of a &lt;t color='%1'&gt;free platform update&lt;/t&gt;. Not only do these improvements complement the premium aircraft splendidly, but they can and will be deployed for certain other existing vehicle types and (we hope!) by mod teams as well:</Original>
        <Chinese>我們很高興能再次為ArmA3這個平台提供&lt;t color='%1'&gt;免費的特色更新&lt;/t&gt;. 這些新功能不僅只出現在新的付費載具上, 你可以在所有的載具上找到這些新功能, 而且我們相信很快所有載具模組的製作團隊也會一起更新上來:</Chinese>
        <French>Nous sommes heureux de pouvoir offrir à tous les joueurs d'Arma 3 de nouvelles fonctionnalités avec cette &lt;t color='%1'&gt;mise à jour de plateforme gratuite&lt;/t&gt;. Ces améliorations viennent renforcer les avions premium, mais elles seront aussi déployées sur d'autres types de véhicules existants, notamment par les équipes de modders (nous l'espérons !) :</French>
        <Spanish>Nos emociona comunicaros que hemos sido capaces de dar a la comunidad de Arma 3 un gran conjunto de funciones gracias a la &lt;t color='%1'&gt;actualización de plataforma gratuita&lt;/t&gt;. Estas mejoras no solo sirven para los aviones, sino que también se pueden usar en otro tipo de vehículos. ¡Y también esperamos que la comunidad de modders les saque todo el jugo posible!</Spanish>
        <Italian>Siamo felici di fornire a tutti i giocatori di Arma 3 una solida serie di funzioni sotto forma di &lt;t color='%1'&gt;aggiornamento gratuito della piattaforma&lt;/t&gt;. Questi miglioramenti non solo completano l'esclusivo aeromobile in maniera magnifica, ma possono e saranno utilizzati per altri veicoli esistenti e (speriamo!) anche dalle squadre di modder:</Italian>
        <Polish>Z przyjemnością udostępniamy całej społeczności graczy Arma 3 zestaw funkcji w postaci &lt;t color='%1'&gt;darmowej aktualizacji platformy&lt;/t&gt;. Usprawnienia te stanowią znakomite uzupełnienie samolotów z pakietu premium. Mogą też być wykorzystane w niektórych już istniejących typach pojazdów, jak też – mamy nadzieję – przez zespoły moderów:</Polish>
        <Russian>Мы рады, что нам удалось предоставить всем игрокам Arma 3 отличный набор новых игровых возможностей в виде &lt;t color='%1'&gt;бесплатного обновления платформы&lt;/t&gt;. Эти улучшения не только великолепно сочетаются с платным авиационным контентом, но их также можно использовать для других видов техники, и (мы надеемся!) ими могут воспользоваться команды моддеров:</Russian>
        <German>Wir sind sehr froh darüber, dass wir der gesamten Spielergemeinde von Arma 3 eine Reihe von Features in Form eines &lt;t color='%1'&gt;kostenlosen Plattformupdates&lt;/t&gt; zur Verfügung stellen können. Diese Verbesserungen ergänzen nicht nur die Premium-Flugzeuge hervorragend, sondern können und werden auch für bereits existierende Fahrzeugtypen und (hoffentlich!) auch von Modteams umgesetzt:</German>
        <Czech>Velmi nás těší, že všem hráčům hry Arma 3 můžeme opět předložit rozsáhlou sadu nových funkcí v podobě &lt;t color='%1'&gt;bezplatné aktualizace platformy&lt;/t&gt;. Tato vylepšení nejenom výborně doplňují prémiová letadla, ale mohou být a budou využita také pro některé jiné typy stávajících vozidel a také, jak doufáme, užitečná pro modderské týmy:</Czech>
        <English>We're pleased to have been able to provide the entire Arma 3 player-base with a solid set of features in the form of a &lt;t color='%1'&gt;free platform update&lt;/t&gt;. Not only do these improvements complement the premium aircraft splendidly, but they can and will be deployed for certain other existing vehicle types and (we hope!) by mod teams as well:</English>
        <Portuguese>Estamos satisfeitos por poder disponibilizar a toda a base de jogadores do Arma 3 um sólido conjunto de funcionalidades nesta &lt;t color = '%1'&gt;atualização gratuita da plataforma&lt;/ t&gt;. Estas melhorias não só complementam esplendidamente o avião premium, mas também podem e serão implementadas (assim a gente espera!) em alguns tipos de veículos existentes por equipes de modding:</Portuguese>
        <Korean>Arma 3 전체 플레이어에 강력한 기능 세트를 &lt;t color='%1'&gt;무료 플랫폼 업데이트/t&gt; 형태로 제공할 수 있게 되어 매우 기쁩니다. 이번 개선을 통해 프리미엄 항공기를 탁월한 수준으로 보완할 수 있으며, 일부 기존 차량 유형에 배치할 수 있습니다. 나아가 모드 팀에도 배치될 수 있기를 바랍니다!</Korean>
        <Chinesesimp>我们很高兴能再次为ArmA3这个平台提供&lt;t color='%1'&gt;免费的特色更新&lt;/t&gt;. 这些新功能不仅只出现在新的付费载具上, 你可以在所有的载具上找到这些新功能, 而且我们相信很快所有载具模组的制作团队也会一起更新上来:</Chinesesimp>
        <Japanese>これまで Arma 3 プレイヤーの皆様には&lt;t color='%1'&gt;無料のプラットフォーム・アップデート&lt;/t&gt;という形で実用的な新機能一式をお届けすることができました。これら改良点はプレミアム機体を見事に補完するだけでなく、同時に一部の既存機体や車両において今後も展開し、また他の MOD チームの手にも適用してもらえたらと考えています。</Japanese>
      </Key>
      <Key ID="str_a3_rscdisplaywelcome_jets_parb_title">
        <Original>PREMIUM</Original>
        <Chinese>付費內容</Chinese>
        <French>PREMIUM</French>
        <Spanish>PREMIUM</Spanish>
        <Italian>PREMIUM</Italian>
        <Polish>PREMIUM</Polish>
        <Russian>ПЛАТНЫЙ КОНТЕНТ</Russian>
        <German>PREMIUM</German>
        <Czech>PRÉMIOVÝ OBSAH</Czech>
        <English>PREMIUM</English>
        <Portuguese>PREMIUM</Portuguese>
        <Korean>프리미엄</Korean>
        <Chinesesimp>付费内容</Chinesesimp>
        <Japanese>プレミアム</Japanese>
      </Key>
      <Key ID="str_a3_rscdisplaywelcome_jets_parb_footer">
        <Original>More about Arma 3 Jets</Original>
        <Chinese>更多關於ArmA3戰機的資訊</Chinese>
        <French>En savoir plus sur Arma 3 Jets</French>
        <Spanish>Más sobre Arma 3 Jets</Spanish>
        <Italian>Maggiori informazioni su Arma 3 Jets</Italian>
        <Polish>Więcej o rozszerzeniu Arma 3 Jets</Polish>
        <Russian>Подробнее о Arma 3 Jets</Russian>
        <German>Mehr über Arma 3 Jets</German>
        <Czech>Více informací o rozšíření Arma 3 Jets</Czech>
        <English>More about Arma 3 Jets</English>
        <Portuguese>Mais sobre Arma 3 Jets</Portuguese>
        <Korean>Arma 3 Jets에 대한 자세한 정보</Korean>
        <Chinesesimp>更多关于ArmA3战机的资讯</Chinesesimp>
        <Japanese>Arma 3 Jets の詳細</Japanese>
      </Key>
      <Key ID="str_a3_rscdisplaywelcome_jets_parb">
        <Original>As you've come to expect from our DLC strategy, this major release brings great new &lt;t color='%1'&gt;premium content&lt;/t&gt; for DLC owners and enhances the sandbox for all Arma 3 players. With Arma 3 Jets, our goal was to deliver air superiority jets capable of combat beyond visual ranges. Owners will gain unrestricted access to &lt;t color='%1'&gt;3 new fighter aircraft&lt;/t&gt; and an &lt;t color='%1'&gt;Unmanned Combat Air Vehicle&lt;/t&gt;. You can experience the enhanced aerial gameplay in the dedicated &lt;t color='%1'&gt;Showcase&lt;/t&gt;, or if you're looking for a quick hands-on preview, boot up the Virtual Arsenal mode to try the assets without restriction.</Original>
        <Chinese>如同我們往常的資料片政策, 這次除了有優質的&lt;t color='%1'&gt;付費內容&lt;/t&gt;外, 我們也提供免費的系統升級給所有的ArmA3玩家. 在ArmA3戰機中, 我們主要的目標就是提供玩家一個超視距空優戰鬥的體驗. 資料片買家將能直接擁有&lt;t color='%1'&gt;3款新戰機&lt;/t&gt;以及&lt;t color='%1'&gt;1台無人戰機&lt;/t&gt;. 你可以直接到&lt;t color='%1'&gt;任務展示&lt;/t&gt;中體驗全新的空中戰鬥, 沒有資料片的玩家也可以直接到虛擬軍火庫中免費體驗這些新載具.</Chinese>
        <French>Comme à l'accoutumée avec nos DLC, cette mise à jour majeure offre un &lt;t color='%1'&gt;contenu premium&lt;/t&gt; de qualité aux acquéreurs du DLC et améliore la plateforme pour tous les joueurs d'Arma 3. Avec Arma 3 Jets, notre intention était d'offrir des chasseurs de supériorité aérienne capables de combattre pas seulement en visuel. Les acquéreurs auront un accès illimité aux &lt;t color='%1'&gt;3 nouveaux avions&lt;/t&gt; et à un &lt;t color='%1'&gt;drone aérien de combat&lt;/t&gt;. Vous pourrez tester ce gameplay aérien amélioré dans la &lt;t color='%1'&gt;Présentation&lt;/t&gt; proposée. Vous pouvez aussi lancer l'Arsenal virtuel pour tester ces ajouts rapidement et sans limite.</French>
        <Spanish>Como suele ser habitual con nuestros DLC, este lanzamiento trae &lt;t color='%1'&gt;contenido premium&lt;/t&gt; para los que tengan el DLC y mejora la experiencia de juego para todos los jugadores de Arma 3. Con Arma 3 Jets, nuestro objetivo es ofrecer cazas de superioridad aérea capaces de enzarzarse en combates que van más allá de donde la vista alcanza. Los que tengan este contenido podrán acceder sin restricciones a &lt;t color='%1'&gt;3 cazas nuevos&lt;/t&gt; y a un &lt;t color='%1'&gt;vehículo de combate aéreo no tripulado&lt;/t&gt;. Puedes disfrutar de una experiencia aérea mejorada en la &lt;t color='%1'&gt;Exhibición&lt;/t&gt; dedicada, o, si quieres disfrutar de ella cuanto antes, puedes acceder al modo Arsenal Virtual para probar las unidades sin ninguna restricción.</Spanish>
        <Italian>Come già ti aspetterai dalla strategia messa a punto con i nostri DLC, questa release principale integrerà nuovi &lt;t color='%1'&gt;contenuti premium&lt;/t&gt; per i possessori del DLC e consentirà di migliorare il sandbox per tutti i giocatori di Arma 3. Il nostro obiettivo con Arma 3 Jets è di fornire jet da superiorità aerea che possano combattere oltre il campo visivo. I possessori otterranno accesso illimitato ai &lt;t color='%1'&gt;3 nuovi aerei da caccia&lt;/t&gt; e all'&lt;t color='%1'&gt;aeroveicolo da combattimento senza equippaggio&lt;/t&gt;. Puoi provare la modalità di gioco aerea avanzata nella sezione &lt;t color='%1'&gt;Dimostrazioni&lt;/t&gt; dedicata oppure, se sei alla ricerca di un'anteprima veloce, avvia la modalità Arsenale virtuale per provare le risorse senza alcuna restrizione.</Italian>
        <Polish>Zgodnie ze strategią wydawniczą naszego studia premiera nowego DLC wnosi całkiem nową, znakomitą &lt;t color='%1'&gt;zawartość premium&lt;/t&gt; dla jego posiadaczy, ale też wprowadza udoskonalenia dla wszystkich graczy Arma 3. Przy tworzeniu Arma 3 Jets założyliśmy sobie opracowanie myśliwców przewagi powietrznej zdolnych prowadzić działania bojowe poza zasięgiem wzroku. Posiadacze zyskają pełen dostęp do &lt;t color='%1'&gt;3 nowych myśliwców&lt;/t&gt; oraz &lt;t color='%1'&gt;bojowego bezzałogowego statku powietrznego&lt;/t&gt;. Udoskonaloną rozgrywkę w powietrzu można wypróbować za pomocą dedykowanej &lt;t color='%1'&gt;prezentacji&lt;/t&gt;. Jeśli wolisz szybkie wprowadzenie, możesz włączyć Wirtualny arsenał i wypróbować nowe elementy bez ograniczeń.</Polish>
        <Russian>Этот крупный релиз полностью соответствует уже привычной для вас стратегии выпуска дополнений и включает отличный новый &lt;t color='%1'&gt;платный контент&lt;/t&gt; для владельцев дополнений, а также улучшает песочницу для всех игроков Arma 3. Цель Arma 3 Jets – добавить в игру истребители, которые способны вести бой за пределами видимости, для завоевания превосходства в воздухе. Владельцы получат неограниченный доступ к &lt;t color='%1'&gt;3 новым истребителям&lt;/t&gt; и &lt;t color='%1'&gt;беспилотному боевому летательному аппарату&lt;/t&gt;. Вы можете насладиться улучшенным воздушным геймплеем в специальном режиме &lt;t color='%'&gt;Демонстрации&lt;/t&gt;, а если вы хотите быстро опробовать новые самолеты, то можете загрузить режим Виртуального арсенала и опробовать новые боевые единицы без каких-либо ограничений.</Russian>
        <German>Wie du es schon von unserer DLC-Strategie kennst, bietet diese Veröffentlichung großartige neue &lt;t color='%1'&gt;Premium-Inhalte&lt;/t&gt; für die Käufer des DLC und verbessert die Sandbox-Erfahrung für alle Spieler von Arma 3. Unser Ziel für Arma 3 Jets war es, Kampfjets im Spiel zu implementieren, die auch über die Sichtreichweite hinaus am Kampf teilnehmen können. Käufer des DLC erhalten uneingeschränkten Zugang zu &lt;t color='%1'&gt;3 neuen Kampfjets&lt;/t&gt; und einem &lt;t color='%1'&gt;unbemannten Kampfflugzeug&lt;/t&gt;. Du kannst den verbesserten Luftkampf in der speziell zugeschnittenen &lt;t color='%1'&gt;Präsentation&lt;/t&gt; erleben, oder wenn du eine schnelle Vorschau haben möchtest, das Virtuelle Arsenal starten, um die Assets ohne Einschränkungen zu testen.</German>
        <Czech>Jak už jste si jistě zvykli, v rámci naší strategie balíčků DLC přinášíme pro majitele DLC v tomto velkém vydání úžasný nový &lt;t color='%1'&gt;prémiový obsah&lt;/t&gt; a zároveň vylepšujeme otevřený svět pro všechny hráče hry Arma 3. V rozšíření Arma 3 Jets vám přinášíme stíhací letouny vzdušné převahy, které jsou schopné boje mimo viditelný dosah. Majitelé tohoto DLC získají neomezený přístup ke &lt;t color='%1'&gt;3 novým stíhacím letounům&lt;/t&gt; a jednomu &lt;t color='%1'&gt;bezpilotnímu bojovému letounu&lt;/t&gt;. Vylepšený vzdušný boj si můžete vyzkoušet ve speciální &lt;t color='%1'&gt;ukázce&lt;/t&gt; – nebo, pokud si chcete vyzkoušet rychlý náhled, můžete spustit Virtuální arzenál a vyzkoušet si nové prvky bez omezení.</Czech>
        <English>As you've come to expect from our DLC strategy, this major release brings great new &lt;t color='%1'&gt;premium content&lt;/t&gt; for DLC owners and enhances the sandbox for all Arma 3 players. With Arma 3 Jets, our goal was to deliver air superiority jets capable of combat beyond visual ranges. Owners will gain unrestricted access to &lt;t color='%1'&gt;3 new fighter aircraft&lt;/t&gt; and an &lt;t color='%1'&gt;Unmanned Combat Air Vehicle&lt;/t&gt;. You can experience the enhanced aerial gameplay in the dedicated &lt;t color='%1'&gt;Showcase&lt;/t&gt;, or if you're looking for a quick hands-on preview, boot up the Virtual Arsenal mode to try the assets without restriction.</English>
        <Portuguese>Como você está acostumado com a nossa estratégia de DLC, esta grande novidade traz novos &lt;t color=%'1'&gt;conteúdos premium&lt;/t&gt; para os proprietários do DLC e melhora o universo do jogo para todos os jogadores de Arma 3. Com Arma 3 Jets, nosso objetivo foi oferecer aeronaves de superioridade aérea capazes de combater além dos limites visuais. Os proprietários terão acesso irrestrito a &lt;t color ='%1'&gt;3 novos aviões de combate&lt;/t&gt; e a um &lt;t color ='%1'&gt;veículo aéreo de combate não tripulado&lt;/t&gt;. Você pode experimentar a jogabilidade aérea aprimorada em &lt;t color = '% 1'&gt;Mostruários&lt;/ t&gt; ou, se estiver procurando uma pré-visualização rápida, basta iniciar o modo “Arsenal Virtual” para experimentar os recursos sem restrição.</Portuguese>
        <Korean>DLC 전략에서 예상할 수 있듯이, 이번 주요 출시에서는 DLC 구매자를 위해 &lt;t color='%1'&gt;프리미엄 콘텐츠&lt;/t&gt;를 제공하며 Arma 3 전체 플레이어에게 강화된 샌드박스 기능을 제공합니다. Arma 3 Jets에서 저희의 목표는 육안 거리 밖에서도 전투할 수 있는 제공권 제트기를 제공하는 것입니다.  구매자들은 &lt;t color='%1'&gt;3 신규 전투 항공기&lt;/t&gt; 및 &lt;t color='%1'&gt;무인전투항공기(UCAV)&lt;/t&gt;를 무제한으로 이용할 수 있게 되었습니다. 전용 &lt;t color='%1'&gt;쇼케이스&lt;/t&gt;에서 강화된 항공 게임플레이를 경험하거나 신속한 자동 미리보기를 원하는 경우 가상 무기고 모드를 부팅하여 제한 없이 자산을 이용해볼 수 있습니다.</Korean>
        <Chinesesimp>如同我们往常的资料片政策, 这次除了有优质的&lt;t color='%1'&gt;付费内容&lt;/t&gt;外, 我们也提供免费的系统升级给所有的ArmA3玩家. 在ArmA3战机中, 我们主要的目标就是提供玩家一个超视距空优战斗的体验. 资料片买家将能直接拥有&lt;t color='%1'&gt;3款新战机&lt;/t&gt;以及&lt;t color='%1'&gt;1台无人战机&lt;/t&gt;. 你可以直接到&lt;t color='%1'&gt;任务展示&lt;/t&gt;中体验全新的空中战斗, 没有资料片的玩家也可以直接到虚拟军火库中免费体验这些新载具.</Chinesesimp>
        <Japanese>今までの弊社の DLC 戦略と同じく、今回のリリースでは DLC をお持ちの方に素晴らしい新たな&lt;t color='%1'&gt;プレミアムコンテンツ&lt;/t&gt;をお届けし、そして全 Arma 3 プレイヤーのサンドボックスをさらに強化します。「Arma 3 Jets」における私達の目標は、視界外での戦闘が可能な制空ジェット戦闘機をお届けすることでした。DLC 所有者の方は&lt;t color='%1'&gt;新戦闘機・全 3 機種&lt;/t&gt;、そして&lt;t color='%1'&gt;無人戦闘航空機 (UCAV)&lt;/t&gt; に無制限でご利用いただけます。専用&lt;t color='%1'&gt;ショーケース&lt;/t&gt;でさらに強化された空中でのゲームプレイを体験することも、「バーチャル武器庫」で手っ取り早く手に取って、制限なしで新規アセットをお試しいただくこともできます。</Japanese>
      </Key>
      <Key ID="str_a3_rscdisplaywelcome_jets_para">
        <Original>Scrambling all pilots! We've launched the &lt;t color='%1'&gt;Arma 3 Jets&lt;/t&gt; DLC for immediate interdiction. We hope this first huge milestone on our &lt;a href='%3' color='%2'&gt;2017 roadmap&lt;/a&gt; will please fans of vehicle gameplay and those looking for an even deeper combined arms experience. For the first time in Arma 3's development, this DLC was created together with a third-party external team: &lt;t color='%1'&gt;BRAVO ZERO ONE Studios&lt;/t&gt;, led by &lt;a href='%4' color='%2'&gt;Make Arma Not War&lt;/a&gt; winner Joshua "Saul" Carpenter. We would like to thank these talented developers for their hard work! Inspect the strong line-up of new assets and features below, or jump right into the cockpit for takeoff!</Original>
        <Chinese>通告所有飛行員! 我們已經讓&lt;t color='%1'&gt;ArmA3戰機&lt;/t&gt;資料片正式上市. 我們希望這個&lt;a href='%3' color='%2'&gt;2017規劃藍圖&lt;/a&gt;的第一個里程碑能讓那些載具愛好者與想要更加擬真體驗的玩家有所感受. 關於這次資料片的開發, 我們是第一次與其他第三方團隊合作: &lt;t color='%1'&gt;BRAVO ZERO ONE 工作室&lt;/t&gt;,是由&lt;a href='%4' color='%2'&gt;讓ArmA不要戰爭&lt;/a&gt;的贏家Joshua "Saul" Carpenter所領軍. 我們很感謝這些厲害的作者做出如此厲害的內容! 你可以看看底下的訊息來了解新載具與新特色, 或是現在立刻進入遊戲中直接體驗!</Chinese>
        <French>À tous les pilotes ! Nous venons de lancer le DLC &lt;t color='%1'&gt;Arma 3 Jets&lt;/t&gt;. Nous espérons que cette sortie importante dans notre &lt;a href='%3' color='%2'&gt;feuille de route 2017&lt;/a&gt; ravira les amateurs de pilotage et ceux d'entre vous qui recherchent une expérience interarmées plus approfondie. Pour la première fois dans l'histoire d'Arma 3, un DLC a été créé par une équipe externe : &lt;t color='%1'&gt;BRAVO ZERO ONE Studios&lt;/t&gt;, dirigée par le vainqueur de &lt;a href='%4' color='%2'&gt;Make Arma Not War&lt;/a&gt;, Joshua "Saul" Carpenter. Nous aimerions en profiter pour remercier ces talentueux développeurs pour leur travail acharné ! Passez en revue les fonctionnalités décrites ci-dessous, ou montez tout de suite dans le cockpit !</French>
        <Spanish>¡Atención, pilotos! Ya está disponible el DLC &lt;t color='%1'&gt;Arma 3 Jets&lt;/t&gt;. Esperamos que este primer hito de &lt;a href='%3' color='%2'&gt;2017&lt;/a&gt; agrade a los fans de los vehículos y a los que quieren una experiencia bélica más centrada en las armas. Por primera vez en el desarrollo de Arma 3, este DLC ha sido creado junto a un equipo experto: &lt;t color='%1'&gt;BRAVO ZERO ONE Studios&lt;/t&gt;, dirigido por el ganador de &lt;a href='%4' color='%2'&gt;Make Arma Not War&lt;/a&gt;, Joshua «Saul» Carpenter. ¡Nos gustaría dar las gracias a estos desarrolladores con tanto talento por trabajar tan arduamente! Echa un ojo a la gran variedad de unidades y funciones disponibles, que podrás ver a continuación, o bien, si lo prefieres, ¡sube a la cabina y prepárate para despegar!</Spanish>
        <Italian>Chiamata a tutti i piloti! Abbiamo lanciato il DLC di &lt;t color='%1'&gt;Arma 3 Jets&lt;/t&gt; per intercettazione immediata. Ci auguriamo che questa prima, enorme tappa della nostra &lt;a href='%3' color='%2'&gt;tabella di marcia del 2017&lt;/a&gt; accontenterà sia i fan della modalità di gioco che riguarda l'utilizzo di veicoli, sia coloro che sono alla ricerca di un'esperienza ancora più approfondita per quel che riguarda le armi combinate. Per la prima volta nello sviluppo di Arma 3, questo DLC è stato realizzato in collaborazione con un team esterno: il &lt;t color='%1'&gt;BRAVO ZERO ONE Studios&lt;/t&gt;, guidato dal vincitore di &lt;a href='%4' color='%2'&gt;Make Arma Not War&lt;/a&gt; Joshua "Saul" Carpenter. Desideriamo pertanto ringraziare questi sviluppatori talentuosi per il duro lavoro svolto! Vai a vedere la grande line-up delle risorse e delle funzionalità qui in basso, oppure monta dentro la cabina di pilotaggio per il decollo!</Italian>
        <Polish>Do wszystkich pilotów! Wydajemy DLC &lt;t color='%1'&gt;Arma 3 Jets&lt;/t&gt; ze skutkiem natychmiastowym. Mamy nadzieję, że ten pierwszy znaczący punkt &lt;a href='%3' color='%2'&gt;na naszej tegorocznej mapie wydawniczej&lt;/a&gt; przypadnie do gustu entuzjastom rozgrywki z udziałem pojazdów oraz sił połączonych. Po raz pierwszy w historii Arma 3 nad DLC pracowaliśmy razem z zewnętrznym zespołem – &lt;t color='%1'&gt;BRAVO ZERO ONE Studios&lt;/t&gt;, któremu szefuje zwycięzca konkursu &lt;a href='%4' color='%2'&gt;Make Arma Not War&lt;/a&gt;, Joshua „Saul” Carpenter. Pragniemy podziękować w tym miejscu za ich ciężką pracę! Zapoznaj się z pełną listą nowych elementów i funkcji poniżej lub też wskakuj od razu do kokpitu i startuj!</Polish>
        <Russian>Внимание всем пилотам! Мы выпустили для вас дополнение &lt;t color='%1'&gt;Arma 3 Jets&lt;/t&gt;. Мы надеемся, что это станет первой крупной вехой в &lt;a href='%3' color='%2'&gt;наших планах на 2017 год&lt;/a&gt; и что наши фанаты, которые ищут еще более глубокого погружения в игру, оценят новые геймплейные особенности. Впервые за всю историю разработки Arma 3 это дополнение было создано совместно со сторонней командой разработчиков: &lt;t color='%1'&gt;BRAVO ZERO ONE Studios&lt;/t&gt;, которую возглавил победитель конкурса &lt;a href='%4' color='%2'&gt;Make Arma Not War&lt;/a&gt; Joshua "Saul" Carpenter. Мы хотели бы поблагодарить этих талантливых разработчиков за их усердную работу! Изучите отличную подборку новой техники и возможностей или запрыгивайте скорей в кабину и готовьтесь ко взлету!</Russian>
        <German>An alle Piloten: Wir haben den DLC &lt;t color='%1'&gt;Arma 3 Jets&lt;/t&gt; für eine unmittelbare Abriegelung des Luftraums veröffentlicht. Wir hoffen, dass dieser erste große Meilenstein auf unserer &lt;a href='%3' color='%2'&gt;Roadmap für 2017&lt;/a&gt; den Fans von Fahrzeuggefechten und einer detaillierteren Repräsentation kombinierter Streitkräfte gefallen wird. Zum ersten Mal in der Entwicklung von Arma 3 wurde ein DLC in Zusammenarbeit mit einem externen Drittanbieter produziert: &lt;t color='%1'&gt;BRAVO ZERO ONE Studios&lt;/t&gt;, geleitet vom &lt;a href='%4' color='%2'&gt;Make Arma Not War&lt;/a&gt;-Gewinner Joshua "Saul" Carpenter. Wir möchten diesen talentierten Entwicklern für ihre harte Arbeit danken! Seht euch unten die neuen Assets an, oder steigt gleich ins Cockpit und hebt ab!</German>
        <Czech>Všichni piloti do vzduchu! Právě jsme vydali DLC &lt;t color='%1'&gt;Arma 3 Jets&lt;/t&gt; vyžadující okamžitý stíhací manévr. Doufáme, že tento první velký milník v rámci našeho &lt;a href='%3' color='%2'&gt;plánu na rok 2017&lt;/a&gt; udělá radost všem fanouškům boje ve vozidlech i hráčům, kteří hledají ještě hlubší zážitek z boje v kombinovaných operacích. Poprvé v historii vývoje hry Arma 3 byl tento balíček DLC vytvořen ve spolupráci s externím týmem: &lt;t color='%1'&gt;BRAVO ZERO ONE Studios&lt;/t&gt;, který vede vítěz soutěže &lt;a href='%4' color='%2'&gt;Make Arma Not War&lt;/a&gt; Joshua „Saul“ Carpenter. Chceme těmto talentovaným vývojářům poděkovat za jejich tvrdou práci. Podívejte se na bohatou nabídku nových prvků a funkcí níže, nebo nasedněte do kabiny a ihned vzlétněte!</Czech>
        <English>Scrambling all pilots! We've launched the &lt;t color='%1'&gt;Arma 3 Jets&lt;/t&gt; DLC for immediate interdiction. We hope this first huge milestone on our &lt;a href='%3' color='%2'&gt;2017 roadmap&lt;/a&gt; will please fans of vehicle gameplay and those looking for an even deeper combined arms experience. For the first time in Arma 3's development, this DLC was created together with a third-party external team: &lt;t color='%1'&gt;BRAVO ZERO ONE Studios&lt;/t&gt;, led by &lt;a href='%4' color='%2'&gt;Make Arma Not War&lt;/a&gt; winner Joshua "Saul" Carpenter. We would like to thank these talented developers for their hard work! Inspect the strong line-up of new assets and features below, or jump right into the cockpit for takeoff!</English>
        <Portuguese>Aviso a todos os pilotos! Lançamos o DLC &lt;t color='%1'&gt;Arma 3 Jets&lt;/t&gt; para apreciação imediata. A gente espera que este primeiro grande marco no nosso &lt;a href='%3' color='%2'&gt;percurso de 2017&lt;/a&gt; agrade aos fãs dos jogos de veículos e àqueles que procuram uma experiência de armas ainda mais intensa. Pela primeira vez no desenvolvimento da Arma 3, este DLC foi criado em conjunto com uma equipe externa: &lt;t color='%1'&gt;BRAVO ZERO ONE Studios&lt;/t&gt;, liderada por Joshua “Saul” Carpente, vencedor do &lt;a href='%4' Color='% 2'&gt;Make Arma Not War&lt;/a&gt;. Gostaríamos de agradecer a esses talentosos desenvolvedores por todo o trabalho árduo realizado! Confira o poderoso conjunto de novos veículos e recursos abaixo ou entre agora mesmo na cabine e prepare-se para a decolagem!</Portuguese>
        <Korean>모든 조종사는 긴급 이륙하라! 즉각적인 차단 위해&lt;t color='%1'&gt;Arma 3 Jets&lt;/t&gt; DLC를 런칭했습니다. &lt;a href='%3' color='%2'&gt;2017 로드맵&lt;/a&gt;의 이 위대한 첫번째 이정표가 항공기 게임플레이를 좋아하는 팬들과 심화된 결합 무기 경험을 원하는 플레이어들에게 희소식이 되기를 바랍니다. 이번 DLC는 Arma 3 개발에서는 최초로 제3자 외부 팀과 손을 잡고 만들었습니다. &lt;t color='%1'&gt;BRAVO ZERO ONE Studios&lt;/t&gt;는 &lt;a href='%4' color='%2'&gt;"전쟁이 아닌 Arma 제작하기(Make Arma Not War)"&lt;/a&gt; 대회의 수상자인 조슈아 "사울" 카펜터가 수장으로 이끌고 있습니다. 재능이 뛰어난 이 개발자분들의 심혈을 기울인 노력에 찬사를 보내드립니다! 한층 강화된 신규 항공자산 및 기능 라인업을 아래에서 확인하거나 조종석에 올라 이륙을 준비하세요!</Korean>
        <Chinesesimp>通告所有飞行员! 我们已经让&lt;t color='%1'&gt;ArmA3战机&lt;/t&gt;资料片正式上市. 我们希望这个&lt;a href='%3' color='%2'&gt;2017规划蓝图&lt;/a&gt;的第一个里程碑能让那些载具爱好者与想要更加拟真体验的玩家有所感受. 关于这次资料片的开发, 我们是第一次与其他第三方团队合作: &lt;t color='%1'&gt;BRAVO ZERO ONE 工作室&lt;/t&gt;,是由&lt;a href='%4' color='%2'&gt;让ArmA不要战争&lt;/a&gt;的赢家Joshua "Saul" Carpenter所领军. 我们很感谢这些厉害的作者做出如此厉害的内容! 你可以看看底下的讯息来了解新载具与新特色, 或是现在立刻进入游戏中直接体验!</Chinesesimp>
        <Japanese>全パイロット、スクランブル！&lt;t color='%1'&gt;Arma 3 Jets&lt;/t&gt; DLC が迎撃のため緊急発進します。弊社の&lt;a href='%3' color='%2'&gt;2017 ロードマップ&lt;/a&gt;で最初の大型目標として公開する今回の内容が、車両・機体のゲームプレイが好きな方、そしてより深みのある総合戦闘をお求めの方を満足させ得るものであると願っております。今回の DLC は、Arma 3 の開発において初めて、&lt;a href='%4' color='%2'&gt;Make Arma Not War&lt;/a&gt; 優勝者ジョシュア・"ソール"・カーペンター氏率いるサードパーティーの外部チーム「&lt;t color='%1'&gt;BRAVO ZERO ONE Studios&lt;/t&gt;」との共同開発で作られました。この才能あふれるデベロッパーたちの日々の努力に改めて感謝いたします！強力な新規アセットや機能の一覧を以下で確認するか、さっそくコックピットに飛び込んで離陸しましょう！</Japanese>
      </Key>
      <Key ID="str_a3_rscdisplaywelcome_jets_pare_list10">
        <Original>use the Y-32 Xi'an aircraft to support friendly troops on Tanoa against NATO forces (bonus for &lt;a href='%2'&gt;Apex&lt;/a&gt; owners)</Original>
        <Chinese>駕駛Y-32"西安"垂直起降機支援友軍對抗Tanoa上的北約部隊(此內容屬於&lt;a href='%2'&gt;頂尖&lt;/a&gt;的一部分)</Chinese>
        <French>utilisez le Y-32 Xi'an pour apporter un soutien aux troupes alliées sur Tanoa contre les forces de l’OTAN (bonus pour les propriétaires de l’extension &lt;a href='%2'&gt;Apex&lt;/a&gt;)</French>
        <Spanish>Usa el avión Y-32 Xi'an para ofrecer apoyo a las tropas aliadas de Tanoa contra las fuerzas de la OTAN (adicional para los que tengan &lt;a href='%2'&gt;Apex&lt;/a&gt;)</Spanish>
        <Italian>usa il velivolo Y-32 Xi'an per supportare le truppe alleate su Tanoa contro le forze NATO (bonus per i possessori di &lt;a href='%2'&gt;Apex&lt;/a&gt;)</Italian>
        <Polish>użyj samolotu Y-32 Xi'an, aby udzielić wsparcia sojusznikom w walce z siłami NATO (bonus dla posiadaczy rozszerzenia &lt;a href='%2'&gt;Apex&lt;/a&gt;)</Polish>
        <Russian>Используйте СВВП Y-32 Xi'an, чтобы оказать поддержку дружественным войскам, противостоящим силам НАТО на Таноа (бонус для игроков, купивших &lt;a href='%2'&gt;Apex&lt;/a&gt;)</Russian>
        <German>Nutze das Y-32 Xi'an, um deine Streitkräfte auf Tanoa gegen die NATO-Truppen zu unterstützen (Bonus für Besitzer von &lt;a href='%2'&gt;Apex&lt;/a&gt;)</German>
        <Czech>pomocí Y-32 Xi'an podpořte své jednotky v souostroví Tanoa proti silám NATO (bonus pro vlastníky rozšíření &lt;a href='%2'&gt;Apex&lt;/a&gt;)</Czech>
        <English>use the Y-32 Xi'an aircraft to support friendly troops on Tanoa against NATO forces (bonus for &lt;a href='%2'&gt;Apex&lt;/a&gt; owners)</English>
        <Portuguese>utilize a aeronave Y-32 Xi'an para apoiar as tropas aliadas em Tanoa contra as forças da OTAN (bônus para os proprietários do &lt;a href='%2'&gt;Apex&lt;/a&gt;)</Portuguese>
        <Korean>Y-32 Xi'an 항공기를 사용하여 NATO군에 대항하여 Tanoa의 아군을 지원할 수 있습니다(&lt;a href='%2'&gt;Apex&lt;/a&gt; 구매자에게 보너스 제공)</Korean>
        <Chinesesimp>驾驶Y-32"西安"垂直起降机支援友军对抗Tanoa上的北约部队(此内容属于&lt;a href='%2'&gt;顶尖&lt;/a&gt;的一部分)</Chinesesimp>
        <Japanese>Y-32 Xi'an 機体を使い、タノアの NATO 軍に攻撃を仕掛ける友軍部隊を支援せよ（&lt;a href='%2'&gt;Apex&lt;/a&gt; 所有者はボーナスをもらう）</Japanese>
      </Key>
      <Key ID="str_a3_rscdisplaywelcome_jets_pare_list10_title">
        <Original>Showcase VTOL</Original>
        <Chinese>垂直起降機任務展示</Chinese>
        <French>Présentation des ADAV</French>
        <Spanish>Mostrar VTOL</Spanish>
        <Italian>Dimostrazioni VTOL</Italian>
        <Polish>Prezentacja samolotów VTOL</Polish>
        <Russian>Демонстрация СВВП</Russian>
        <German>Präsentation: VTOL</German>
        <Czech>Ukázka letounu VTOL</Czech>
        <English>Showcase VTOL</English>
        <Portuguese>Exibir VTOL</Portuguese>
        <Korean>VTOL 쇼케이스</Korean>
        <Chinesesimp>垂直起降机任务展示</Chinesesimp>
        <Japanese>VTOL ショーケース</Japanese>
      </Key>
    </Container>
    <Container name="FieldManual">
      <Key ID="STR_A3_CfgHints_PremiumContent_PremiumJets1">
        <Original>Dominate the skies over the battlefield in 3 new fighter aircraft and an Unmanned Combat Air Vehicle. Fly fast and agile air superiority jets to provide air support in the dedicated Showcase, and more, in the Arma 3 Jets DLC.%1&lt;img size='9' shadow='0' image='A3\Data_F_Jets\Images\jets_fm_overview_co' /&gt;%1%2F/A-181 Black Wasp II - a fifth generation NATO carrier-based fighter jet%1%2To-201 Shikra - a fifth generation CSAT air superiority fighter jet%1%2A-149 Gryphon - an advanced fourth generation AAF fighter jet%1%2Sentinel - a NATO carrier-based Unmanned Combat Air Vehicle%1%2Deck Crew Vests - colored vests for various characters roles on the carrier%1%2Showcase Fighter Jets - take to the skies over Altis and engage in Air-to-Air and Air-to-Ground operations%1%2Official Sound Track - a new music track befitting the jets theme%1%2Achievements - a set of extra &lt;a href='http://steamcommunity.com/stats/107410/achievements'&gt;Steam Achievements&lt;/a&gt;%1</Original>
        <Chinese>駕馭全新的3款戰機與1款無人戰機, 你就可以稱霸整個戰場的領空. 你可以在任務展示中體驗到新飛機的高速與敏捷性, 讓你獲得絕對的空優, 這些盡在ArmA3戰機資料片中.%1&lt;img size='9' shadow='0' image='A3\Data_F_Jets\Images\jets_fm_overview_co' /&gt;%1%2F/A-181"黑蜂"2型戰鬥攻擊機 - 北約的一台第五代艦載戰鬥攻擊機%1%2To-201"褐耳鷹"戰鬥機 - 廣協同盟的一台第五代空優戰鬥機%1%2A-149"獅鷲"戰鬥機 - Altis政府軍的一台先進第四代戰鬥機%1%2"哨兵"無人戰機 - 北約的一台艦載無人戰機%1%2甲板人員背心 - 數種不同顏色的背心供航空母艦的甲板人員使用%1%2戰鬥機任務展示 - 前往Altis體驗空對空與空對地的飛行任務%1%2官方原聲帶 - 一首配合戰機主題的曲子%1%2成就 - 新的一組&lt;a href='http://steamcommunity.com/stats/107410/achievements'&gt;Steam成就&lt;/a&gt;%1</Chinese>
        <French>Dominez le ciel aux commandes de trois nouveaux avions de chasse et d'un drone de combat. Pilotez des chasseurs de supériorité aérienne pour offrir votre appui aérien, notamment dans la présentation dédiée du DLC Arma 3 Jets.%1&lt;img size='9' shadow='0' image='A3\Data_F_Jets\Images\jets_fm_overview_co' /&gt;%1%2F/A-181 Black Wasp II - un chasseur de combat de 5e génération de l'OTAN (pour porte-avions)%1%2To-201 Shikra – un chasseur de supériorité aérienne de 5e génération du CSAT%1%2A-149 Gryphon – un chasseur de combat avancé de 4e génération de l'AAF%1%2Sentinel – un drone aérien de combat de l'OTAN destiné aux porte-avions%1%2Gilets d'officiers d'appontage – gilets aux couleurs des différentes unités d'appontage%1%2Présentation des chasseurs – envolez-vous au-dessus d'Altis et prenez part à des combats air-air ou air-sol%1%2Bande originale – un nouveau morceau sur le thème des chasseurs%1%2Succès - des &lt;a href='http://steamcommunity.com/stats/107410/achievements'&gt;Succès Steam&lt;/a&gt; supplémentaires%1</French>
        <Spanish>Hazte con el control de los cielos gracias a 3 cazas nuevos y a un vehículo de combate aéreo no tripulado. Pilota estos cazas rápidos y ágiles y hazte con la superioridad aérea para ofrecer apoyo aéreo en la exhibición dedicada, entre otras cosas, gracias al contenido descargable Arma 3 Jets.%1&lt;img size='9' shadow='0' image='A3\Data_F_Jets\Images\jets_fm_overview_co' /&gt;%1%2F/A-181 Black Wasp II: un caza embarcado de la OTAN de quinta generación.%1%2To-201 Shikra: un caza de superioridad aérea del CSAT de quinta generación.%1%2A-149 Gryphon: un caza AAF avanzado de cuarta generación.%1%2Sentinel: un vehículo de combate aéreo no tripulado de la OTAN.%1%2Chalecos de la tripulación de cabina: chalecos de colores para los diferentes miembros de la tripulación del portaaviones.%1%2Exhibición Cazas: asciende a lo más alto de Altis y realiza operaciones aire-aire y aire-tierra.%1%2Banda sonora oficial: una nueva pista de música muy adecuada para los cazas.%1%2Logros: un conjunto adicional de &lt;a href='http://steamcommunity.com/stats/107410/achievements'&gt;logros de Steam&lt;/a&gt;.%1</Spanish>
        <Italian>Domina i cieli sul campo di battaglia con 3 nuovi aerei da caccia e un velivolo da combattimento senza equippaggio. Siediti ai comandi dei jet da superiorità aerea e vola con velocità e agilità fornendo supporto aereo nella sezione Dimostrazioni dedicata e nel DLC di Arma 3 Jets.%1&lt;img size='9' shadow='0' image='A3\Data_F_Jets\Images\jets_fm_overview_co' /&gt;%1%2F/A-181 Black Wasp II – un jet imbarcato da caccia di quinta generazione NATO%1%2To-201 Shikra – un jet da caccia da superiorità aerea di quinta generazione CSAT%1%2A-149 Gryphon – un jet da caccia avanzato di quarta generazione AAF%1%2Sentinel – un aereo imbarcato tattico da combattimento privo di equipaggio NATO%1%2Gilet per l'equipaggio addetto al ponte – gilet colorati adatti ai vari ruoli sulla portaerei%1%2Dimostrazioni Jet da caccia – sfreccia per i cieli di Altis e conduci operazioni di combattimento aria-aria e aria-terra%1%2Colonna sonora ufficiale – un nuovo brano fedele al tema musicale dei jet%1%2Achievement – un set di &lt;a href='http://steamcommunity.com/stats/107410/achievements'&gt;Achievement di Steam&lt;/a&gt;%1 extra</Italian>
        <Polish>Zdominuj przestworza nad polem bitwy za pomocą 3 nowych myśliwców i bojowego bezzałogowego statku powietrznego. Pilotuj superszybkie i zwrotne myśliwce przewagi powietrznej i udzielaj wsparcia jednostkom naziemnym w trybie prezentacji w ramach DLC Arma 3 Jets.%1&lt;img size='9' shadow='0' image='A3\Data_F_Jets\Images\jets_fm_overview_co' /&gt;%1%2F/A-181 Black Wasp II – myśliwiec odrzutowy CSAT 5. generacji dostosowany do lotniskowców%1%2To-201 Shikra – myśliwiec odrzutowy przewagi powietrznej CSAT 5. generacji%1%2A-149 Gryphon – zaawansowany myśliwiec odrzutowy AAF 4. generacji%1%2Sentinel – bojowy bezzałogowy statek powietrzny NATO dostosowany do lotniskowców%1%2Kamizelki załogi pokładowej – różnokolorowe kamizelki dla różnych członków załogi lotniskowca%1%2Prezentacja myśliwców odrzutowych – wzbij się w przestworza nad Altis i weź udział w pojedynkach powietrznych oraz nalotach bombowych%1%2Oficjalna ścieżka dźwiękowa – nowy utwór inspirowany motywem odrzutowców%1%2Osiągnięcia – zestaw dodatkowych &lt;a href='http://steamcommunity.com/stats/107410/achievements'&gt;osiągnięć Steam&lt;/a&gt;%1</Polish>
        <Russian>Доминируйте в небе над полем боя с 3 новыми истребителями и беспилотными летательными аппаратами. Летайте на быстрых и маневренных истребителях для обеспечения поддержки с воздуха в специальном режиме Демонстрации. И еще многое другое ждет вас в Arma 3 Jets.%1&lt;img size='9' shadow='0' image='A3\Data_F_Jets\Images\jets_fm_overview_co' /&gt;%1%2F/A-181 Black Wasp II – палубный истребитель НАТО пятого поколения%1%2To-201 Shikra – истребитель CSAT пятого поколения, предназначенный для завоевания господства в воздухе%1%2A-149 Gryphon – современный истребитель AAF четвертого поколения%1%2Sentinel – палубный беспилотный летательный аппарат НАТО%1%2Жилеты палубной команды – цветные жилеты для различных персонажей на авианосце%1%2Демонстрация истребителей – покорите небеса над Алтисом и сразитесь с вражескими самолетами и средствами ПВО%1%2Официальный саундтрек – новая музыкальная композиция, соответствующая теме самолетов%1%2Достижения – набор дополнительных &lt;a href='http://steamcommunity.com/stats/107410/achievements'&gt;Достижений в Steam&lt;/a&gt;%1</Russian>
        <German>Dominiere den Himmel über dem Schlachtfeld mit 3 neuen Kampfjets und einem unbemannten Kampfflugzeug. Fliege im Arma 3 Jets DLC schnelle und wendige Jagdflugzeuge, um in der speziell zugeschnittenen Präsentation Luftunterstützung zu liefern und vieles mehr.%1&lt;img size='9' shadow='0' image='A3\Data_F_Jets\Images\jets_fm_overview_co' /&gt;%1%2F/A-181 Black Wasp II – ein trägergestützter NATO-Kampfjet der fünften Generation%1%2To-201 Shikra – ein CSAT-Jagdflugzeug der fünften Generation%1%2A-149 Gryphon – ein fortschrittlicher AAF-Kampfjet der vierten Generation%1%2Sentinel – ein unbemanntes, trägergestütztes NATO-Kampfflugzeug%1%2Deckbesatzungs-Westen – verschiedenfarbige Westen für unterschiedliche Rollen auf dem Träger%1%2Präsentation: Kampfjets – Starte in den Himmel über Altis und nimm an Luft-Luft- und Luft-Boden-Operationen teil%1%2Offizieller Soundtrack – ein neuer Musiktrack passend zum Jets-Thema%1%2Errungenschaften – eine Reihe zusätzlicher &lt;a href='http://steamcommunity.com/stats/107410/achievements'&gt;Steam-Errungenschaften&lt;/a&gt;%1</German>
        <Czech>Ovládněte nebe nad bojištěm ve 3 nových stíhacích letounech nebo v bezpilotním bojovém letounu. Ve speciální ukázce vyzkoušejte rychlé a obratné stíhací letouny vzdušné převahy a poskytněte leteckou podporu. To a mnoho dalšího v novém DLC Arma 3 Jets.%1&lt;img size='9' shadow='0' image='A3\Data_F_Jets\Images\jets_fm_overview_co' /&gt;%1%2F/A-181 Black Wasp II – proudový stíhací letoun NATO páté generace se startem z letadlové lodě%1%2To-201 Shikra – proudový stíhací letoun vzdušné převahy CSAT páté generace%1%2A-149 Gryphon – pokročilý proudový stíhací letoun AAF čtvrté generace%1%2Sentinel – bezpilotní bojový letoun NATO se startem z letadlové lodě%1%2Vesty palubního personálu – barevné vesty pro posádku letadlové lodě s různými rolemi%1%2Ukázka Stíhací letouny – vzlétněte nad Altis a zapojte se do bojových protivzdušných a protipozemních operací%1%2Oficiální soundtrack – nová skladba vhodná k tematice stíhacích letounů%1%2Achievementy – několik nových &lt;a href='http://steamcommunity.com/stats/107410/achievements'&gt;achievementů služby Steam&lt;/a&gt;%1</Czech>
        <English>Dominate the skies over the battlefield in 3 new fighter aircraft and an Unmanned Combat Air Vehicle. Fly fast and agile air superiority jets to provide air support in the dedicated Showcase, and more, in the Arma 3 Jets DLC.%1&lt;img size='9' shadow='0' image='A3\Data_F_Jets\Images\jets_fm_overview_co' /&gt;%1%2F/A-181 Black Wasp II - a fifth generation NATO carrier-based fighter jet%1%2To-201 Shikra - a fifth generation CSAT air superiority fighter jet%1%2A-149 Gryphon - an advanced fourth generation AAF fighter jet%1%2Sentinel - a NATO carrier-based Unmanned Combat Air Vehicle%1%2Deck Crew Vests - colored vests for various characters roles on the carrier%1%2Showcase Fighter Jets - take to the skies over Altis and engage in Air-to-Air and Air-to-Ground operations%1%2Official Sound Track - a new music track befitting the jets theme%1%2Achievements - a set of extra &lt;a href='http://steamcommunity.com/stats/107410/achievements'&gt;Steam Achievements&lt;/a&gt;%1</English>
        <Portuguese>Domine o céu sobre o campo de batalha em 3 novos caças e um veículo de combate aéreo não tripulado. Pilote jatos de superioridade aérea rápidos e ágeis para prestar suporte aéreo no modo dedicado “Mostruário” e faça muito mais no DLC Arma 3 Jets.%1&lt;img size='9' shadow='0' image='A3\Data_F_Jets\Images\jets_fm_overview_co' /&gt;%1%2F/A-181 Black Wasp II: um caça baseado em porta-aviões da 5ª geração da OTAN%1%2To-201 Shikra: um caça de combate superior da 5ª geração da CSAT%1%2A-149 Gryphon: um caça de combate avançado da 4ª geração da AAF%1%2Sentinel: um veículo aéreo não tripulado da OTAN%1%2Trajes da equipe da plataforma: trajes coloridos para vários personagens e funções no porta-aviões%1%2Mostruário jatos de combate: domine os céus de Altis e mobilize-se em diversas operações ar-ar e ar-terra%1%2Trilha sonora oficial: uma nova faixa musical condizente com o tema de Jets%1%2Conquistas: uma conjunto extra de &lt;a href='http://steamcommunity.com/stats/107410/achievements'&gt; Conquistas Steam&lt;/a&gt;% 1</Portuguese>
        <Korean>3 신규 전투기와 무인전투항공기를 타고 전장 상공을 점령하세요. 신속하고 민첩한 제공권 제트기를 비행하여 Arma 3 Jets DLC 전용 쇼케이스 등에서 항공 지원을 제공하세요.%1&lt;img size='9' shadow='0' image='A3\Data_F_Jets\Images\jets_fm_overview_co' /&gt;%1%2F/A-181 Black Wasp II - 5세대 NATO 항공 모험 기반 전투기%1%2To-201 Shikra – 5세대 CSAT 제공권 전투기%1%2A-149 Gryphon – 최신 4세대 AAF 전투기%1%2Sentinel – NATO의 항공 모함 기반 무인전투항공기%1%2데크 승무원 조끼 – 항공 모함에서 다수의 캐릭터에 따라 구분한 색상별 조끼%1%2전투기 쇼케이스 – 알티스 영공으로 이동하여 공대공, 공대지 작전을 수행합니다.%1%2공식 사운드트랙 – 제트기별 테마에 어울리는 신규 음악 트랙입니다.%1%2업적 - &lt;a href='http://steamcommunity.com/stats/107410/achievements'&gt;Steam 업적&lt;/a&gt; 추가 세트%1</Korean>
        <Chinesesimp>驾驭全新的3款战机与1款无人战机, 你就可以称霸整个战场的领空. 你可以在任务展示中体验到新飞机的高速与敏捷性, 让你获得绝对的空优, 这些尽在ArmA3战机资料片中.%1&lt;img size='9' shadow='0' image='A3\Data_F_Jets\Images\jets_fm_overview_co' /&gt;%1%2F/A-181"黑蜂"2型战斗攻击机 - 北约的一台第五代舰载战斗攻击机%1%2To-201"褐耳鹰"战斗机 - 广协同盟的一台第五代空优战斗机%1%2A-149"狮鹫"战斗机 - Altis政府军的一台先进第四代战斗机%1%2"哨兵"无人战机 - 北约的一台舰载无人战机%1%2甲板人员背心 - 数种不同颜色的背心供航空母舰的甲板人员使用%1%2战斗机任务展示 - 前往Altis体验空对空与空对地的飞行任务%1%2官方原声带 - 一首配合战机主题的曲子%1%2成就 - 新的一组&lt;a href='http://steamcommunity.com/stats/107410/achievements'&gt;Steam成就&lt;/a&gt;%1</Chinesesimp>
        <Japanese>全 3 機種の新戦闘機、そして無人戦闘航空機 (UCAV) で戦場上空を制圧せよ。「Arma 3 Jets」DLC の専用ショーケースで高速飛行・超機動の制空ジェット戦闘機を飛ばして、航空支援を行ったりしてみませんか。%1&lt;img size='9' shadow='0' image='A3\Data_F_Jets\Images\jets_fm_overview_co' /&gt;%1%2F/A-181 ブラックワスプ II - NATO 軍の空母発艦型第五世代ジェット戦闘機%1%2To-201 シクラ – CSAT 軍の第五世代ジェット制空戦闘機%1%2A-149 グリフォン – AAF 軍の先進型第四世代ジェット戦闘機%1%2センチネル – NATO 軍の空母発艦型無人戦闘航空機%1%2甲板要員用ベスト – 空母の多様なキャラクター用の色付きベスト%1%2ショーケース・ジェット戦闘機 – アルティスの上空へと飛び出し、空中戦、そして空対地戦へと突入せよ%1%2公式サウンドトラック – Jets のテーマに沿った新規音楽トラック%1%2実績 - 追加の &lt;a href='http://steamcommunity.com/stats/107410/achievements'&gt;Steam 実績&lt;/a&gt;一式%1</Japanese>
      </Key>
    </Container>
  </Package>
</Project>